<node>
  <doctext>&lt;p&gt;
Hi there, and welcome to Everything2! You might be wondering what E2 actually &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt;; hopefully we can clear that up a bit.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
E2 is different things to different people: it's fact, sort of. It's fiction... in a way. It's prose on weekdays, poetry on weekends. It's a community with a community's complexities, from loves to rivalries to bad jokes and good stories. It's a place to grow and to learn, both to showcase your writing and about each other. In short: pretty much everything you could want. Pretty much ... everything!
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
We're an open forum, but we have content standards - writing well and following the site's guidelines are key to becoming a successful contributor. To help ease you in as smoothly as possible, we ask that you do a few things. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Your first stop should be [E2 Quick Start]. It'll give you the rundown on the site basics: what to write, how to format and integrate your writeups, and how to use our on-site messaging system. For specific help, you can check out the many topics in the [Everything FAQ]. Five minutes there can make a world of difference.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
We're a site for readers as much as writers, so take your time to get to know us! Look at this [page of cool|list of respected writeups] to see a selection of our current favorites.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
If you need us, we're here to help; every member, whether we are part of [the power structure of everything2|the administrative staff] or not, can answer questions for you. We have a [e2 mentoring sign-up|mentoring system], an [everything university|encyclopedia of useful information], [usergroup lineup|usergroups] to join, and a [E2 FAQ: Chatterbox|chat facility] for the asking of questions, as well as for indulging in buffoonery. It can get noisy in there, though &lt;i&gt;(see: buffoonery)&lt;/i&gt;, so you might have to raise your voice a bit. Somebody will hear you, we promise!
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Most importantly: have an open mind, and Welcome to Everything2!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Login: &lt;user&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Password: &lt;passwd&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
(Your password was randomly generated - you can change it to something more memorable by clicking the &quot;Edit Homenode&quot; link that appears next to your username on the right hand side of the screen after your first login.)
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks a lot,&lt;br /&gt;
Management&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;site_url&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</doctext>
  <createtime>1999-11-09 21:42:27</createtime>
  <totalvotes>0</totalvotes>
  <node_id>1923471</node_id>
  <edittime>0000-00-00 00:00:00</edittime>
  <type_nodetype>154</type_nodetype>
  <document_id>1923471</document_id>
  <author_user>113</author_user>
  <mail_id>1923471</mail_id>
  <title>new user mail backup</title>
</node>
