<node>
  <node_id>1986741</node_id>
  <title>bounty comments</title>
  <type_nodetype>153</type_nodetype>
  <vars>
    <key>Aerobe</key>
    <value>It's a good novel, for one!</value>
  </vars>
  <vars>
    <key>Ashigaru</key>
    <value>&amp;nbsp;</value>
  </vars>
  <vars>
    <key>Auduster</key>
    <value>The biggest badass of the British 17th Century...  England's Thomas Paine, only with a better moustache. A snotty, opinionated fiercely educated revolutionary who personally made life about as difficult for the Roundheads as anyone could hope. Imprisoned, unimprisoned, imprisoned again...  Makes Ben Franklin look like a royalist.  The man deserves a decent writeup.</value>
  </vars>
  <vars>
    <key>Auspice</key>
    <value>We've got the [Tree of Life] well-noded, now tell me all about the dark side. Bonus points may be award for separate nodes about the dark aspects of each of the sefira.</value>
  </vars>
  <vars>
    <key>Bitriot</key>
    <value>The company that founded Everything/E2. Fell in the dot-com bust, leaving this community as an imprint.  A good writeup will earn a C! and a node audit from me and, considering the subject matter, probably a toehold in E2 lore.</value>
  </vars>
  <vars>
    <key>Clockmaker</key>
    <value>The node is terribly subpar, with the first writeup as of the time of writing consisting of about 50% aggressive falsehood by volume. A good writeup that doesn't talk nonsense about unsubstantiated &#239;&#191;&#189;primordial mythologies&#239;&#191;&#189; will earn a ching, and I can egg you until I get tired of it.</value>
  </vars>
  <vars>
    <key>GhettoAardvark</key>
    <value>test</value>
  </vars>
  <vars>
    <key>Glowing Fish</key>
    <value>We should have something: I would prefer a writeup that gave his biography and explained the importance of his works, but just about anything would be good.</value>
  </vars>
  <vars>
    <key>Halspal</key>
    <value>Thoughtful and soulful writeups will earn rare signed first edition copies of Halspal's book [Humane Society] and his infinite favor. See www.nevilshute.org for the starter kit.</value>
  </vars>
  <vars>
    <key>Heisenberg</key>
    <value>I'd be happy to send every noder with a good new w/u about Italo Disco a cool mix cd with my favourite (you guessed it) ITALO DISCO!!</value>
  </vars>
  <vars>
    <key>Heitah</key>
    <value>C! guaranteed. I want a scientific explanation please :)</value>
  </vars>
  <vars>
    <key>Jet-Poop</key>
    <value>A ching is a stone guarantee for a well-done and complete writeup. Node audits or other rewards can be discussed.</value>
  </vars>
  <vars>
    <key>JohnnyCashed</key>
    <value>Not looking for the band, looking for a commentary on the idea that boys are failing in schools, etc. and the counter argument it's because we're feminizing education. In short, there's arguments for and against it being because of a change in the nature of school and work, and another saying it's affirmative action. I'd like a female noder to examine these issues critically.</value>
  </vars>
  <vars>
    <key>Morwen</key>
    <value>Why in the hell is there no writeup for the TV series? If you do a good job, you get a C! from me, and can request which original series Doctor Who story I write up next. I do not just want to hear about [Emma Peel], you must discuss all the main characters who worked with Steed (including boring old Keel). Try this site for starters: [http://theavengers.tv/forever/guide.htm]</value>
  </vars>
  <vars>
    <key>OldMiner</key>
    <value>This isn't a real bounty, sorry.</value>
  </vars>
  <vars>
    <key>Oolong</key>
    <value>I will also cook [triple-cooked chips] for you if I get the chance.</value>
  </vars>
  <vars>
    <key>Pericles McGee</key>
    <value>A C! for a good writeup on this [Ho-Chunk] myth.</value>
  </vars>
  <vars>
    <key>Posmella</key>
    <value>Cover the book and film well, and you'll get an upvote, a C!, and a message of appreciation.</value>
  </vars>
  <vars>
    <key>ReiToei</key>
    <value>Could do with a bit of updating. So to speak.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rewards? Undying love and C!, and if you are really good, a gift from a friendly god.</value>
  </vars>
  <vars>
    <key>Simulacron3</key>
    <value>To the moon on a magic carpet, and just maybe back.</value>
  </vars>
  <vars>
    <key>StuartO)))</key>
    <value>It is absurd that there is a writeup about a skateboarding trick in this Node but nothing on Madonna the singer born Madonna Louise Ciccone .</value>
  </vars>
  <vars>
    <key>Tem42</key>
    <value>I'm too lazy. You do it. </value>
  </vars>
  <vars>
    <key>The Custodian</key>
    <value>The man just passed away and deserves recognition.</value>
  </vars>
  <vars>
    <key>TheDeadGuy</key>
    <value>Actress who played Carmen in [The Big Sleep],  I need more information.  We'll discuss rewards in a coffee shop later on.</value>
  </vars>
  <vars>
    <key>Timeshredder</key>
    <value>It's been hanging so long, and someone should fill it.</value>
  </vars>
  <vars>
    <key>Wuukiee</key>
    <value>It needs a good writeup. I've been meaning to do it myself for years, and have not to this day gotten around to it. Someone do this awesome event justice.</value>
  </vars>
  <vars>
    <key>Zephronias</key>
    <value>WRITE A STORY. WRITE IT NOW (please).</value>
  </vars>
  <vars>
    <key>andycyca</key>
    <value>A writeup by someone with more D&amp;amp;D experience than myself would be greatly appreciated. GP reward may increase based on quality and links to related Tolkien/D&amp;amp;D materials</value>
  </vars>
  <vars>
    <key>avalyn</key>
    <value>This team ought to have a better writeup by now. Give it a go!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reward: A C! for each deserving writeup and a maximum of fifty (50) upvotes of your other stuff. If I've already voted on all of your writeups, I'll give you 200 GP and a special bonus, to be determined based on your level.</value>
  </vars>
  <vars>
    <key>borgo</key>
    <value>C! awaits anybody who does this justice</value>
  </vars>
  <vars>
    <key>cassparadox</key>
    <value>We've got the [Tree of Life] well-noded, now tell me all about the dark side. Bonus points may be award for separate nodes about the dark aspects of each of the sefira.</value>
  </vars>
  <vars>
    <key>civilwaractionfigure</key>
    <value>Spending time on research on a woman who stalks me in music stores called Shakira and I cannot figure out why she is doing this based on writeups that are existing there now and very worried. Help.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A really informative writeup will get you a blessing and a C! from some of my elitist old guard friends. A writeup that helps me with the stalking problem will get you a computer transmitted photograph of me, Berhardt Goats, being kissed by two lesbians.</value>
  </vars>
  <vars>
    <key>dannye</key>
    <value>After all the work that [JessicaPierce] put into this site, this nodeshell has been sitting there begging to be filled on her homenode for what seems like forever. Do it for her. And I'll ching it. Promise. </value>
  </vars>
  <vars>
    <key>decoy hunches</key>
    <value>C! for work that is lipogrammatic and/or anagrammatic or employs a different interesting constraint.</value>
  </vars>
  <vars>
    <key>e2hockey</key>
    <value>Not currently a nodeshell, but easily could be.&lt;br&gt;&lt;small&gt;It's a sort of a threat, you see[Slartibartfast|.]&lt;/small&gt;  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;bad writeup - A good ol'-fashioned sweater-over-head [goon]ing&lt;br&gt; good writeup - weblogged to the [e2hockey] page&lt;br&gt; amazing writeup - upvotes &amp;amp; C!s from the user group&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Contact [Lord Brawl])</value>
  </vars>
  <vars>
    <key>e2reneta</key>
    <value>When you steal the mantle of most influential animator from Walt Disney, when they buy your company to get you to save their ailing company, when you've got Hiyao Miyazaki's phone number programmed into your cell, I think you deserve a writeup here.</value>
  </vars>
  <vars>
    <key>eh2</key>
    <value>Good writeup - weblogged to the [eh2] page&lt;br&gt; amazing writeup - upvotes &amp;amp; C!s from the user group&lt;br&gt; jawdroppingly awesome writeup - A Tim Horton's gift certificate&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Contact [Lord Brawl])</value>
  </vars>
  <vars>
    <key>gnarl</key>
    <value>If reviewed as well as described, a Ching.</value>
  </vars>
  <vars>
    <key>jessicaj</key>
    <value>Unfinished at the time of the composer's death this moving piece deserves investigation and recognition. A stunning, definitive writeup will be taken to the editorial staff for review and potential endorsement. </value>
  </vars>
  <vars>
    <key>joer</key>
    <value>Tallu was, as they say, &quot;mad, bad, and dangerous to know&quot;, but the existing w/u gives us no idea why. She had an interesting history, both because of her family, and as a performer. Make us proud, and not only will you get 300 GP, but a disc containing all her '[The Big Show]' broadcasts still existing. Aside from the kitsch value, it's a great listen into the last gasp of big network radio.</value>
  </vars>
  <vars>
    <key>kthejoker</key>
    <value>bad writeup - a &quot;John 3:16&quot; sign pointed in your direction&lt;br /&gt; good writeup - a C! from me and possibly a visit from [Morgana the Kissing Bandit]&lt;br /&gt; amazing writeup - 50 GP and an autographed picture of the [San Diego Chicken]</value>
  </vars>
  <vars>
    <key>liveforever</key>
    <value>I'll award up to 50 GP, depending on quality -- and a ching if it merits it. </value>
  </vars>
  <vars>
    <key>mauler</key>
    <value>One of the main regions of Spain, the one which produced most of the famous conquistadors.</value>
  </vars>
  <vars>
    <key>misterfuffie</key>
    <value>The officlal/unofficial motto of the Wild Weasels. Give me a history of the motto and the Wild Weasels. A good writeup earns a guaranteed ching. Other prizes may also apply!</value>
  </vars>
  <vars>
    <key>randombit</key>
    <value>I'll upvote and ching a solid writeup. I'll even mail you a postcard, if you want.</value>
  </vars>
  <vars>
    <key>schizophasic</key>
    <value>Probably chinged because [Veruca Salt] is better than Everything.</value>
  </vars>
  <vars>
    <key>tentative</key>
    <value>I want to know everything about training a sheep dog (also known as working or herding dog), using a sheep or cow dog, on the farm, shearing time, in shows, basically a very, very detailed thing about every aspect of a sheepdog's life. If it is not everything, I'll frown on it. If it has everything, you'll probably get a ching and endless praise. </value>
  </vars>
  <vars>
    <key>wertperch</key>
    <value>She deserves a good biography.</value>
  </vars>
  <vars>
    <key>wordnerd</key>
    <value>He played Eomer in the Lord of the Rings and Bones in the new Star Trek reboot. I think that gives him sufficient geek cred to hang out on this site.</value>
  </vars>
</node>
