<node>
  <doctext>originally by s_alanet (May 9 2002)
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Try as I may, try as I might. I can't get this thing to work on Netscape, IE, and Opera. The current code does. While DOM compliance might be nice, if it ain't really broke, let's not play with it.</doctext>
  <createtime>2003-01-12 16:47:32</createtime>
  <node_id>1414309</node_id>
  <htmlcode_id>1414309</htmlcode_id>
  <edittime>0000-00-00 00:00:00</edittime>
  <code>function replyTo(s, c) {
        //alert(&quot;foo!&quot;);
	if (c == 0) {
		if (document.form1.autofill.checked == 0) {
			return;
		}
	}
	document.form1.message.value = &quot;/msg &quot; + s + &quot; &quot;;
	document.form1.message.focus();
}

function clearReply() {
	document.form1.message.value = &quot;&quot;;
}

function checkAll(){
// Brief discussion of the validity of the next three lines of code
// Dom Level 1 Reference: 
//   http://www.w3c.org/TR/2000/WD-DOM-Level-1-20000929

// line +1 is valid because of &quot;The HTMLCollection object 
// has the following properties: length &quot;, and form1 being an
// HTMLCollection. &quot;item(index) This method returns a Node object.&quot;
// Ergo, saying item(1).length refers to the &quot;length&quot; of item #1.
// For checkboxes, this is probably not what you want. Saying
// item.length has no meaning under the DOM spec, except perhaps
// in that it would calculate the &quot;length&quot; of the item function...

// line +2 is valid because name is a property of all form elements.
// substring is a method of all strings (which name is).

// Line +3: checked is a property of check boxes. To be anal, you'd want
// to dump the type of the form item and see if it's (first) a
// HTMLInputElement, and (second) if property &quot;type&quot; is right.

// Ok. Now, I haven't actually run this code in context (I can't
// without lots of effort). But if you're running on a DOM level 1
// compliant browser, this should work.

// (If you're going to criticize this code, you'd best RT_F_M.)

    for (i=0; i &lt; document.form1.length; i++) {
      if(document.form1.item[i].name.substring(0,9) == &quot;deletemsg&quot;)
          {document.form1.item[i].checked=1;}
    }
}
</code>
  <type_nodetype>1382262</type_nodetype>
  <document_id>1414309</document_id>
  <title>Message Inbox JavaScript DOM compliance patch backup</title>
</node>
