<node>
  <doctext>[{linkGroupMessages:GrouchyOldMan}]

&lt;h3&gt;The Copyright Salvage Team Charter&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Copyright Salvage Team (CST) was formed&amp;nbsp; in mid August 2003 in
response to the new E2 copyright policy.&amp;nbsp; The CST originally operated under
the auspices of the [E2 Quest: Copyright Redemption|Copyright Redemption Quest]&amp;nbsp;
During the Quest, the Copyright Salvage Team (CST) reviewed
over 550 writeups submitted by 97 different E2 authors. 535 of the writeups were
deemed compliant with the new policy and the authors were encouraged to add the
[CST Approved] tag as an indication that the writeup had passed a formal
inspection. The text of these
reviews was stored for future reference in a series of documents titled [CST_Storage_n].&amp;nbsp; A summary of the compliant reviews was
created in [Copyright Compliant Lyrics and Poems].&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Quest formally ended on 22 September 2003, and the idea of continuing the
CST as an ongoing service to the E2 community was considered.&amp;nbsp; This
document formalizes the results of those discussions and provides a working
framework for the CST's continuing operations.&amp;nbsp; It is intended to be a
working model that will evolve as new ideas and techniques emerge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;Mission &amp;amp; Mandate&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The CST's primary purpose is to provide a service to the E2 community,
authors, editors and management.&amp;nbsp; We perceive that the transition to a
copyright-compliant database has benefits for all involved and our goal is to
facilitate that transition wherever possible.&amp;nbsp; To date we have identified
three primary areas where we feel we can be of service:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Reviews. &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;The CST will provide quick and competent reviews of
  existing or draft writeups for compliance with the [E2 Copyright Changes|E2 copyright
  policy].&amp;nbsp;
  Compliant writeups will be authorized to add the [CST Approved] link
  indicating that they have been reviewed.&amp;nbsp; It is important that authors
  understand that the [CST Approved] ONLY indicates compliance with the E2
  copyright policy and does not guarantee that their writeup won't be nuked for
  other reasons.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Advice.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt; The CST has developed a certain expertise in the
  application of the E2 copyright policy through significant hands on experience
  applying it to a wide variety of writeups.&amp;nbsp; This experience is a resource
  that can be tapped by the E2 community and the CST intends to respond to
  copyright-related questions from any source.&amp;nbsp; It is important to note
  however that none of the CST members have professional legal experience and
  the E2 management has the final word in all cases.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Rescue or Removal.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt; Typically the CST_Group attempts to work with authors to bring writeups into compliance with the [E2 FAQ: Copyrighted Material|E2 copyright policy]. When this process fails, the CST_Group includes Content Editors, who take responsibility for removing non-compliant writeups from the database as required.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h5&gt; Questions and comments: /msg Content_Salvage &lt;/h5&gt;</doctext>
  <createtime>2004-01-12 21:08:57</createtime>
  <node_id>1512726</node_id>
  <edittime>0000-00-00 00:00:00</edittime>
  <type_nodetype>16</type_nodetype>
  <document_id>1512726</document_id>
  <title>CST_Group</title>
</node>
