<node>
  <doctext>&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;big&gt;&lt;b&gt;Welcome to e2hockey!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/big&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you enjoy fast-paced, almost non-stop action, the subtle scratching sound skates make on ice, the sharp SLAP! of a stick on a puck, the roar of a goal foghorn or an excited rabid crowd, the dull thud of a puck rebounding off end boards, the excitement of your team scoring a goal, and even in some situations the DING! of a puck hitting a post or crossbar -- if you LOVE HOCKEY -- this is the group for you!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No matter what team you follow, be it the Detroit Red Wings or the St. Louis Blues, these are the things we all have in common. I founded this group because I thought it was about time that all of us E2 hockey fans had a place to talk hockey, to nodevertise our hockey writeups, to console each other in the dark days of the 2004-2005 non-season. I have noticed there are quite a few hockey fans on E2, maybe more fans of that sport than any other sport (that I've noticed anyway). It's time for us all to come together. Let's try to recruit &lt;i&gt;all&lt;/i&gt; the E2 hockey fans, find them, seek them out, /msg them (I'm currently doing so). Let everybody - who would care - about our wonderful new group.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So come, rejoice, praise the sport's excitement, rant about officials or the CBA, no subject is taboo!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I, &lt;a title=&quot;artman2003&quot; href=&quot;/index.pl?node=artman2003&amp;lastnode_id=1147724&quot;&gt;artman2003&lt;/a&gt; am the founder and &lt;a title=&quot;avalyn&quot; href=&quot;/index.pl?node=avalyn&amp;lastnode_id=1147724&quot;&gt;avalyn&lt;/a&gt; is a charter member. A complete member list is below:&lt;/p&gt;  
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;!-- This links to the usergroup message archive (if enabled for the group). Not sure what the username param does, if anything. LB. --&gt;
[{linkGroupMessages:artman2003}]
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;!-- This enables the weblog (when it is turned on) with 3 display items --&gt;
[{weblog:3}]
&lt;hr&gt;</doctext>
  <totalvotes>0</totalvotes>
  <createtime>2005-03-16 15:36:29</createtime>
  <node_id>1707759</node_id>
  <edittime>0000-00-00 00:00:00</edittime>
  <type_nodetype>16</type_nodetype>
  <document_id>1707759</document_id>
  <author_user>1489024</author_user>
  <title>e2hockey</title>
</node>
