<node>
  <doctext>&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
&lt;b&gt;&lt;big&gt;&lt;big&gt;&lt;&lt;big&gt;&lt;big&gt;&lt;big&gt;&lt;big&gt;&lt;big&gt;&lt;big&gt;
&amp;#1576;&amp;#1587;&amp;#1605; &amp;#1575;&amp;#1604;&amp;#1604;&amp;#1607; &amp;#1575;&amp;#1604;&amp;#1585;&amp;#1581;&amp;#1605;&amp;#1606; &amp;#1575;&amp;#1604;&amp;#1585;&amp;#1581;&amp;#1610;&amp;#1605;

&lt;/big&gt;&lt;/big&gt;&lt;/big&gt;&lt;/big&gt;&lt;/big&gt;&lt;/big&gt;&lt;/big&gt;&lt;/big&gt;
&lt;br&gt;In the Name of [Allah], the most Benevolent, the most Merciful
&lt;/b&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
e2muslims is a usergroup for Muslim noders but we welcome messages from non-Muslims who seek knowledge or have any questions about [Islam].
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
This is a forum for Muslim noders to talk amongst their brothers and sisters. As a group of noders our goals are:
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Reviewing the current Islamic related nodes on E2&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
As part of this process we will set about fixing any misconceptions that may have crept into the database. 
There has been a lot of progress in this area and this group will provide a means for Muslims noders to
communicate and seek assistance from one another. The [Islam] metanode by [E2Religion] is an excellent starting point for this task.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Response Team&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Users are encouraged to highlight new writeups which have a bearing on Islam, we should encourage the author with 
helpful advice, references, and general guidance through answering of queries. If the writeup requires further clarification then we
should seek to provide a balanced perspective. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Regular noding&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
We should actively undertake Islamic noding projects. There is much scope for new writeups, this group will allow us to 
distribute the workload and should hopefully make cross-referencing, and dealing with biased opinion much easier. 
</doctext>
  <node_id>1472175</node_id>
  <type_nodetype>16</type_nodetype>
  <title>e2muslims</title>
</node>
