<node>
  <doctext>&lt;em&gt;aka. Johann Excellent Nodeshell Rehabilitation Center And Everything2 Cocktail Party&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
Est. 2003&lt;br&gt;
&lt;small&gt;FOR THE&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;big&gt;A&lt;/big&gt;DVANCEMENT and &lt;big&gt;P&lt;/big&gt;ROMOTION&lt;br&gt;
&lt;small&gt;OF&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;big&gt;&lt;big&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HIPBONE GAMES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/big&gt;&lt;/big&gt;&lt;br&gt;
In their various forms, &lt;em&gt;Especially&lt;/em&gt; to everything&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt;-specific variations and rules.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;small&gt;&amp;#91;[all matters of what becomes visible, and when|BARE BOARDS]&amp;#93; -- &amp;#91;[the curvature of the earth is obscured by local noise|ONGOING GAMES]&amp;#93; -- &amp;#91;[GAMES GALLERY]&amp;#93;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr&gt;
From [Italo Calvino]'s [Invisible Cities], Trading Cities 4 
&lt;blockquote&gt;In Ersilia, to establish the relationships that sustain the city's life, the inhabitants stretch strings from the corners of the houses, [white] or [black] or [gray] or [black and white|black-and-white] according to whether they mark a relationship of [bloodline|blood], of [trade route|trade], [course of power|authority], [bureaucracy |agency]. When the strings become so numerous that [you can no longer pass among them], the inhabitants leave: the houses are dismantled; [only the strings and their supports remain]. From a mountainside, camping with their household goods, Ersilia's refugees look at the [labyrinth] of taut strings and poles that rise in the plain. That is the city of Ersilia still, [and they are nothing]. They rebuild Ersilia elsewhere. They [weave a similar pattern of strings] which they would like to be more complex and at the same time more regular than the other. Then they abandon it and take themselves and their houses still farther away. &lt;br&gt;
Thus, when traveling in the territory of Ersilia, you come upon the ruins of abandoned cities, without the walls which do not last, without the [bones of the dead] which the wind rolls away: [spider webs of intricate relationships seeking a form]. 
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</doctext>
  <core>0</core>
  <reputation>0</reputation>
  <lockedby_user>0</lockedby_user>
  <totalvotes>0</totalvotes>
  <locktime>0000-00-00 00:00:00</locktime>
  <createtime>2003-07-08 00:08:00</createtime>
  <hits>0</hits>
  <node_id>1475035</node_id>
  <edittime>0000-00-00 00:00:00</edittime>
  <type_nodetype>16</type_nodetype>
  <document_id>1475035</document_id>
  <author_user>399547</author_user>
  <package>0</package>
  <title>Ersilians</title>
</node>
