<node>
  <doctext>&lt;p&gt;
This document is not current, and is kept only for archival purposes. Please refer to [Everything2 Help] for all up-do-date help documents.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;
[The Power Structure of Everything2|The administration] does 
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;
take the voting and experience point system all that seriously.
&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p align=center&gt;&lt;big&gt;&lt;big&gt;&lt;big&gt;&lt;big&gt;&lt;strong&gt;
&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;Woe to those who do.&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/big&gt;&lt;/big&gt;&lt;/big&gt;&lt;/big&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p align=center&gt;&lt;big&gt;&lt;big&gt;
XP is an [imaginary] number granted to you by an&lt;br&gt;
[anonymous] stranger. Treat it as such.
&lt;/big&gt;&lt;/big&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p align=center&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Please see the table below to figure out when you first receive votes and [C!]'s,&lt;br&gt;then read through this for a brief explanation of how the [E2] XP system works.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Votes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Level 2 users and up can vote. To vote on any given [writeup], simply click on the + or - icons to the left of the [timestamp].  You can click + or - on each writeup of a node and vote on all them at once by then clicking the &lt;strong&gt;vote!&lt;/strong&gt; button located below the last writeup and before the [soft link] box.  The '[Reputation]' number will then appear in the header of the writeup with a parenthetical breakdown of positive and negative votes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Use these votes &lt;u&gt;wisely&lt;/u&gt;!&lt;/strong&gt; Editors will be performing [Everything User Search|user-searches] on users regularly and checking their best and worst work, from the [rep] perspective. The reputation of a writeup doesn't mean it will be deleted, nor does it mean it will &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; be deleted. It merely acts as one more way to qualify written work and to help editors find what can often be a weak writeup. The editor will then usually delete the writeup, [msg] the author with a [E2 FAQ: Klaproth|Klaproth] message, and explain what the author should best do to improve the writeup and repost it. If one of your writeups is deleted, you will lose the &lt;strong&gt;one&lt;/strong&gt; [XP] you received for creating it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Voting and deletion are two ways we try to keep quality [writeup|writeups] coming in - a hastily/poorly written writeup will often cost a user XP.  Conversely, if your writeups are voted up by your fellow users, you will gain experience points. Details are below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
You don't gain voting powers instantly upon reaching the new level: votes and C!s refresh at midnight server time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;C!s&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
The most common power is &quot;Cooling&quot; (also known as &quot;C!ing&quot; or &quot;chinging&quot;). Beginning at 4th level, users will get the ability to cool an &lt;em&gt;individual&lt;/em&gt; writeup by clicking the [C!] located next to the voting buttons. This will give the author of the writeup &lt;b&gt;ten&lt;/b&gt; XP, and kick the writeup to the front page and the [Cool Archive] for all to see. Users get a certain number of C!s per day, depending upon their level.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Use these chings &lt;u&gt;wisely!&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; Just because you have chings doesn't mean you should use them with careless abandon. Most users view a writeup's chings as an endorsement of &lt;em&gt;quality&lt;/em&gt; regardless of the impulsive reason you may have chosen to bestow that &quot;Attaboy&quot;. &lt;em&gt;Do you really want your name to be associated with something that we might consider to be stupid ten minutes/days/months from now?&lt;/em&gt; Think twice before you click on that C!; chings spent in haste can be regretted in leisure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
A writeup can be C!d &lt;em&gt;any number of times,&lt;/em&gt; but only &lt;strong&gt;once&lt;/strong&gt; by any given user.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;XP&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
The &quot;percentage chances&quot; are another way to encourage interaction with the Everything system: Every time you vote or get voted on there is a percentage chance that your XP will increase (or decrease, if your writeup gets voted on negatively).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Finally, you will have five [XP] for each [writeup] under your belt, and you will gain five XP for each writeup you make. If each writeup is created using the guidelines detailed in [The perfect node], they will pay off many times over in XP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The voting/level system:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(Note: You must meet &lt;em&gt;both&lt;/em&gt; requirements to reach a level, and you lose the level if you drop below either requirement.). Once you have reached level 2, you may also qualify to level up &lt;u&gt;without meeting the minimum writeup requirement&lt;/u&gt; by way of the [Honor Roll], which factors in your writeups' reputation and rewards those users whose work performs above average. The maximum gain under the Honor Roll system is to effectively double your writeup count for leveling-up purposes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Your user level is in bold.&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table border=&quot;1&quot; cellpadding=&quot;2&quot; cellspacing=&quot;1&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;th&gt;Level&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th&gt;Level Title&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th&gt;XP&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th&gt;Writeups Req&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th&gt;Votes per Day&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th&gt;[C!]s per Day&lt;/th&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;

[%

use Everything::Experience; 

my $TITLES = getVars(getNode('level titles', 'setting'));
my $VOTES = getVars(getNode('level votes', 'setting'));
my $EXP = getVars(getNode('level experience', 'setting'));
my $COOLS = getVars(getNode('level cools', 'setting'));
my $WRITEUP = getVars(getNode('level writeups', 'setting'));

my $max = 12;
my $str;
my $userLevel;

if (getId($USER) == $HTMLVARS{guest_user}) {
$userLevel = 0;
}
else {
$userLevel = getLevel($USER) || 0;
}

for(my $i = 1; $i &lt;= 12; $i++) {

  $str.=&quot;&lt;tr &quot;.($i == $userLevel ? &quot;style='font-weight:bold'&quot; :&quot;&quot;).&quot;&gt;&lt;TD&gt;$i&lt;/TD&gt;&lt;TD&gt;$$TITLES{$i}&lt;/TD&gt;&lt;TD&gt;$$EXP{$i}&lt;/TD&gt;&lt;TD&gt;$$WRITEUP{$i}&lt;/TD&gt;&lt;TD&gt;$$VOTES{$i}&lt;/TD&gt;&lt;TD&gt;$$COOLS{$i}&lt;/TD&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&quot;;
}

$str;
%]
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Powers:&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;i&gt;(More to come, mostly [level 6] and higher)&lt;/i&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Level 1 &amp;#8212; Access to your deleted writeups via [Node Heaven] - you'll need this, most new users lose half of their first ten writeups or so.  You'll have the ability to view someone's [E2 Scratch Pad|Scratch Pad] with [Scratch Pad Viewer], if the user permits it &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Level 2 &amp;#8212; [voting]; eligible for [Honor Roll] advancement &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Level 3 &amp;#8212; Can see who created a nodeshell using ANY E2 [user settings|theme], [Everything Poll Creator|create polls], and change [writeup settings|change the writeup header display]; can buy C!s at the [E2 Gift Shop] &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Level 4 &amp;#8212; [C!] power!;  may become a [E2 mentoring sign-up|mentor]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Level 5 &amp;#8212; Display an (uncopyrighted) image in your home node (Nope, no [porn] allowed!), ability to [create room]s in the [Chatterbox]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Level 6 &amp;#8212; Can reset the chatterbox topic by buying a token at the [E2 Gift Shop].&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Level 7 &amp;#8212; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Level 8 &amp;#8212; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Level 9 &amp;#8212; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Level 10 &amp;#8212; [Cloaking] oneself in the [Other Users] nodelet. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Level 11 &amp;#8212; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Level 12 &amp;#8212; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p align=center&gt;&lt;b&gt;You can [gain] or [lose] [XP] in the following ways &lt;i&gt;only&lt;/i&gt;:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Each writeup you turn in gives you five [XP]. If it's later deleted, you lose one XP.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;+10 XP each time one of your writeups is [C!]'d ([Cool Archive|Cooled] by another user and sent to the [Cool Archive])&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;33% chance of +1 XP every time you cast a [vote] for somone else's [writeup] - whether that vote be positive or negative.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;33% chance of gaining or losing one XP if your writeup is voted up or down by another user.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Every day after [level 2] you will be granted a certain number of votes to cast. For every 10 votes that you cast, you will be awarded a bonus of five [XP]. Furthermore, if you use all of your votes in any given 24-hour period, you will gain an additional five XP. These bonuses are in addition to any XP you gained via the 33% rule above. The [Everything2] clock is set to [UTC] time, votes/[C!]'s reset at midnight UTC. See the [Epicenter Nodelet] to view the current time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participating in an [Everything Quest] &lt;em&gt;within the given time frame &lt;/em&gt;. Everything Quests can be sponsored by any content editor or member of the gods group. There can be any number of them running at any given time. If you've a good idea for an Everything Quest, please msg an admin.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Being [bless]ed by a member of the gods group. (See [The Power Structure of Everything2])&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Getting &quot;[E2 FAQ: Eggs, Tokens, E2 Gift Shop and Wheel of Surprise|egged]&quot; or similar in the [chatterbox] by another user (+3XP)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Note:&lt;/strong&gt; If a writeup you've submitted has accrued a positive reputation and it is deleted, you &lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;will not&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &quot;lose&quot; any [XP] you'd already gained for the + votes. You will only lose 1 XP for losing 1 writeup. If your writeup has a negative [rep], deleting it will not increase your XP (though it will prevent future loss from downvotes on that writeup, obviously).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Gaining and losing one XP for adding and deleting also applies to &quot;housekeeping&quot; write-ups like [E2 Nuke Request|Writeup Deletion Request] and [Edit These E2 Titles|Node Title Edit]. It can be disconcerting to get the &quot;[Ack! You lost experience!]&quot; message from these, but that's life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p align=center&gt;
&lt;em&gt;back to&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;[Everything FAQ]&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</doctext>
  <createtime>2000-03-07 18:48:31</createtime>
  <totalvotes>0</totalvotes>
  <node_id>444459</node_id>
  <edittime>0000-00-00 00:00:00</edittime>
  <type_nodetype>14</type_nodetype>
  <document_id>444459</document_id>
  <author_user>315</author_user>
  <title>Archived: Voting/Experience System</title>
</node>
