<node>
  <doctext>&lt;p&gt;
This document is not current, and is kept only for archival purposes. Please refer to [Everything2 Help] for all up-do-date help documents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;An [Everything2 Help] Document&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p align=center&gt;&lt;big&gt;&lt;big&gt;
XP is an [imaginary] number granted to you by an&lt;br&gt;
[anonymous] stranger. Treat it as such.
&lt;/big&gt;&lt;/big&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Votes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Level 1 users and up can vote. To vote on any given [writeup], simply click on the + or - icons to the left of the [timestamp].  You can click + or - on each writeup of a node and vote on all them at once by then clicking the &lt;strong&gt;vote!&lt;/strong&gt; button located below the last writeup and before the [Links on Everything2|soft link] area near the bottom.  The '[Reputation]' number will then appear in the header of the writeup with a parenthetical breakdown of positive and negative votes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Use these votes &lt;em&gt;wisely&lt;/em&gt;!&lt;/strong&gt; Editors will be performing [Everything User Search|user-searches] on users regularly and checking their best and worst work, from the [rep] perspective. The reputation of a writeup doesn't mean it will be deleted, nor does it mean it will &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; be deleted. It merely acts as one more way to qualify written work and to help editors find what can often be a weak writeup. The editor will then usually try to suggest ways of improving the writeup, or delete it if it seems to be beyond redemption. If one of your writeups is deleted, you will lose &lt;strong&gt;five&lt;/strong&gt; [XP].&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Voting and deletion are two ways we try to keep quality [writeup|writeups] coming in - a hastily/poorly written writeup will often gain a negative reputation.  Conversely, if your writeups are voted up by your fellow users, you will gain XP. Details are below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Note: not all powers are gained instantly upon reaching a new level: votes and C!s refresh at midnight server time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;C!s&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
One important power is the ability to grant a &quot;C!&quot; (also known as &quot;C!ing&quot; or &quot;chinging&quot;). Beginning at 4th level, users will get the ability to C! an &lt;em&gt;individual&lt;/em&gt; writeup by clicking the [C!] located next to the voting buttons. This will give the author of the writeup &lt;b&gt;twenty&lt;/b&gt; XP, and kick the writeup to the front page and the [Cool Archive] for all to see.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Use these chings &lt;u&gt;wisely!&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; Just because you have chings doesn't mean you should use them with careless abandon. Most users view a writeup's chings as an endorsement of &lt;em&gt;quality&lt;/em&gt; regardless of the impulsive reason you may have chosen to bestow that &quot;Attaboy&quot;. &lt;em&gt;Do you really want your name to be associated with something that we might consider to be stupid ten minutes/days/months from now?&lt;/em&gt; Think twice before you click on that C!; chings spent in haste can be regretted in leisure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
A writeup can be C!d &lt;em&gt;any number of times,&lt;/em&gt; but only &lt;strong&gt;once&lt;/strong&gt; by any given user.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;XP&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
You will have five [XP] for each [writeup] under your belt, and you will gain five XP for each new writeup you make, in addition to all the XP you get when other people vote up your writeups. If each writeup is created using the guidelines detailed in [The perfect node], they will pay off many times over in XP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;The voting/level system:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(Note: You must meet &lt;em&gt;both&lt;/em&gt; requirements to reach a level, and you lose the level if you drop below either requirement).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;
Level   Level Title        XP   Writeups Req    Votes per Day   C!s per Day
    0   Initiate            *           NONE             NONE          NONE
    1   Novice            500             10               50          NONE
    2   Acolyte           900             20               50          NONE
    3   Scribe           1500             30               50          NONE
    4   Wordsmith        2300             40               50             1
    5   Crafter          3300             50               50             1
    6   Artificer        4500             60               50             1
    7   Chronicler       5900             70               50             1
    8   Chronicler       7500             80               50             1
    9   Encyclopedist    9300             90               50             1
   10   Archivist       11300            100               50             1
   11   Literatus       13500            110               50             1
   12   Laureate        16000            120               50             1
  n+1                  n+2500           n+10               50             1
.
.
.
&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For additional level stats, please visit [Level Settings].&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Powers:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Level 0 &amp;#8212; Joining Everything2 gives you the ability to [E2 Quick Start|contribute writeups], communicate with other members via the [Chatterbox] and message system, customise your view of the site in [User Settings], etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Level 1 &amp;#8212; Can [voting|vote] on E2 writeups by other users.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Level 2 &amp;#8212; Can [E2 Gift Shop|buy additional votes] at the [E2 Gift Shop].&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Level 3 &amp;#8212; Can buy [Easter Egg|easter eggs] at the [E2 Gift Shop]; Can [Everything Poll Creator|create polls].&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Level 4 &amp;#8212; [C!] power!;  may become a [E2 mentoring sign-up|mentor]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Level 5 &amp;#8212; Display an (uncopyrighted) image in your home node (Nope, no [porn] allowed!), ability to [create room]s in the [Chatterbox]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Level 6 &amp;#8212; Can reset the chatterbox topic by buying a token at the [E2 Gift Shop].&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Level 7 &amp;#8212; Can buy [Easter Egg|easter eggs] at the [E2 Gift Shop].&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Level 8 &amp;#8212; Can give [Easter Egg|easter eggs] to other users at the [E2 Gift Shop].&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Level 9 &amp;#8212; Can give votes to other users at the [E2 Gift Shop].&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Level 10 &amp;#8212; Can [Cloak] oneself in the [Other Users] nodelet. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Level 11 &amp;#8212; Can [Sanctify] other users with GP.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Level 12 &amp;#8212; Can purchase up to one extra C! per day at the [E2 Gift Shop]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Level 13 &amp;#8212; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;br&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;You can [gain] or [lose] [XP] in the following ways &lt;em&gt;only&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Each writeup you turn in gives you five [XP]. If it's later deleted, you lose that five XP.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;+20 XP each time one of your writeups is [C!]'d ([Cool Archive|Chinged] by another user and sent to the [Cool Archive])&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;+1 XP every time another user upvotes one of your [writeup|writeups].&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Note:&lt;/strong&gt; If a writeup you've submitted has accrued a positive reputation and it is deleted, you &lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;will not&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &quot;lose&quot; any [XP] you'd already gained for the + votes. You will only lose the 5 XP you got when you initially posted the writeup.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Gaining and losing XP for adding and deleting also applies to &quot;housekeeping&quot; write-ups like [E2 Nuke Request|Writeup Deletion Request] and [Edit These E2 Titles|Node Title Edit]. It can be disconcerting to gain and lose XP from these, but that's life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;You can [gain] or [lose] [GP] in the following ways, and possibly others:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Each time you cast a vote you have a 1 in 3 chance of gaining 1 GP.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;+ 10 GP every time you are [bless|blessed] by an administrator.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;+10 GP every time you are [sanctify|sanctified] by another user.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;+3 GP every time you are [easter egg|egged] by another user in the chatterbox.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;variable GP rewards for participating in [Everything Quest|Quests and contests].
&lt;li&gt;GP can be spent at the [E2 Gift Shop] and similar nodes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p align=center&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;[The Power Structure of Everything2|The administration] does not take the voting and experience point system too terribly seriously.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p align=center&gt;&lt;u&gt;Woe to those who do.&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p align=center&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;back to&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;[Everything2 Help]&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</doctext>
  <node_id>1962895</node_id>
  <type_nodetype>14</type_nodetype>
  <title>Archived: Voting/Experience System 2008</title>
</node>
