<node>
  <doctext>&lt;p&gt;
This document is not current, and is kept only for archival purposes. Please refer to [Everything2 Help] for all up-do-date help documents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;big&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note: [Klaproth] has retired. Most of this information no longer applies.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/big&gt;&lt;/p&gt;


[%
my $uid = getId($USER);
return unless ((exists $HTMLVARS{'group_content editors'}{$uid}) || (exists $HTMLVARS{'group_gods'}{$uid}));
my $nid = getId($NODE) || 0;
'&lt;p&gt;&lt;big&gt;&lt;big&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Editor only information&lt;/strong&gt; (this section only displays for CEs)&lt;/big&gt;&lt;/big&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to use the Klaproth automated deletion notification system:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
After you click on the button labeled &lt;em&gt;the killing floor II&lt;/em&gt;, you have two text boxes to work with.
The upper box is for Klaproth, the bottom box is so you may cut &amp;amp; paste the nuked node information to an editor log, if you so desire.
The section we are concerned with looks similar to the following:
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;form method=&quot;POST&quot; enctype=&quot;application/x-www-form-urlencoded&quot;&gt;
&lt;input type=&quot;hidden&quot; name=&quot;node_id&quot; value=&quot;'.$nid.'&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;table border=&quot;1&quot; cellpadding=&quot;5&quot; cellspacing=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;th&gt;reason*&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th&gt;title&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th&gt;node_id&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th&gt;author&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th&gt;options&lt;/th&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;text&quot; name=&quot;demo1&quot; size=&quot;16&quot; maxlength=&quot;127&quot;&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/index.pl?node_id='.$nid.'&quot;&gt;cute furry bunnies (thing)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;31415&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/index.pl?node_id=220&quot;&gt;nate&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;(mercifully) &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;text&quot; name=&quot;demo2&quot; size=&quot;16&quot; maxlength=&quot;127&quot;&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/index.pl?node_id='.$nid.'&quot;&gt;cute furry bunnies (idea)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;16777216&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;'.linkNode($USER).'&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;text&quot; name=&quot;demo3&quot; size=&quot;16&quot; maxlength=&quot;127&quot;&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/index.pl?node_id='.$nid.'&quot;&gt;cute furry bunnies (definition)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;9740&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/index.pl?node_id=176726&quot;&gt;Webster 1913&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;(InstaKill &lt;strong&gt;(not-InstaKill is better)&lt;/strong&gt;) &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p align=&quot;right&quot;&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;submit&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/index.pl?node_id='.$nid.'&quot;&gt;Changed my mind.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/form&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Under &lt;em&gt;reason&lt;/em&gt;, there is a text box you may add comments to.
Before filling in the reason why you are killing a writeup (WU), you must consider a few items:
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There is a little checkbox with your name. Check this box &lt;b&gt;only if&lt;/b&gt; you want your name to be appended to the Klaproth message. This option is very handy if you\'re nuking some of your earlier, non-Pulitzer work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This is a notification that a WU is dead. Try to keep the message direct and factual. Having Klaproth say that a WU is nuked because &quot;you just suck&quot; is counter-productive. While it may seem obvious to you, an experienced and trusted member of the E2 team, most of the time it is &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; obvious to the author. Placing a factual reason why it was killed will help them learn from the experience instead of feeling that someone is attacking them.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When you add text, it will be inserted into a pre-formatted message:&lt;br /&gt;
[Klaproth] says : I ate your writeup &quot;&lt;var&gt;Node Title Here&lt;/var&gt;&quot;.  &lt;var&gt;Your Reason Here&lt;/var&gt;. Node Heaven will become its new residence.&lt;br /&gt;
Try to complete the sentence using proper grammar (remember, you\'re setting an example).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will remain anonymous to the author unless you put your name in the reason text box.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Be professional, even if you feel the author is a troll. Take the high road, then /msg a [gods|god]. Nuking accounts is their department. If you have further questions about Klaproth, ask one of your fellow [Content Editors] or gods to assist you.
&lt;/p&gt;
';
%]


&lt;p&gt;&lt;big&gt;&lt;big&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Questions Only&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/big&gt;&lt;/big&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;small&gt;(These questions link to the question and answer on this page.)&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#whowhat&quot;&gt;Who or what is Klaproth?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#whymsg&quot;&gt;Why did Klaproth send me a message?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#howinform&quot;&gt;How do I get informed when a writeup of mine is deleted?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#undestruct&quot;&gt;How can I make a node &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; marked for destruction?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#whynotell&quot;&gt;Why didn't Klaproth tell me about one of my writeups being deleted?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#whynoreason&quot;&gt;Why do I keep getting messages from Klaproth without reasons why a node was killed?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#whynotdirect&quot;&gt;Why have a mindless bot forwarding nuke messages? Why don't the editors just tell us directly?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#noabuse&quot;&gt;If the editors and administrators are anonymous, what is to keep them from becoming abusive?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#avoid&quot;&gt;How can I avoid Klaproth?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#helpmywus&quot;&gt;What other suggestions can I get to improve my writeups?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#olddays&quot;&gt;What was it like in the olden days?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#whyexist&quot;&gt;Why did the establishment hire Klaproth?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#nameorigin&quot;&gt;Where did Klaproth's name come from?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;&lt;big&gt;&lt;big&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Questions and Answers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/big&gt;&lt;/big&gt;&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;dl&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;a name=&quot;whowhat&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;big&gt;Q&lt;/big&gt;: Who or what is [Klaproth]?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dd&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;big&gt;A&lt;/big&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: When a node is marked for deletion by an E2 [Content Editor] or [gods|administrator], Klaproth does his best to inform you of its demise. Some folks do not wish to be so informed, and there are ways to block his message of doom from reaching you, but the end result is the same. Sometimes, Klaproth will tell you why a node was killed. On rare occasions, he may tell you who killed the node if the editor adds their name to the message Klaproth sends you. Some editors just add the deleted node to the daily [editor logs]. Klaproth is a [bot] god that helps your deceased nodes' transition over to [Node Heaven]. Since he is not a human being (in actuality, he's a few lines of programming code), he cannot reply to your inquiries.  &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please do not msg him!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;  If you've a question about the deletion it would be wise to msg an [the power structure of everything 2|editor or member of the gods usergroup] - they will help you resolve the issue.&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;/dl&gt;

&lt;dl&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;a name=&quot;whymsg&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;big&gt;Q&lt;/big&gt;: Why did Klaproth send me a message?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dd&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;big&gt;A&lt;/big&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: Klaproth attempts to send you a message every time a writeup belonging to you is marked for destruction or instantly deleted by a [Content Editor] or [gods|administrator]. If Klaproth includes a message as to why a node was deleted, you should take care to heed his ghostly advice. Part of Klaproth's job is to help you improve your writing by pointing out why that particular node failed. You shouldn't waste your time by /msg'ing Klaproth, since he is busy conducting deceased nodes across the divide into Node Heaven. Instead, /msg an editor or administrator (identified by the &lt;strong&gt;$&lt;/strong&gt; or &lt;strong&gt;@&lt;/strong&gt; next to their names) to inquire why a node was killed, assuming Klaproth did not include the reason in his message to you. &lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;/dl&gt;

&lt;dl&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;a name=&quot;howinform&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;big&gt;Q&lt;/big&gt;: How do I get informed when a writeup of mine is deleted?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dd&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;big&gt;A&lt;/big&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: By default, you &lt;em&gt;are&lt;/em&gt; informed. It is possible to block messages from Klaproth if you so desire by visiting your [user settings] and unchecking the option for notification if a node of yours is deleted. Just like his friend [Cool Man Eddie], [Klaproth] will not become annoyed if you choose this option. If you are not getting messages from Klaproth, check this setting to see if it was accidentally set to reject notifications. You currently are [% $$VARS{no_notify_kill} ? 'ignoring Klaproth, so re-enable this setting if you wish to be informed about future deletions' : 'not ignoring Klaproth' ; %].&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;/dl&gt;

&lt;dl&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;a name=&quot;undestruct&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;big&gt;Q&lt;/big&gt;: How can I make a node &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; marked for destruction?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dd&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;big&gt;A&lt;/big&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: You can't. Once a writeup is so marked, it is conducted from this plane of existence into [Node Heaven]. Not even an E2 [gods|administrator] can resurrect a dead writeup. If Klaproth included a reason why it was deleted, you should heed Klaproth's wisdom. If you wish to, you can work on and improve your deceased work, then re-submit it as a new writeup under that node. If you choose this path, it is suggested that you ask a [Content Editor] to preview your writeup by posting it on your [% linkNode($USER,'homenode'); %], then inviting an editor to view it. If you decide to just cut and paste the node from Node Heaven, you risk the chance of having the node deleted &lt;em&gt;again&lt;/em&gt; with a 5 XP penalty. Note that it takes time for your dearly departed writeup to reach Node Heaven, typically a couple of days.&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;/dl&gt;

&lt;dl&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;a name=&quot;whynotell&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;big&gt;Q&lt;/big&gt;: Why didn't Klaproth tell me about one of my writeups being deleted?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dd&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;big&gt;A&lt;/big&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: Make sure the option is not set to block messages from Klaproth (see &lt;a href=&quot;#howinform&quot;&gt;above&lt;/a&gt;). Another common reason may be that an entire node filled with writeups was killed by an E2 [gods|administrator] en masse. Most of the time this happens when it is deemed to be a [GTYK|getting to know you] type node, but sometimes it may be due to a mis-spelled node title that was filled by folks who did not realize it, even though there is a properly spelled node that is already filled with  writeups. In this instance, you can typically copy your node from [Node Heaven] to the proper node, but you should check the writeups to ensure you aren't just repeating already added content. Normally, when an entire node is deleted with all writeups (including yours), you are messaged by the appropriate administrator that the writeup was killed, since Klaproth cannot tell you himself.&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;/dl&gt;

&lt;dl&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;a name=&quot;whynoreason&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;big&gt;Q&lt;/big&gt;: Why do I keep getting messages from Klaproth without reasons why a node was killed?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dd&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;big&gt;A&lt;/big&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: [Klaproth] is rather new, and as the editors get used to the system, more of them will take the time to add a personalized message detailing why it was killed. Sometimes, if the editor feels it is obvious (one-liner, abusive, not formatted), they may skip adding the message. If you get a Klaproth message without a reason why the node was killed, you can always ask an [Content Editor|editor] or [gods|administrator] for assistance.&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;/dl&gt;

&lt;dl&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;a name=&quot;whynotdirect&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;big&gt;Q&lt;/big&gt;: Why have a mindless bot forwarding nuke messages? Why don't the editors just tell us directly?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dd&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;big&gt;A&lt;/big&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: There are several reasons for having [Klaproth] as an intermediary. [Content Editors|Editors] and [gods|administrators] who kill a node risk having their own writeups hit by serial downvoters as a retaliatory action. While (in most cases) these volunteers have the XP to spare, it is still a concern to some. Keeping the database clean of trash is a thankless task, and having someone dump downvotes can be demoralizing. Klaproth allows these editors to do their job, and the majority of them add a note to the Klaproth message to tell you why it was deleted. Sometimes mistakes are made, and a good writeup may be deleted accidentally. If you have a question as to why a particular node was killed, just ask a friendly [gods|administrator] in the chatterbox via a /msg (they have an @ next to their nicks). When you get down to brass tacks, some editors just wish to remain anonymous. Who would want to log on daily to a page of conflict and abusive /msgs?&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;/dl&gt;

&lt;dl&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;a name=&quot;noabuse&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;big&gt;Q&lt;/big&gt;: If the editors and administrators are anonymous, what is to keep them from becoming abusive?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dd&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;big&gt;A&lt;/big&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: The [Content Editors|editors] and [gods|administrators] are human beings. Yes, there is a possibility that abuses may happen, which is why there are checks and balances in the system. When a node is killed, the person who killed it has their name marked on the writeup. Users cannot see it, but editors can. If you believe that someone is abusing the system, just send a message to [Lord Brawl] or another online administrator (they have an @ next to their nick). Abuse is not tolerated, period. If someone is taking advantage of their position, they will be held accountable. &lt;p&gt;It's also quite possible that an editor made a &lt;em&gt;mistake&lt;/em&gt;.  It happens.  Writeups can be 'resurrected' when it does happen.  What does or doesn't get published on E2 is always going to be very, very subjective territory.  The secret is communication:  if you have a question just talk to somebody, preferably [Lord Brawl].&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;/dl&gt;

&lt;dl&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;a name=&quot;avoid&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;big&gt;Q&lt;/big&gt;: How can I avoid Klaproth?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dd&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;big&gt;A&lt;/big&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: There are several means to avoid conflict with Klaproth. First and foremost - take the time to write cohesive and complete writeups, use proper linking and pay attention to formatting. When it comes to content, avoid being rude or obnoxious to people or particular users. Writing &quot;[getting to know you]&quot; ([GTKY]) writeups can result in a visit by Klaproth. Before hitting that submit button, ask yourself if this is a [node for the ages]. Think whether you would be interested in the writeup if someone else wrote it last year. If the answer is no, rewrite it. This is not to say that you should only node factual data. Adding fiction, observation and wit can be a good thing if it is timeless. The only problem is that it tends to be subjective, and there is always the possibility it may be deleted later. Subjective writeups stay for a subjective time period. &lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;/dl&gt;

&lt;dl&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;a name=&quot;helpmywus&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;big&gt;Q&lt;/big&gt;: What other suggestions can I get to improve my writeups?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dd&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;big&gt;A&lt;/big&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: Spend a little time at [Everything University]. Yes, it is a lot of information, but you'll be better off if you read it a bit at a time. You can always sign up for a [E2 Mentoring Sign-Up|mentor] to assist you. Ask a [Content Editor] or [gods|administrator] for their opinion, it's part of their job description. You can also ask some of the users hanging out in the chatterbox, most of the time you'll get some good advice. Find a high-level noder whose work you particularly enjoy, then read everything you can. Do not try to &quot;copy&quot; their style, try to incorporate the good points into your unique style. For new users, reading &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; fundamental.&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;/dl&gt;

&lt;dl&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;a name=&quot;olddays&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;big&gt;Q&lt;/big&gt;: What was it like in the olden days?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dd&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;big&gt;A&lt;/big&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: Before [Klaproth], you wouldn't know a node was deleted unless you used a [node tracker]. If you looked for your deceased node, you wouldn't be able to locate it unless you visited Node Heaven or went through a bunch of Editor Logs. This usually resulted in complaints in the chatterbox, which would attract downvoters. This vicious cycle just made the user angrier and angrier. Now, using [modern science], E2 can keep you informed through Klaproth. &lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;/dl&gt;

&lt;dl&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;a name=&quot;whyexist&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;big&gt;Q&lt;/big&gt;: Why did the establishment hire Klaproth?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dd&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;big&gt;A&lt;/big&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: Everything 2 is slowly changing for the better. One of the common complaints heard in the chatterbox concerned deleted nodes. People were asking for someone like [Cool Man Eddie] to notify them should one of their writeups get axed. E2 has a host of selfless volunteers that worked on this feature, and Klaproth is the result. Users who don't like Klaproth can turn off the notification, while those who appreciate the notification can bask in the death of their expired writeups. Some folks ask for more capabilities, such as blind messaging to the editor who nuked the writeup. That may be a future feature, should the programmers have the time to create it. If you have a suggestion, email it to [dem bones], his address is on his homenode. If you know how to program [Perl], join the [edev] usergroup and try your hand at improving E2. For now, Klaproth is the method of notification for deleted nodes.&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;/dl&gt;

&lt;dl&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;a name=&quot;nameorigin&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;big&gt;Q&lt;/big&gt;: Where did Klaproth's name come from?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dd&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;big&gt;A&lt;/big&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: [Martin Heinrich Klaproth] (&lt;a href=[% urlGen({'node'=&gt;'Klaproth','type'=&gt;'user'}); %]&gt;picture&lt;/a&gt;) was an early German chemist. He learned chemistry while working as an apothecary's assistant, later performing that job in cities like Hannover, Berlin, and Gda&#241;sk. He was hired by the University of Berlin when it was originally founded in 1810. Klaproth was their first professor of chemistry, a position he held until his death. Klaproth was considered the father of analytical chemistry. Some of his discoveries included uranium, zirconium, chromium, and cerium. His specialty was devising quantitative methods of mineral analysis, which was used extensively in chemical analysis in the field of archaeology. Of course, he had nothing to do with why we selected 'Klaproth' as our director of death around here: Klaproth is a [Neil Gaiman] character from the [Sandman] series. He's the Master of Funerary Rites in [Necropolis].&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;/dl&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;border: solid black 1px; margin-left: 50px; margin-right: 50px; margin-top: 100px; padding: 10px;&quot;&gt;&lt;small&gt;Have another question? Send [% linkNode(getNode('N-Wing','user')); %] a &lt;code&gt;/msg&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;Thanks a lot to [Rancid_Pickle], who added a whole bunch of more detail, along with entire questions (and answers).&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot; style=&quot;border: solid black 2px; padding: 10px; margin: 5px;&quot;&gt;
related topic:&lt;br /&gt;
[Everything FAQ]
&lt;/p&gt;</doctext>
  <core>0</core>
  <reputation>0</reputation>
  <lockedby_user>0</lockedby_user>
  <createtime>2001-06-13 07:05:31</createtime>
  <locktime>0000-00-00 00:00:00</locktime>
  <totalvotes>0</totalvotes>
  <hits>0</hits>
  <node_id>1079637</node_id>
  <edittime>0000-00-00 00:00:00</edittime>
  <type_nodetype>14</type_nodetype>
  <document_id>1079637</document_id>
  <author_user>9740</author_user>
  <package>0</package>
  <title>Archived E2 FAQ: Klaproth</title>
</node>
