<node>
  <type_nodetype>14</type_nodetype>
  <doctext>&lt;P&gt;This will be short but sweet.

&lt;P&gt;&lt;B&gt;Q: Why does E2 have polls?&lt;/b&gt;

&lt;P&gt;A: The short answer: polls are a quick and easy way to get user feedback on all things everything2. 

&lt;P&gt;&lt;B&gt;Q: And the long answer?&lt;/b&gt;

&lt;P&gt;A: Questions about demographics, policy decisions, new features, concerns, your usage of everything2, and many other aspects of the website will be addressed through the polls. Many polls will be created and selected by the admins themselves, to get users' perspectives on changes being made around E2. In addition, users can also create polls.

&lt;P&gt;&lt;B&gt;Q: Who can create polls?&lt;/b&gt;

&lt;P&gt;A: Any user who is [The Power Structure of Everything2|Level 3] or higher can create a poll. You do not receive any XP for creating a poll, nor for votes on that poll.

&lt;P&gt;&lt;B&gt;Q: How can I create a poll?&lt;/b&gt;

&lt;P&gt;A: Simple. Simply go to &lt;b&gt;[Everything Poll Creator]&lt;/b&gt; and follow the simplified instructions.

&lt;P&gt;&lt;B&gt;Q: What happens when a poll is created?&lt;/b&gt;

&lt;P&gt;A: The poll goes into a queue with all other created polls. (The full queue of polls can be viewed at &lt;b&gt;[Everything Poll Directory]&lt;/b&gt;.) Gods then review all of these polls, and they decide whether to delete them, edit them, or make them the Current User Poll. [anthropod] is the god currently in charge of polls.

&lt;P&gt;&lt;B&gt;Q: Hey! My poll is up there, but it's been changed a bit.&lt;/b&gt;

&lt;P&gt;A: First, that's not a question. Second, a number of submitted polls have good ideas, but contain typos, poor wording, or confusing choices; these can be edited before publishing. If you have any concerns or questions about a poll you've created, please contact [anthropod].

&lt;P&gt;&lt;B&gt;Q: How can I vote on a poll?&lt;/b&gt;

&lt;P&gt;A: Voting on a poll is just like voting on a writeup. That is, you must have a vote left to vote on the poll, and you have a 1/5 chance of receiving 1 XP for voting on a poll.

&lt;P&gt;There are two ways of voting on the current user poll.

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;First, you can activate the [Current User Poll] nodelet at &lt;b&gt;[Nodelet Settings]&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alternatively, you can visit the standalone superdoc [Everything User Poll].&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;P&gt;&lt;B&gt;Q: What happens when a poll is no longer the User Poll?&lt;/b&gt;

&lt;P&gt;A: That poll is no longer votable, but can be viewed, along with other past poll results, at [Everything Poll Archive].


[%

return unless $APP-&gt;isAdmin($USER);

my $str=&quot;&lt;P&gt;&lt;hr width=220&gt;

&lt;P&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Info for Gods&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;P&gt;&lt;b&gt;Q: Where can I view submitted polls?&lt;/b&gt;

&lt;P&gt;A: At [Everything Poll Directory]. There you will see each poll, along with a link to the poll itself, the poll's author, and options to make that poll the current poll or to delete the poll. (Note that [anthropod] is the poll god at the moment and would prefer you left the posting of polls up to her. Feel free to discuss anything relevant with her.)

&lt;P&gt;&lt;B&gt;Q: A poll seems good, but has typos|poor formatting|incomplete or erroneous choices. How can I edit it?&lt;/b&gt;

&lt;P&gt;A: First, go to the poll itself by clicking on its title at [Everything Poll Directory]. From there, click the \&quot;edit\&quot; link in your [Administrative Stuff] nodelet.

&lt;P&gt;At first this may seem cryptic if you don't know Perl, but this is fairly simple. Here is a sample of what you might see at the page:&quot;;


$str.='
&lt;P&gt;
&lt;code&gt;
my $question=&quot;&amp;lt;p&gt;What is your favorite type of E2 writeup?&amp;lt;/p&gt;&quot;;&lt;br&gt;
my %options=(0 =&gt; &quot;Historical factual&quot;, 1 =&gt; &quot;Pop culture factual&quot;, 2 =&gt; &quot;Biographical&quot;, 3 =&gt; &quot;Original fiction&quot;, 4 =&gt; &quot;Original nonfiction&quot;, 5 =&gt; &quot;Original poetry&quot;, 6 =&gt; &quot;CST-approved copyrighted content&quot;);&lt;br&gt;
$HTMLVARS{options}={0 =&gt; &quot;Historical factual&quot;, 1 =&gt; &quot;Pop culture factual&quot;, 2 =&gt; &quot;Biographical&quot;, 3 =&gt; &quot;Original fiction&quot;, 4 =&gt; &quot;Original nonfiction&quot;, 5 =&gt; &quot;Original poetry&quot;, 6 =&gt; &quot;CST-approved copyrighted content&quot;};
&lt;/code&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To change the question, alter the text in quotes after &lt;i&gt;my $question=&lt;/i&gt;.
&lt;li&gt;Options are a little trickier. Notice that the options list appears twice. Each list consists of a series of entries, beginning with entry &lt;i&gt;0&lt;/i&gt;.

&lt;blockquote&gt;0 =&gt; &quot;Historical factual&quot;, 1 =&gt; &quot;Pop culture factual&quot;, etc ...&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;li&gt;The options list cannot go above &lt;i&gt;12&lt;/i&gt;. Entries above twelve will appear at the poll, but votes for those options will not be counted by the voting mechanism.
&lt;li&gt;To add an option, simply find the highest-numbered option, add 1, and add an entry to the end of &lt;i&gt;both&lt;/i&gt; option lists, separated by a comma.
&lt;li&gt;To alter an existing option, change the text in &lt;i&gt;both&lt;/i&gt; entries.
&lt;li&gt;If your changes to the question or options include a double quote (&quot;) or a dollar sign ($) you must place a forward slash (\) before them, or things get messed up. For example, 

&lt;blockquote&gt;0 =&gt; &quot;Historical \&quot;factual\&quot;&quot;&lt;/blockquote&gt;

Would appear as &lt;i&gt;Historical &quot;factual&quot;&lt;/i&gt; in the poll itself.';

return $str;

%]</doctext>
  <node_id>1690970</node_id>
  <title>Archived E2 FAQ: Polls</title>
</node>
