<node>
  <doctext>   &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
   &lt;p align=center&gt;
   [%
   my @wit = (
   &quot;One [artist] I read about recently dismembered baby dolls, sprayed them with paints and hung them up on the wall in disfigured poses.&lt;br&gt;
   You know, that would convey a message to someone of a [pessimistic], angst-ridden mindset.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
   --&lt;em&gt;[Thomas Kinkade], [Painter of Light]&#174;&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
  
   &quot;Why do people keep insisting that I join the [21st Century]? &lt;br&gt;
  I *&lt;strong&gt;live&lt;/strong&gt;* in the 21st Century! I just don't want to be bothered by the [shitheads] on the Internet!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
  --&lt;em&gt;[Harlan Ellison]&lt;em&gt;&quot;,
  
  &quot;What's all this business about being a [writer]?, 
  It's just putting one word after another.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
  --&lt;em&gt;[Irving Thalberg]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
  
  &quot;I know you believe you understand what you think I said, but I am not sure you realise that what you heard is not what I meant.&lt;br&gt;
  --&lt;em&gt;[Alan Greenspan]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
  
  &quot;Airing one's [dirty linen] never makes for a masterpiece.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
  --&lt;em&gt;[Fran&#231;ois Truffaut]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
  
  &quot;I hate [Submissions for the Everything Quote Server | quotations]. Tell me what you know.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
  -- &lt;em&gt;[Ralph Waldo Emerson], May 1849&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
  
  &quot;I had the song '[Fish Heads]' stuck in my head in 1985. [All] of 1985.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
  --&lt;em&gt;[jwz]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
  
  &quot;[Passers-by were amazed by the unusually large amounts of blood].&quot;,
  
  &quot;[Don't node nude!]&quot;,
  
  &quot;The most [merciful] thing in the world, I think, is the inability of the human mind to correlate all its contents.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
  --&lt;em&gt;[H.P. Lovecraft]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
  
  &quot;Famous remarks are very [seldom] quoted correctly. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
  --&lt;em&gt;[Simeon Strunsky]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
  
  &quot;I love deadlines. I love the [whooshing] sound they make as they fly by. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
  -- &lt;em&gt;[Douglas Adams]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
  
  &quot;You don't pray in my school and I won't think in your church. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
  -- &lt;em&gt;A bumper sticker seen on the back of a [Toyota]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
  
  &quot;Of the four wars in my lifetime, none came about because the U.S. was too strong.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
  -- &lt;em&gt;[Ronald Reagan]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
  
  &quot;Find your own [trajectory] and stick to it. Find kindred spirits. Follow your bliss.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
  -- &lt;em&gt;[Joseph Campbell]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
  
  &quot;Truth is strong because it is true...Truth is justice because it is true...&lt;br&gt;
  Don't you think it is very persuasive?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
  --&lt;em&gt;[Taro], [Serial Experiments Lain], Layer 09:Protocol&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
  
  &quot;Why does man [kill]? Man kills for food. But not only for food - frequently a beverage is also required.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
  -- &lt;em&gt;[Woody Allen]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
  
  &quot;Despite my [ghoulish] reputation, I really have the heart of a small boy. I keep it in a [jar] on my desk.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
  -- &lt;em&gt;[Robert Bloch]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
  
  &quot;Of course you're mad. If you weren't mad, you wouldn't be here.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
  -- &lt;em&gt;the [Mad Hatter] to Alice (from [Lewis Carroll | Lewis Carroll's] [Alice in Wonderland])&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
  
  &quot;No, we won't think noble because we're not noble. We won't live in [beautiful harmony] because there's no such thing in this world, nor should there be. We promise only to do our best and live out our lives. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dear [God] that's all we can promise in [truth].  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
  -- &lt;em&gt;[Lillian Hellman]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
  
  &quot;[Sarcastic]? You mean [malicious]. Yes, I am a little malicious. I only fear that my malice is to be wasted on such miserable objects.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
  -- &lt;em&gt;Thomas Mann&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,

  &quot;Always read stuff that will make you look good if you die in the middle of it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
  -- &lt;em&gt;P. J. O'Rourke&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,

  &quot;as yes is to if, [love] is to yes&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
  -- &lt;em&gt;spud\@nothingness.net&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
  
  &quot;[Madness] is something rare in individuals - but in groups, parties, peoples, ages it is the rule.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
  -- &lt;em&gt;[Friedrich Nietzsche], [Beyond Good and Evil]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;, 
  
  &quot;I don't remember what the point was, but actually {[Bill Gates]} conceded that I was right and then just moved on, which I found extremely scary that he would consider something, consider his own position, consider this alternative view, weigh the merits of each argument, and then adopt the best view. And it was irrelevant whether the best view was his or someone else's.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
  -- &lt;em&gt;[Larry Ellison] &lt;/em&gt;&quot;,

  &quot;A [diplomat] is a man who says you have an open mind, instead of telling you that you have a hole in the head.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
  -- &lt;em&gt;Unknown&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
  
  &quot;I once knew a rotund lesbian [Luxembourg | Luxembourger] who enjoyed making laborious dot-matrix style pictures of [Seven of Nine] with a felt tip pen.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
  --&lt;em&gt;[The Alchemist]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
  
  &quot;I just wrote a [node] with links in it. [hard link | Those brackets are great]. Really easy to do stuff.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
  -- &lt;em&gt;ThePress&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
  
  &quot;For some reason, I felt I was hard pressed to find much that was Mexican in [Mexico].&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
  --&lt;em&gt;[Valhalla]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,

  &quot;We can't afford to be [innocent].&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
  --&lt;em&gt;[Girlface]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
  
  &quot;[Globalisation] is an American ideology. It stands for expansion on our terms, and for free trade [as long as it serves us].&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
  -- &lt;em&gt;[Chalmers Johnson], Manager of the [Japan Policy Reseach Institute].&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
  
  &quot;[Oh my God]! Space aliens! Don't eat me, I have a wife and kids! Eat them. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
  -- &lt;em&gt;[Homer Simpson] - [The Treehouse of Horror]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
  
  &quot;To model our political system upon speculations of lasting [tranquillity], is to calculate on the weaker springs of the human character.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
  -- &lt;em&gt;[Alexander Hamilton]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
  
 &quot;Restriction of free thought and [free speech] is the most dangerous of all subversions. It is the one un-American act that could most easily defeat us.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[William O. Douglas]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;Nothing is illegal if one hundred businessmen decide to do it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Andrew Young]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;Get crazy with the [Cheez Whiz],&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Beck] - '[Where It's At]'&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;Question with [boldness] even the existence of a God; because, if there be one, he must more approve of the homage of reason, than that of blind-folded fear.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Thomas Jefferson]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;Every word is like an unnecessary stain on [silence] and [nothingness].&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Samuel Beckett]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;Happiness isn't something you experience; it's something you remember.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Oscar Levant]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;A man can make up for his intelligence with his effort, but a man cannot make up for his effort with his intelligence. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Joseph Garvin]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;He hoped and prayed that there wasn't an [afterlife]. Then he realised there was a contradiction involved here and merely hoped that there wasn't an afterlife.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Douglas Adams]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;Take me [drunk], I'm home again!&quot;,

 &quot;Every time you manage to close the door on [Reality], it comes in through the window. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Unknown]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;Care about other people. Not what they think.&quot;, 
 
 &quot;Those who say it cannot be done... are often passed by those doing it.
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Unknown]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;One treats others with [courtesy] not because they are gentlemen or gentlewomen, but because you are.
 -- &lt;em&gt;G. Henrichs&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;Faith is Belief without evidence in what is told by one who speaks without [knowledge], of things without [parallel].
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Ambrose Bierce]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;A sharp [axe] is easier to wield than a sharp [wit].&quot;,

 &quot;[Fuck the system]? Nah, you might catch something.&quot;,
 
 &quot;Shell to [DOS]... Come in DOS, do you copy? Shell to DOS...&quot;,
 
 &quot;Man who go to bed with itchy butt, wake with smelly finger&quot;,
 
 &quot;From every tree in the garden did he grant them to eat, save but one. And that tree, in the centre of the garden, was called the tree of life. And the [Satan | Snake] said to Eve, 'Eat of this fruit and you will become as God.'&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Genesis 3 | Book of Genesis, Chapter 3, Verse 4]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;As memory may be a [paradise] from which we cannot be driven, it may also be a hell from which we cannot escape.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[John Lancaster Spalding]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;Stupidity is present among the most [intelligent] of man.&quot;,
 
 &quot;A list is only as strong as its [You are the Weakest Link, Goodbye | are the weakest link].&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;Don Knuth&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;I cannot believe that [God] plays dice with the [cosmos].&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;Albert Einstein, on the randomness of [quantum mechanics]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;Christmas is a time when kids tell Santa what they want and adults pay for it. Deficits are when adults tell the government what they want-and their kids pay for it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Richard Lamm]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;There is an exception to every rule, except the rule of exceptions.&quot;,
 
 &quot;The surest way to corrupt a youth is to instruct him to hold in higher esteem those who think alike than those who think differently.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- [Fredrich Nietzsche]&quot;,
 
 &quot;What the hell, It's only [XP | Karma].&quot;,
 
 &quot;+fhjmnoptxB&quot;, 
 
 &quot;I saw him earlier - he was in the [bathroom] getting a drink of water - and the seat fell and hit him on the head.&quot;,
 
 &quot;[EDB | Death] rides a swift horse.&quot;,
 
 &quot;Why am I better than you, you ask? If you need to think about that, there you are.&quot;,
 
 &quot;heh if the fbi ever rings me im going to keep them talking for as long as possible, i have to get someone back for the cost of all these parking tickets.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;'trapper', [#cyberarmy] [DALNet]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;any hot ladies want to chat with an ultimate [pokemon] trainer?&quot;,
 
 &quot;[History Repeating | History will always be repeated] because there are only a [finite] number of possible actions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Nanosecond]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;Eternal vigilance is the price of liberty.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Thomas Jefferson]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;Let us make sure of the facts before being concerned with the cause.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;Fontenelle&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;You can tell a lot about a fellow's character by his way of eating [jelly beans].&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Ronald Reagan]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;I want to know God's thoughts....the rest, are details.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Albert Einstein]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;Don't run from [sniper | snipers], you'll just die tired.&quot;,
 
 &quot;Whoever decided to call it necking was a poor judge of [anatomy].&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; 
 -- &lt;em&gt;Groucho Marx&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;We are born naked, wet, and hungry. Then things get worse.&quot;,
 
&quot;There is nothing more uncommon than [common sense].&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Frank Lloyd Wright]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;A great many people will think they're thinking when they are merely rearranging their prejudices.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[William James]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;Common sense is the collection of prejudices acquired by age eighteen.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Albert Einstein]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;I am free of all prejudices. I hate everyone equally. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[W.C. Fields]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;, 
 
 &quot;[Fashion] is a form of ugliness so intolerable that we have to alter it every six months.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Oscar Wilde]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;The [optimist] sees opportunity in every danger; the [pessimist] sees danger in every opportunity.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Winston Churchill]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;Why do grandparents and grandchildren get along so well? They have the same enemy-- the [mother].&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Claudette Colbert]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;Whenever you have an efficient government you have a [dictatorship].&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Harry S. Truman]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;There's no fool like an old fool -- you can't beat [XP | experience].&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Jacob Braude]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;There is nothing so annoying as to have two people talking when you're busy interrupting.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Mark Twain]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;[Editor | Power] corrupts. [Gods | Absolute power] corrupts absolutely.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Rosabeth Moss Kantor]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;[Imagination] is more important than knowledge.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Albert Einstein]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;, 
 
 &quot;[Imagination] rules the world.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; 
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Napoleon]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;There's a [sucker] born every minute.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; 
 -- &lt;em&gt;[PT Barnum]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;The whole is equal to the sum of its parts.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Euclid]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;[Consistency] only comes in death.&quot;,
 
 &quot;They that can give up essential [liberty] to obtain a little temporary [safety] deserve neither liberty nor safety.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Benjamin Franklin]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;grrrrr....&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[EDB]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;You know, the condom is the [Cinderella | glass slipper] of our generation. You slip it on when you meet a stranger. You dance all night, then you throw it away. The [condom], I mean. Not the stranger.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Marla Singer] - [Fight Club]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;Our generation has had no [Great Depression], no [First World War | Great War]. Our war is a spiritual war. Our depression is our lives.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Tyler Durden] - [Fight Club]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;You are not your [job].&lt;br&gt;
 You are not the money in your [bank account].&lt;br&gt;
 You are not the [car] you drive.&lt;br&gt;
 You are not how much money is in your [wallet].&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 [You are the all-singing, all-dancing crap of the world].&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Tyler Durden] - [Fight Club]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;Yes, there is no benefit of having [copper] at .25um, but that's not the point. The point is would you rather go to copper when you can, or when you have to?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[chic_hearne]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;You wanna know something funnier? [Rambus] are made up of a bunch of old [AMD] guys that left back in the mid-late 80's. Hehe ... Talk about stealth...&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Michael Lim], alluding to Rambus's hand in the weakening of [Intel] Corp. in the year 2000&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;It was because he wanted there to be [conspirator | conspirators]. It was much better to imagine men in some smoky room somewhere, made mad and cynical by privilege and power, plotting over the [Courvoisier | brandy]. You had to cling to this sort of image, because if you didn't then you might have to face the fact that bad things happened because ordinary people, the kind who brushed the dog and told their children [bedtime stories], were capable of then going out and doing horrible things to other ordinary people. It was much easier to blame it on Them. It was bleakly depressing to think that They were Us. If it was Them, then nothing was anyone's fault. If is was Us, what did that make Me? After all, I'm one of Us. I must be. I've certainly never thought of myself as one of Them. No one ever thinks of themselves as one of Them. We're always one of Us. It's Them that do the bad things&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 --&lt;em&gt;[Terry Pratchett]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;Sort of like the old joke about the woman who was trying to get [pregnant] after having been married for two years. She goes to the [doctor] who says 'but you're still a [virgin]' and she says 'Well, I'm married to an [Intel] salesman and he just sits on the edge of the bed and tells me how great it is going to be&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[idiot]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;[Mustang | Mustangs] and [Thunderbirds] and [Spitfire | Spitfires] - Oh MY!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
  --&lt;em&gt;[tejek]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;Oh that bug, that is no bug, that is a creature I mean feature, a new evolutionary [CPU] from [Intel], it creates different answers for you to rely on and those companies that survive will be stronger&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
  -- &lt;em&gt;[Bill Jackson ]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;[WTF] ... while spec is evaded as 'not important for [itanium]' ... what does [intel] think our cluster is going to do, [mp3] decoding?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 --&lt;em&gt;[Tim Wilkens] &lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;I would have loved to be a fly on the wall this morning to hear the first words out of [Jerry Sanders]' mouth when he heard of the 1.13GHz [Pentium III] recall. For that matter, I would have loved to hear the conversation when Micky D. called Barrett this morning. I would have loved to see the look on Barrett's face when his secretary said, 'Craig, Michael's on the phone and he  sounds [a little pissed].'&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
  -- &lt;em&gt;[Pravin Kamdar] &lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;I'll connect the dots for youcheap [MHz] + dumb public = [profit]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Paul DeMone]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,  
 
 &quot;Michael Dell has built a large company...now he wants to build a small company from it&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;  
  -- &lt;em&gt;[Bill Jackson], on [Dell]'s single sourcing and public bashing of [AMD] products&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;Our strategy is high performance at fair prices. Our competitor's is fair performance at high prices&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
  -- &lt;em&gt;[Jerry Sanders]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;, 
 
 &quot;Only a fool would bet against you. After all, it's not [RAMBUS] or [Willy] it's the benchmarks....! Reminds me of [Star Trek] [OS] episode (later in a movie) about the '[Kobiashi Maru]'...the no win situation...what do you do? You change the rules! [Intel] will change the benchmarks! Bet on it...&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; 
  -- &lt;em&gt;[Jim McMannis]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;In the Kingdom of the [MHz], the man with one [GHz] is king.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
  -- &lt;em&gt;JC&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;There are lies, damn lies, and then what the [PR] guy says.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Drew Prairie]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;Wafer [frisbee], That is a good way to lose your head.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Bill Jackson]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;...a [Gateway] Select commercial came on. In the commercial they were talking about the superior [AMD Athlon] processor. Then at the end they showed the Gateway screen with the AMD logo where the [Intel] logo usually is. My wife turns to me a goes 'where was the [Intel Pentium III music | dint din ding]?'&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; 
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Kwas]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;It looks like they tried the 'Get 9 women, I want that baby in a month' approach
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Bill Jackson], on the [Coppermine] chipset&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;It's not just the arrival of chips which match -- or out-perform -- the [Pentium III]; and it's not just the total unavailability of Pentium III gigahertz processors, and it's not just the continuing farce of [Rambus]; what's now in question is the very basis of [Intel] technology. Because logically, what [AMD] is doing shouldn't be possible&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;Kewney&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;[Intel] has done the impossible! [Dual-boot] with one [OS]!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;             
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Steve Harris], on the [Coppermine bug]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;We hold these truths to be self-evident, that all men people are created equal&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 --  &lt;em&gt;[Thomas Jefferson]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;I think I must be a [mushroom] because they keep me in the dark and feed me [bullshit].&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 --  &lt;em&gt;[Unknown]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;Truth has many faces&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 --&lt;em&gt;[Morgaine], [The Mists if Avalon] by [Marion Zimmer Bradley]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;Two roads diverged in a wood and I- I took the one less travelled by&lt;br&gt;
 And that has made all the difference. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Robert Frost], [The Road not Taken]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;Whatever you do, you'll regret it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Allan McCleod Gray]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;I don't suffer from [insanity] I enjoy every minute of it.&quot;,
 
 &quot;[Sanity] is a playground for the unimaginative.&quot;, 
 
 &quot;I'm not [weird], I think in new ways&quot;,
 
 &quot;It's useless for [sheep] to pass resolutions in favour of vegetarianism when [wolf | wolves] remain of a different opinion.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[William Ralph Inge]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;Dear [Lord], give me [chastity] and self-restraint. . . but not yet, Oh Lord, not yet!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; 
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Saint Augustine]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;The [truth] is the one thing that nobody will believe.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[George Bernard Shaw]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;[Violence] never settles anything.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;Genghis Khan&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;The mice voted to bell the cat.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; 
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Aesop]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;[Democracy] can withstand anything but democrats.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; 
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Robert Heinlein]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;[PMS | Pre-menstrual Syndrome] - Just before their periods women behave the way men do all the time.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Robert Heinlein]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;Women are meant to be loved, not understood.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Oscar Wilde]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
   
 &quot;Rascality has limits; [stupidity] has not.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 --  &lt;em&gt;[Napoleon Bonaparte] &lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
   
 &quot;The [optimist] proclaims that we live in the best of all possible worlds; the [pessimist] fears this is true.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
  -- &lt;em&gt;[James Branch Cabell]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;Obvious is the most dangerous word in mathematics.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Eric Bell]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;Minds are like parachutes; they only function when they are open. 
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Sir James Dewar]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;Don't go around saying the world owes you a [living]; the world owes you [nothing]; it was here first.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Mark Twain]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;The man who never makes a mistake always takes orders from one who does.&quot;,
 
 &quot;If a [million] people say a foolish thing, it is still a [foolish] thing.
  -- &lt;em&gt;[Anatole France]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;Too bad all the people who know how to run this country are busy running [taxi | taxicabs] or [hairdresser | cutting hair]. 
 - &lt;em&gt;[George Burns]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;The only [fool] bigger than the person who knows it all is the person who argues with him.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Stanislaw Jerszy Lec]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;I will not [condemn] you for what you did yesterday, if you do it right today.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 --&lt;em&gt;[Sheldon S. Maye]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;We know what a person thinks not when he tells us what he thinks, but by his actions. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Isaac Bashevis Singer]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;Those are my [principles]. If you don't like them I have others.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Groucho Marx]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;A [classic] is a book which people praise and don't read.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
  -- &lt;em&gt;[Mark Twain]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;A jury consists of twelve people who determine which client has the better [lawyer].&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Robert Frost]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;Of those who say [nothing], few are silent.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Thomas Neill]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;[Wise] men talk because they have something to say; [fools], because they have to say something.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Plato]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;Those who cannot remember the [past] are condemned to repeat it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[George Santayana]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;There are three types of people in this world. Those who can count, and those who can't. 
 - &lt;em&gt;Seen on a [bumper sticker]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;[History] is the version of past events that people have decided to agree upon.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Napoleon Bonaparte]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;I can't understand why people are frightened by new ideas. I'm frightened of old ones. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[John Cage]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;[Imagination] is the one weapon in the war against reality.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Jules de Gaultier]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;The important thing is never to stop questioning.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Albert Einstein]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;If you want to make enemies, try to change something.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Woodrow Wilson]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;You must believe in free will; there is no choice.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Isaac Bashevis Singer]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;I haven't failed, I've found 10,000 ways that don't work.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Albert Einstein]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;Why does the [USAF | Air Force] need expensive new bombers? Have the people we've been bombing over the years been complaining?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[George Wallace]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;A [cynic] is a man who knows the price of everything, and the value of nothing. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Oscar Wilde]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;Don't say you don't have enough time. You have exactly the same number of hours per day that were given to [Helen Keller], [Pasteur], [Michaelangelo], [Mother Teresa], [Leonardo da Vinci], [Thomas Jefferson], and [Albert Einstein].&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[H. Jackson Brown]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;It's kind of fun to do the impossible.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; 
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Walt Disney]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;It has to start somewhere. It has to start sometime. 
 What better place than here? What better time than now?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Rage Against the Machine], [Guerilla Radio], [The Battle of Los Angeles]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
  &quot;[Dog eat Dog], every day&lt;br&gt;
  On our fellow men we pray&lt;br&gt;
  Dog eat Dog, to get by&lt;br&gt;
  Hope you like my [genocide].&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
  -- &lt;em&gt;[The Offspring], [Genocide], [Smash]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,  
 
 &quot;[Life] is a lesson, you learn it when you're through.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; 
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Limp Bizkit], [Take a Look Around]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;Who is the greater [fool]?  &lt;br&gt;
 The fool or the fool that follows him?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Obi-Wan Kenobi], [Star Wars | Star Wars: A New Hope]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;[Do or do not], There is no try.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Yoda], [The Empire Strikes Back | Star Wars The Empire Strikes Back]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;'[Houston], we have a problem.'&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Jim Lovell], on board [Apollo 13]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;There is no [king] who has not had a slave among his ancestors, and no [slave] who has not had a king among his.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Helen Keller]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;There is nothing like returning to a place that remains unchanged to find the ways in which you yourself have altered.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Nelson Mandela]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;There is nothing that can be said by [mathematical] symbols and relations which cannot also be said by words. The converse, however, is false. Much that can be and is said by words cannot successfully be put into equations, because it is [nonsense].&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[C. Truesdell]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;There was never a [genius] without a [tincture] of [madness]. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Aristotle]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;There's a difference between [beauty] and [charm]. A beautiful woman is one I notice. A charming woman is one who notices me.&lt;br&gt;&lt;Br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[John Erskine]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;There's a fine line between [genius] and [insanity]. I have erased this line. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Oscar Levant]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;There's many a best-seller that could have been prevented by a good teacher.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Flannery O'Connor]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;Those parts of the system that you can hit with a [hammer] (not advised) are called [hardware]; those program instructions that you can only curse at are called [software].&quot;,
 
 &quot;This [book] fills a much-needed gap. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Moses Hadas]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;Weaselling out of things is good. It's what separates us from the other animals....except [weasel | weasels].&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Homer Simpson]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;Whenever I dwell for any length of time on my own shortcomings, they gradually begin to seem mild, [harmless], rather engaging little things, not at all like the staring [defect | defects] in other people's characters.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Margaret Halsey]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;Whenever I'm caught between two [evil | evils], I take the one I've never tried.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Mae West]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;Who controls the [past] controls the [future]. Who controls the [present] controls the [past]. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[George Orwell]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;Whenever you find that you are on the side of the [majority], it is time to reform.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Mark Twain]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
  &quot;Whether outwardly or inwardly, whether in [space] or [time], the farther we penetrate the [unknown], the [vaster] and more [marvellous] it becomes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Charles Lindbergh]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
  
  &quot;Whoever controls the [media]...the [image | images]...controls the [culture].&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Allen Ginsberg]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;Whoever undertakes to set himself up as a judge of [Truth] and [Knowledge] is shipwrecked by the laughter of the [God | gods].&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Albert Einstein]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
  
 &quot;Why are [women] so much more interesting to [men] than [men] are to [women]?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Virginia Wolf]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;Don't you try to out-weird me... I get stranger things than you free with my breakfast cereal&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Zaphod Beeblebrox], [The Hitch Hiker's Guide to the Galaxy]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;Time is an [illusion]. Lunchtime doubly so.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; 
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Ford Prefect], [The Hitch Hiker's Guide to the Galaxy]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;One must have an interesting lifestyle if one has occasion to use the plural of '[clitoris]'. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Reverend | Rev.] Tony Bell (Letter to the '[Grauniad | Guardian]')&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;We are all in the [gutter], but some of us are looking at the [stars].&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Oscar Wilde]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;Winning is not [everything]. It's the [only] thing.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Vince Lombardi]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;I often think that the night is more [alive] and more richly coloured than the day.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Vincent Van Gogh]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;If an [American] is hit on the head by a ball at the ballpark, he sues. If a [Japanese] person is hit on the head, he says, 'It's my honour. It's my fault.'&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Koji Yanase], of the [Japanese Federation of Bar Associations], on why there are half as many lawyers in his country as in the [Washington] area.&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;I ask people why they have deer heads on their walls. They say, \&quot;Because it's such a [beautiful] animal.\&quot; There you go! I think my mother is attractive, but I have [photograph|photographs] of her. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Ellen Degeneres]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;I must not [fear]. Fear is the mind-killer. Fear is the [little death] that brings total obliteration. I will face my fear. I will permit it to pass over me and through me. And when it has gone past I will turn the inner eye to see its path. Where the fear has gone there will be nothing. [Only I will remain].&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Frank Herbert], '[Bene Geressit] Litany Against Fear', [Dune]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;The concept of [progress] acts as a mechanism to shield us from the terrors of the [future].&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Frank Herbert], from the [Collected Sayings of Muad`Dib] by [Princess Irulan], [Dune]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;Deep in the human unconscious is a pervasive need for a logical universe that makes sense. But the real universe is always one step beyond logic. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 - &lt;em&gt;[Frank Herbert], from the [Collected Sayings of Muad`Dib] by [Princess Irulan], , [Dune]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;[Touch the puppy] is so seriously [wrong] I have to suggest it.&quot;, 
 
 &quot;If all the [raindrops] were [lemon drops] and [gum drops] oh what a world it would be!&quot;, 
 
 &quot;In the land of the blind, the one eyed man is [king].&quot;,
 
 &quot;When smashing monuments, save the pedestals - they always come in handy.
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Stanislaw Jerszy Lec]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,  
 
 &quot;An intellect does not function on the premise of its own [impotence].&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Ayn Rand]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;Any sufficiently advanced [technology] is indistinguishable from [magic].&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[ Arthur C. Clarke]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;You see things and say, '[Why]?' But I dream things that never were and say, '[Why not]?'.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[George Bernard Shaw]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;If one morning I walked on top of the water across the [Potomac River], the headline that afternoon would read 'PRESIDENT CAN'T SWIM'.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Lyndon B. Johnson]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;A citizen of [America] will cross the ocean to fight for [democracy], but won't cross the street to vote in a national [election].&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; 
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Bill Vaughan]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;Like a [monkey] ready to be shot off into a space. A [space monkey].&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; 
  -- &lt;em&gt;[Tyler Durden], [Fight Club]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;[Fashion] is what you adopt when you don't know who you are.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Quentin Crisp]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;The mind of the [bigot] is like the [pupil] of the eye - the more [light] you pour upon it, the more it will [contract] &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Oliver Wendell Holmes]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;Millions long for [immortality] who do not know what to do with themselves on a rainy Sunday afternoon.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Susan Ertz]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;A [fanatic] is one who can't change his [mind] and won't change the [subject].&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Winston Churchill]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,  

 &quot;I'm desperately trying to figure out why [kamikaze] pilots wore helmets. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Dave Edison]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;, 
 
 &quot;The person who is [master] of their [passion | passions] is [reason | reason's] slave. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 --&lt;em&gt;[Cyril Connelly]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;When the facts change, I change my mind -- what do you do, sir?.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[John Maynard Keynes], upon being questioned by reporters about changing his mind on an issue&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;You're [ugly]. And you're [boring]. And you're totally [ordinary], and you know it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;Em&gt;[American Beauty]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;The highest function of [ecology] is understanding consequences. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Frank Herbert], [Dune]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;I don't believe in [God] because I don't believe in [Mother Goose].&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Clarence Darrow]&lt;/em&gt; &quot;,
 
 &quot;[Monkey]! [Bat]! [Robot Hat]!&quot;,
 
 &quot;[Hail], Emperor, those who will die salute you.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;The [Gladiator | fighters'] greeting to the [Emperor] before gladiatorial games&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;There is no problem that cannot be solved with the proper application of [TNT | high explosives] - Me, amongst others.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 --&lt;em&gt;[Glowin Orb]&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 &quot;[Commercialism] is a poor substitute for [angular momentum].&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 -- &lt;em&gt;[Fruan]'s retort to the statement '[Money makes the world go round  | Money makes the World go 'round].'&lt;/em&gt;&quot;,
 
 
 );
 
 &quot;&lt;font size=3&gt;&quot;.$wit[int(rand(@wit))].&quot;&lt;/font&gt;&quot;
 %]
 &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
</doctext>
  <createtime>2002-02-28 06:40:03</createtime>
  <totalvotes>0</totalvotes>
  <node_id>1261598</node_id>
  <edittime>0000-00-00 00:00:00</edittime>
  <type_nodetype>14</type_nodetype>
  <document_id>1261598</document_id>
  <author_user>459692</author_user>
  <title>Everything Quote Server II</title>
</node>
