<node>
  <doctext>&lt;h3&gt;OVERALL&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;s&gt;Logo needs to be inserted into [e3 container] header.&lt;/s&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;s&gt;Tabs need to be properly styled, including a &quot;selected&quot; class.&lt;/s&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;s&gt;Login form / logout link needs to be styled in [e3 minilogin].&lt;/s&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Search form needs to be rewritten to be simpler.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Search results need to combine full text, node titles, debates, categories, etc. into one relevance-based result set.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We need an intuitive way for a person to enter &quot;Category&quot; mode, whereby they can add a writeup/node to a category.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We need a nodelet that will appear briefly alongside other nodelets when a new notification appears.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When a user receives a message, we need some sort of visual cue in the header.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Everything needs to be tested for guest users, borged users, different level users, admin/non-admins, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;s&gt;Master Control needs to be rewritten to be more efficient (mostly just cut out everything except the Node Notes and the Node Toolset.)&lt;/s&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;HOME&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;s&gt;[Welcome to Everything] needs to be subverted to a simpler frontpage for the [e3 theme].&lt;/s&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The [Cool Staff Picks] nodelet needs to be modeled after the [tfcool nodelet - zen].&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cool Staff Picks needs to be set to auto-update.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;s&gt;&gt;We need a new nodelet to replace [News for Noders].&lt;/s&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The new NFN nodelet needs to auto-update.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There needs to be a notification for changes to the NFN nodelet.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The writeup in Cream of the Cool needs to be set to fade-in/fade-out, instead of just update.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We need an &quot;About Us&quot; section.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;READ&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Further Reading nodelet needs all 6 htmlcodes of &quot;further reading&quot; suggestions built: one for Random Nodes, one for Categories, one for softlinked nodes, one for other writeups by the user, one for recommended nodes based on [Do You C! What I C?], and one for new writeups.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;s&gt;The writeup header needs to be rewritten. It should be static, and contain: author, date submitted, reputation, C! list, a blab box, and links to bookmark and print the writeup.&lt;/s&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The writeup footer also needs to be simplified. Just vote buttons and a link to C! for now.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We need an AdminTools htmlcode that contains links/forms to: forward a node, firmlink a node, lock a node, axe/instakill a node, insure a node, ed-cool a node, clone a node, view XML, edit node, viewcode a node, document a node, delete a node.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We need to integrate the [ShareThis] widget into our writeup header.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;WRITE&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because the read/write portion of our site has been intertwined for so long, this is the tab that probably needs the most work, as well as the most &quot;thoughtful design.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If someone clicks a link underneath an existing e2node/writeup to &quot;Add your writeup to this node&quot;, it takes them here, to a pre-titled scratch pad.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Helpful Hints nodelet ... needs to be helpful.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We should notify certain admins if a user with 0 writeups is on the write tab.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We need to build a custom nodelet that is essentially a &quot;mini-chatterbox.&quot; This can be invoked by an admin on any user's page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We should check if a writeup has been &quot;asamothed&quot; and notify admins.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;CHAT&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Chatterbox needs to be restyled as an AIM-style chat, with more obvious spacing and delineation of each user's message.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We should implement [Gravatars] on the site.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We need to rebuild the Other Users nodelet to be more useful and dynamic.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We need to build a separate nodelet for [Message Inbox] that sits alongside the chatterbox nodelet.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;PROFILE&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Need to integrate Achievements into the site.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We need the ability to add a user to our favorites.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to message user.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;s&gt;Display a user's last 3 writeups.&lt;/s&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Allow in-line editing of a user's doctext and image.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Notifications are needed for when a person updates their doctext or image.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;Profile Feed&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;s&gt;Feed items need to be styled.&lt;/s&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;S&gt;Users need the ability to delete items from their feed.&lt;/s&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Should users be able to comment on other people's feed items a la Facebook?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;s&gt;Notification is needed for when a user adds a feed item.&lt;/s&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We need filters up top for user bookmarks and user cools.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We probably need some pagination of some sort.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;s&gt;We may need to revise [displayUserFeed] into a nodelet.&lt;/s&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;s&gt;We probably need to limit displayUserFeed based on time.&lt;/s&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;User Info&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We need certain &quot;profile&quot; registries to show up here. These need to be editable in-line.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We might want to implement, for example, a Twitter API if a user provides an accountname that displays their last 10 items.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;






</doctext>
  <node_id>1988655</node_id>
  <type_nodetype>14</type_nodetype>
  <title>interface todo list</title>
</node>
