<node>
  <doctext>[%
  return '&lt;p&gt;You must be logged in to be suprised.&lt;/p&gt;' if($APP-&gt;isGuest($USER));
  #my $isHalloween = htmlcode('isSpecialDate','halloween');

  my $isHalloween = 0;
  my $costumeCost = 5;

  my ($str, $resultStr) = (&quot;&quot;,&quot;&quot;);

  my $spinCost = 5;

  if ($isHalloween) {
    $spinCost = 0;
  } else {

    #if ($$USER{GP} &lt; $spinCost) {
    # return &quot;&lt;p&gt;Sorry, you don't have enough GP to spin the wheel.&lt;/p&gt;&quot;;
    #}
    return &quot;&lt;p&gt;Your vow of poverty does not allow you to gamble. You need to [User Settings|opt in to] the GP System in order to spin the wheel.&lt;/p&gt;&quot; if ($$VARS{GPoptout});

    if ($$USER{GP} &lt; $spinCost) {
      #if ($$USER{GP} &lt; -10) {
      return &quot;&lt;p&gt;You approach the Wheel but two large gentlemen with shaved heads and tattoos saying \&quot;MOM\&quot; stop you. One of them twists your head to face the wall while the other points to a sign on said wall that says \&quot;shirt and shoes required\&quot;. You know that they'd let you play naked if you flashed them some GP but then if you had that much GP you wouldn't be barefoot and shirtless, would you now?  As the large gentleman twists your head toward the door, you spot the oversized sign that says &lt;strong&gt;&lt;font color=\&quot;#FF0000\&quot;&gt;Minimum Wager 5 GP&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Come back when you have GP to burn and a shirt on your back.&lt;/p&gt;&quot;;
    }

  }

  if ($query-&gt;param(&quot;spinthewheel&quot;)) {
    $$VARS{spin_wheel} += 1;
    $$USER{GP} += (-1*$spinCost);
    my $rnd = int(rand(10000));
    $resultStr= &quot;&lt;p&gt;The Wheel of Surprise awards you ...&quot;;

    if ($isHalloween) {
	if ($rnd&lt;450) {
                 $resultStr .= &quot; &lt;b&gt;a brick!&lt;/b&gt; You also feel a hand in your pocket as a spooky voice asks if you have a banana. You tell it that [Yes! We have no bananas!|you do not have a banana] and, no, you would not be glad to see the hand's owner, even if it were not pitch dark. The hand creeps back out of your pocket and disappears into the darkness.&quot;;
	}
	elsif ($rnd&lt;500) {
                $resultStr .= &quot; &lt;b&gt;a voodoo doll!&lt;/b&gt; Why, this looks like someone high up in the E2 management. You forget all about tricks and treats, and quickly trot off to raid your mom's sewing cabinet for pins.&quot;;
	}
	elsif ($rnd&lt;1000) {
                $resultStr .= &quot; &lt;b&gt;a bucket full of coal!&lt;/b&gt; Wrong holiday, you think, but you also get a sense that someone is trying to distract you from something. Your wallet feels lighter.&quot;;
	}
	elsif ($rnd&lt;1500) {
                $resultStr .= &quot; &lt;b&gt;an apple with a razor blade.&lt;/b&gt; What a pathetic clich&amp;egrave;! You fling a coin at the wheel and leave in disgust.&quot;;
	}
	elsif ($rnd&lt;2000) {
                $resultStr .= &quot; &lt;b&gt;a coin covered in goo.&lt;/b&gt; A deep voice asks you for abaht tree-fiddy. You fork over 10GP and run.&quot;;
	}
	elsif ($rnd&lt;2500) {
                $resultStr .= &quot; &lt;b&gt;a piece of jalape&amp;ntilde;o-flavoured chewing gum!&lt;/b&gt; &amp;iexcl;Ay ay caliente! Some small change flies out of your pocket as you dip your head into the nearest fountain.&quot;;
	}
	elsif ($rnd&lt;3000) {
                $resultStr .= &quot; &lt;b&gt;a pint of blood wine&lt;/b&gt;! As you lift it to your lips, you hear a voice that sounds like a drunk Norwegian with a bad case of catarrh. You decide to skip the drink and slink off instead.&quot;;
	}
	elsif ($rnd&lt;3500) {
                $resultStr .= &quot; &lt;b&gt;a clammy hand.&lt;/b&gt; You soon discover that the hand is attached to a zombie. The zombie growls \&quot;treeeeeat, treeeeeat!\&quot; and tries to tuck into your arm. You decide that now would be a good time to disappear.&quot;;
	}
	elsif ($rnd&lt;4000) {
                $resultStr .= &quot; &lt;b&gt;a tin-foil hat.&lt;/b&gt; Just what you need to complete your conspiracy theorist costume. What do you mean, that's &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; a costume?&quot;;
	}
	elsif ($rnd&lt;4500) {
#		$resultStr .= &quot;&lt;b&gt;a trick!&lt;/b&gt; Hope you didn't need that GP ...&quot;;
#		$$USER{GP} += -10;
                $resultStr .= &quot; &lt;b&gt;a generic trick!&lt;/b&gt; Something tells you you should try again.&quot;;
	}
        elsif ($rnd&lt;4550) {
                return &quot;ACK! Wheel disabled by Werewolf attack! ([Young Frankenstein|Where wolf? There wolf!])&quot;;
        }
        elsif ($rnd&lt;4700) {
                $$USER{GP} += 10;
                return &quot;You discover a trick that makes the wheel make a horrible chattering noise. After several minutes of making an unholy din a skeleton appears and offers to pay you if you'll just STOP. You're not the sort to refuse money for nothing so that's the way you do it.&quot;;
        }
        elsif ($rnd&lt;4702) {
                $$USER{GP} += 1000;
                return &quot;As the wheel clatters to a halt, you see a little man in green hanging onto it for dear life. You pluck him off and dust him down. He promises you great rewards if you let him go but you find that the legendary pot of gold is really just full of GP. Never trust an E2 leprechaun.&quot;;
        }
        elsif ($rnd&lt;5000) {
                return &quot;ACK! Wheel disabled by Vampire attack!&quot;;
        }
	else {
		$resultStr .= &quot;&lt;b&gt;a treat!&lt;/b&gt; I wonder what it's for ...&quot;;
		if (!exists($$VARS{treats})) {
			$$VARS{treats} = 1;
		}
		else {
			$$VARS{treats} += 1;
		}
                $resultStr .= &quot;&lt;br /&gt;You count the treats in your bag. $$VARS{treats}!&quot;;
                   if ($$VARS{treats} &gt;= $costumeCost) {
                   $resultStr .= &quot;&lt;br /&gt;That's enough to [The Costume Shop|buy a costume]!&quot;;
                   }
                   else {
                   $resultStr .= &quot; That might buy a Richard Nixon mask but you'll have to work some more if you want to dress up properly;&quot;
                   }
	}
}

if (!$isHalloween) {
        $APP-&gt;securityLog($NODE, $USER, &quot;[$$USER{title}] spun the [Wheel of Surprise].&quot;);
	if ($rnd&lt;3800) {
		$resultStr .= &quot;&lt;b&gt;nothing!&lt;/b&gt; Too bad ...&quot;;
	}
	elsif ($rnd&lt;3850) {
		$resultStr .= &quot;&lt;b&gt;a coupon for a free [Butterfinger McFlurry].&lt;/b&gt; Alas, they no longer make them.&quot;;
	}
	elsif ($rnd&lt;3910) {
		$resultStr .= &quot;&lt;b&gt;a porcupine egg!&lt;/b&gt; I wonder what will hatch. Probably nothing.&quot;;
	}
	elsif ($rnd&lt;3915) {
		$resultStr .= &quot;&lt;b&gt;a tin of fair trade caviar!&lt;/b&gt; The perfect gift for the up-and-coming hippie plutocrat!&quot;;
	}
	elsif ($rnd&lt;3930) {
		$resultStr .= &quot;&lt;b&gt;an easter ostrich egg!&lt;/b&gt; This has to be worth three ordinary easter eggs! I wonder what's inside.&quot;;
		if (!exists($$VARS{easter_eggs})) {
			$$VARS{easter_eggs} = 3;
			$$VARS{easter_eggs_bought} = 3;
		}
		else {
			$$VARS{easter_eggs} += 3;
			$$VARS{easter_eggs_bought} += 3;
		}
	}
	elsif ($rnd&lt;3935) {
		$resultStr .= &quot;&lt;b&gt;a Christmas egg!&lt;/b&gt; It's red and green and plays Jingle Bells when you open it. That's about all that it does. Is that not enough!?&quot;;
		if (!exists($$VARS{easter_eggs})) {
			$$VARS{easter_eggs} = 1;
			$$VARS{easter_eggs_bought} = 1;
		}
		else {
			$$VARS{easter_eggs} += 1;
			$$VARS{easter_eggs_bought} += 1;
		}
	}
	elsif ($rnd&lt;3940) {
		$resultStr .= &quot;&lt;b&gt;a passover egg!&lt;/b&gt; I wonder what's inside. Probably a matzo ball.&quot;;
		if (!exists($$VARS{easter_eggs})) {
			$$VARS{easter_eggs} = 1;
			$$VARS{easter_eggs_bought} = 1;
		}
		else {
			$$VARS{easter_eggs} += 1;
			$$VARS{easter_eggs_bought} += 1;
		}
	}
	elsif ($rnd&lt;3950) {
		$resultStr .= &quot;&lt;b&gt;five counterfeit GP!&lt;/b&gt; You pawn them off on some unsuspecting noder in exchange for a shiny new easter egg.&quot;;
		if (!exists($$VARS{easter_eggs})) {
			$$VARS{easter_eggs} = 1;
			$$VARS{easter_eggs_bought} = 1;
		}
		else {
			$$VARS{easter_eggs} += 1;
			$$VARS{easter_eggs_bought} += 1;
		}
	}
	elsif ($rnd&lt;4000) {
		$resultStr .= &quot;&lt;b&gt;an anvil!&lt;/b&gt; At least that's what it feels like when you drop it on your foot. Hmm. Maybe it's a strange form of easter egg.&quot;;
		if (!exists($$VARS{easter_eggs})) {
			$$VARS{easter_eggs} = 1;
			$$VARS{easter_eggs_bought} = 1;
		}
		else {
			$$VARS{easter_eggs} += 1;
			$$VARS{easter_eggs_bought} += 1;
		}
	}
	elsif ($rnd&lt;4950) {
		$resultStr .= &quot;&lt;b&gt;an easter egg!&lt;/b&gt; I wonder what's inside.&quot;;
		if (!exists($$VARS{easter_eggs})) {
			$$VARS{easter_eggs} = 1;
			$$VARS{easter_eggs_bought} = 1;
		}
		else {
			$$VARS{easter_eggs} += 1;
			$$VARS{easter_eggs_bought} += 1;
		}
	}
	elsif ($rnd&lt;4999) {
		$resultStr .= &quot;&lt;b&gt;a C!&lt;/b&gt; Coolness!&quot;;
                $$VARS{cools} ||= 0;
		$$VARS{cools} += 1;
		setVars($USER,$VARS);
	}
	elsif ($rnd==4999) {
		$resultStr .= &quot;&lt;b&gt;5 C!s&lt;/b&gt; Hurry up and spend 'em while you got 'em!&quot;;
                $$VARS{cools} ||= 0;
		$$VARS{cools} += 5;
		setVars($USER,$VARS);
	}
	elsif  ($rnd == 5000) {
		$resultStr .= &quot;&lt;b&gt;500 GP!&lt;/b&gt; Jackpot!&quot;;
		$$USER{GP} += 500;
	}
	elsif ($rnd&lt;5006) {
		$resultStr .= &quot;&lt;b&gt;158 GP!&lt;/b&gt; That's 100 GP adjusted for inflation.&quot;;
		$$USER{GP} += 158;
	}
	elsif ($rnd&lt;5011) {
		$resultStr .= &quot;&lt;b&gt;42 GP!&lt;/b&gt; That's 100 GP after taxes. You get the feeling that it's also the answer to something.&quot;;
		$$USER{GP} += 42;
	}
	elsif ($rnd&lt;5100) {
		$resultStr .= &quot;&lt;b&gt;100 GP!&lt;/b&gt; Sweet!&quot;;
		$$USER{GP} += 100;
	}

	elsif ($rnd&lt;5200) {
		$resultStr .= &quot;&lt;b&gt;a token!&lt;/b&gt; Go spend it at the [e2 gift shop|gift shop]!&quot;;
		if (!exists($$VARS{tokens})) {
			$$VARS{tokens} = 1;
			$$VARS{tokens_bought} += 1;
		}
		else {
			$$VARS{tokens} += 1;
			$$VARS{tokens_bought} += 1;
		}
		setVars($USER,$VARS);
	}
	elsif ($rnd&lt;5220) {
		$resultStr .= &quot;&lt;b&gt;a black token!&lt;/b&gt; Politically correct but there's not a whole lot you can do with it.&quot;;
	}
	elsif ($rnd&lt;5240) {
		$resultStr .= &quot;&lt;b&gt;a New York City subway token!&lt;/b&gt; Free ride! Expires April 13, 2003.&quot;;
	}
	elsif ($rnd&lt;5500) {
		$resultStr .= &quot;&lt;b&gt;25 GP!&lt;/b&gt; Hooray!&quot;;
		$$USER{GP} += 25;
	}
	elsif ($rnd&lt;6500) {
		$resultStr .= &quot;&lt;b&gt;10 GP!&lt;/b&gt; Spin it again!&quot;;
		$$USER{GP} += 10;
	}
	elsif ($rnd&lt;6750) {
		$resultStr .= &quot;&lt;b&gt;5 GP!&lt;/b&gt; You also find one GP that the last player left behind.&quot;;
		$$USER{GP} += 6;
	}
	elsif ($rnd&lt;7000) {
		$resultStr .= &quot;&lt;b&gt;nothing&lt;/b&gt; as it comes to a creaking, chattering, jerky halt. You complain to the manager about the wheel's condition and get your nickel back.&quot;;
		$$USER{GP} += 5;
	}
	elsif ($rnd&lt;9000) {
		$resultStr .= &quot;&lt;b&gt;your [5 GP|nickel] back!&lt;/b&gt; Spin it again!&quot;;
		$$USER{GP} += 5;
	}
	else {
		$resultStr .= &quot;&lt;b&gt;1 GP!&lt;/b&gt; (Wah-wah-wah!)&quot;;
		$$USER{GP} += 1;
	}
$resultStr .= &quot;&lt;/p&gt;&quot;;

htmlcode('achievementsByType','miscellaneous,'.$$USER{user_id});

}

}

if (!$isHalloween) {
$str = '&lt;h3&gt;Welcome, welcome, one and all. Step right up, put your [5 GP|nickel] in the hat and spin the wonderful Wheel of Surprise! Who knows what mysterious wonders will emerge?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;All rights reserved. Must be 18 to play (19 in Quebec and Alabama). Contest open to legal residents of Earth and overseas territories only. Wash cold, tumble dry low. Guarantee void in Tennessee.&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;';
}
else {
$str = '&lt;h3&gt;Welcome, welcome, one and all. Tonight we\'re offering a Trick or Treat Special - and it\'s free to spin, all night long! Who knows what mysterious wonders will emerge?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Guarantee void in Transylvania.&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;';
}




$str.=htmlcode('openform');
$str.=$query-&gt;submit('spinthewheel','spin');
$str.=$query-&gt;end_form;

return $resultStr.$str;

%]


[%
###This makes sure future XP and GP messages in the epicenter will be accurate - mauler

$$VARS{oldexp} = $$USER{experience};
$$VARS{oldGP} = $$USER{GP};

return &quot;&quot;;

%]</doctext>
  <node_id>1874886</node_id>
  <title>Wheel of Surprise</title>
  <type_nodetype>14</type_nodetype>
</node>
