<node>
  <doctext>&lt;h3&gt;Primary Purpose&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Category nodes will serve as the de facto standard for &quot;grouping&quot; related nodes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;Project Goals&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Allow users and usergroups to &quot;own&quot; categories (and thus edit them.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;s&gt;Create a [category] linktype to use to link nodes to category nodes.&lt;/s&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create a category opcode to handle adding/editing/removing category linktypes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create an easy to use interface to add nodes to categories. My own thoughts are to set $$VARS{currentcategory} as needed, then have a link near the &quot;bookmark!&quot; link that says &quot;add to CURRENT CATEGORY&quot;, along with a link &quot;add to ANOTHER CATEGORY&quot;, which will take them to a page listing all the categories they are allowed to edit.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conversely, we'll need to make the node bucket code available to everyone (sanitized, naturally) so they can visit nodes, create a bucket ready for categorizing, and then create / visit the category and place all of their collected nodes within it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;s&gt;We should probably make the Node Bucket its own nodelet.&lt;/s&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We should have a [Random Category] nodelet for the front page, that displays the category name, a snippet of a random node from the random category (a la [Cream of the Cool]), 5-10 links to other nodes within the category, and of course a link to the category node itself.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We should have a couple of different displaytypes for category pages: &lt;b&gt;display&lt;/b&gt; should just give you a list of the links in alphabetical order, while &lt;b&gt;random&lt;/b&gt; should give you a random node, with navigational options to traverse through the rest of the nodes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;Questions&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Are all those &lt;em&gt;username&lt;/em&gt;_root categories going to stay? If so, what is their purpose? &lt;b&gt;kthejoker&lt;/b&gt; - They may or may not stay. I'm leaning towards getting rid of them. Their original purpose (the entire category node's purpose) was to replace the metanode concept. The _root category nodes were going to contain other category nodes, such as &quot;user bookmarks&quot;, &quot;user writeups&quot;, etc etc to kind of provide a hierarchy for nodes based by user.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;Will all users be able to update (user-based) categories, or is this a level power or by special permission only? &lt;b&gt;kthejoker&lt;/b&gt; - I was thinking of making it a level 2 power. Either that or it's open for everybody. This is a feature I want to subsequently publicize and &quot;do things with&quot;, like automate quest submissions and such.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Will usergroup categories be editable by the entire group, or just the group leader? &lt;b&gt;kthejoker&lt;/b&gt; - everyone in the group.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Will categories be significantly different than &amp;quot;tagging&amp;quot;? &lt;b&gt;kthejoker&lt;/b&gt; - Yes, signifitcantly. This is more like &quot;metanodes&quot;, or Amazon lists. Think &quot;A European Travelogue&quot;, &quot;Albums I Own&quot;, &quot;11 Writeups About Love&quot;, &quot;The Definitive Guide To Star Trek&quot;, etc etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Correct me if I'm wrong, but a quick look at the category and links table makes me think that the nodes in a category will be defined as:
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;links table&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;from_node:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;em&gt;category_id&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;to_node:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;em&gt;node_id of categorized node (all displayable nodetypes or just a subset?)&lt;/em&gt; (we'll have to create a [category] opcode that inserts entries here (similar to [bookmark] opcode), we'll do any filtering out of inappropriate entries there)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;linktype:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;var&gt;1935395&lt;/var&gt; &lt;em&gt;(node_id of category linktype)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;hits:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;em&gt;not used for this linktype?&lt;/em&gt; (yes, not used, nor is food)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;food:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;em&gt;I have no idea what this is for at all&lt;/em&gt; (food = &quot;weight&quot; of link)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;Progress&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NOTE: All of this should be considered in in test/beta mode. I will clean up the code (i.e., make things pageable, fix the formatting, write appropriate descriptions, etc.) once everything actually works. Also note that I might switch back from 'nodelist' to 'category' to avoid confusion (isalso links are going to say &amp;quot;XXX is also a category&amp;quot;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[Create Category] (working) - superdoc to create a new category&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[Display Categories] (working) - superdoc to list categories (NOTE: paging needs to be added)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[category] (working) - opcode to create a new category&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[category] (working) - nodetype (NOTE: I have set &amp;quot;restrict duplicate titles&amp;quot; to &amp;quot;no&amp;quot;. This is so multiple users can have their own &amp;quot;My Favorite Movies&amp;quot; (or whatever) category. [category maintenance create] ensures that two categories with the same name AND same maintainer cannot be created.&lt;li&gt;[Nodelists] (working) - nodelet to list categories you can add to (NOTE: The interface may need to be changed as some noders may eventually have hundreds of lists they can edit, and the ability to add the current node to a category. Also, I'd like to move the bookmark link from the epicenter to this nodelet, because basically, bookmarks and nodelists are very similar &lt;b&gt;kthejoker&lt;/b&gt; *sigh* we'll have to make this a [user settings] since some people won't turn on this nodelet. We can talk about this, anyway.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[category maintenance create] (working) - maintenance node for creating categories&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[category display page] (working&lt;strike&gt;, old code needs to be removed&lt;/strike&gt;) - htmlpage to display categories&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[category edit page] (working&lt;strike&gt;, old code needs to be removed&lt;/strike&gt;) - htmlpage to edit (i.e., delete links from) categories&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[E2 Client Development] and [zen theme] (working) - good sample categories to view&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;TODO:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Link to the category from nodes contained in the category&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Display user categories on homenodes]&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;STATUS:&lt;/b&gt; not started&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Display usergroup categories on usergroup pages]&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;STATUS:&lt;/b&gt; not started&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strike&gt;fix bug in [create category] page. maintainer (author_user) is being set to current user no matter what selection is made&lt;/strike&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;enable add/edit doctext for [create category] and [category edit page]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;strike&gt;&lt;p&gt;Design [Create Category] form 
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;kthejoker&lt;/b&gt; this should be revised to using op new and then a [category maintenance create] maintenance node to authenticate/deny category node creations. So the full process is: 1) create maintenance node (BETA) and assign it to the [category] nodetype (DONE) (visit the nodetype node, the option is there: 2) use the Create Category page to post the three parameters needed to create new nodes: nodetype, title, and op=new, (DONE) and then 3) modify the maintenance node as necessary to deny invalid attempts (BETA) (you may also look at [writeup maintenance create] for general guiding principles.)&lt;/strike&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strike&gt;Write new [category|opcode]&lt;/strike&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strike&gt;Write new [nodelists|nodelet]&lt;/strike&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strike&gt;Design [Display Categories] page (QUESTION: Should categories use the doctext field as a &quot;lede&quot; to the category? &lt;b&gt;kthejoker&lt;/b&gt; seems reasonable.)&lt;/strike&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strike&gt;Design Edit Category form (QUESTION: should the same users who can add a node be able to edit/delete?&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;kthejoker&lt;/b&gt; yes, absolutely.)&lt;/strike&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;/ul&gt;</doctext>
  <createtime>2008-03-26 14:55:44</createtime>
  <totalvotes>0</totalvotes>
  <node_id>1935394</node_id>
  <edittime>0000-00-00 00:00:00</edittime>
  <type_nodetype>854232</type_nodetype>
  <document_id>1935394</document_id>
  <author_user>1312198</author_user>
  <title>Category Nodes</title>
</node>
