<node>
  <doctext>&lt;h4&gt;Purpose&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The primary purpose of the E2 Ticketing System is to be the one-stop shop for all e2 service tickets: nuke requests, title changes, bugs, feature requests, writeup moves, account issues, etc. Basically anything you would normally ask an editor or admin via message or posting on the site you would post here instead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;Implementation&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There will be a &lt;b&gt;[ticket_type]&lt;/b&gt; nodetype to cover the various request types.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There where also be a &lt;b&gt;[ticket]&lt;/b&gt; nodetype for the actual requests.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We'll need a &lt;b&gt;[ticket]&lt;/b&gt; dbtable which will include:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The type of ticket (ticket_type node_id)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The submitter (user_id)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The group/user in charge of the ticket (editors, admins, edev, single user if applicable) - this will probably be set according to the ticket type.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A description of the ticket (set by the user)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A hash of node(s) applicable to the ticket&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A status (this should be based on our current [status] nodetype, but we may need to revise our current status nodes to meet our needs.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We'll need a &lt;b&gt;Submit Ticket&lt;/b&gt; superdoc to allow users to enter the ticket type, a description, and a list of nodes (by title). (The backend will need to translate node titles to node_ids.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We'll also need a &lt;b&gt;[Ticket Center]&lt;/b&gt; superdoc to allow staff and superusers to handle their tickets. This will need segregation of tickets based on the ability to handle them (editors shouldn't see admin-only tickets, etc.) as well as integration of some of our various administrative tools (Nodeshell Hopper, etc.) and possibly invention of new mass-node tools that will essentially make completing a &quot;delete nodeshells&quot; or &quot;change writeup title&quot; a one-click process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We'll need two &lt;b&gt;[ticket]&lt;/b&gt; notifications that get called when every ticket is submitted - one for the submitter (for tracking) and one posted at large (for spotting.)
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;Rootbeer277's plan&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I'd like to tackle this project.

&lt;p&gt;This is how I picture the ticket system.  Keep in mind that I do not have a job with a ticketing system in place and have no idea how this sort of thing works in real life.  As for the look and feel, I see this as being sort of a public version of scratch pads, except replace &quot;private&quot; pads with &quot;admin only&quot;.

&lt;p&gt;Tickets would have:

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;created by user ID
&lt;li&gt;date created
&lt;li&gt;date closed
&lt;li&gt;description (just like doctext)
&lt;br&gt;First sentence of description should be phrased in such a way that it is a one-sentence summary
&lt;li&gt;hash of affected nodes
&lt;li&gt;status
	&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Open
	&lt;li&gt;Rejected &amp; Closed
	&lt;li&gt;Handled &amp; Closed
	&lt;li&gt;Being Handled
	&lt;li&gt;Wait (admin only)
	&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;ticket_type
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;username change
&lt;li&gt;msg forward
&lt;li&gt;copyright issues 
&lt;li&gt;nuke request
&lt;li&gt;title change
&lt;li&gt;bug report
&lt;li&gt;feature request
&lt;li&gt;reparenting
&lt;li&gt;account problem
&lt;li&gt;human resources issue
&lt;li&gt;Unacceptable writeup (eds/admins only)
&lt;br&gt;this is for tracking linkless, etc, New Writeups even after they have fallen off the NW list.
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;assigned to (admin only):
	&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;open (default) (all access restricted to admins until assigned)
&lt;li&gt;editors
&lt;li&gt;admins
&lt;li&gt;coders (including edev)
&lt;li&gt;human resources (auto admin-only)
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;closed / being handled by (restricted to someone in the group assigned, or admins)
&lt;li&gt;comment / reason (restricted to person who closed /  it, or admins)
&lt;li&gt;admin only flag (hides from all non-admins, including edev if applicable)
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;
&lt;u&gt;Field            Type       Default              Null  Key  Extra&lt;/u&gt;
ticket_id        int(11)                         NO    PRI  auto_increment
user_created     int(11)                         NO
user_assigned    int(11)                         NO
date_created     datetime   0000-00-00 00:00:00  NO
date_closed      datetime   0000-00-00 00:00:00  NO
summary          char(255)                       NO
description      text                            YES
status           int(11)    0                    NO
type_ticket      int(11)    0                    NO
locked_user      int(11)    0                    NO
locked_comment   char(255)                       YES
admin_only       int(2)     0                    NO
nodes_affected   ???
&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tickets are created by at Ticket Center by any user.  There should be a link at the bottom of nodes, under the softlinks, that would take you to Ticket Center and auto-fill applicable details.  In node view, this would fill in the node_id, in writeup view, the writeup_id in the node hash.

&lt;p&gt;Ticket Center would work like Scratch Pads, generating a list of tickets with Admin Only tickets hidden by everyone except admins and the ticket creator.  By default it would list tickets, 50 per page, in order of submission.  Filters can display tickets of status x and/or tickets assigned to group y.  

&lt;p&gt;In list view it would display the creator, one-sentence summary (the first sentence of the description), date created, status, type, and the name of the user who is handling it.  Everyone can see the list view, except for admin only tickets.

&lt;p&gt;In ticket view, everything is displayed, but there are restrictions on what can be changed (see list above).  Only editors, admins, and the creator can see the ticket view, unless it's been assigned to coders, in which case edev can also see them, unless it's admin only.

&lt;p&gt;When tickets are opened, a Notifications Nodelet message appears for editors and admins.  When a ticket is closed, a /msg is sent to the originator.  The handler should always fill out the comment section, which would be a text input box, when handling and closing tickets.  If the handler wishes to add more detail the description textarea can be used.
</doctext>
  <core>0</core>
  <reputation>0</reputation>
  <lockedby_user>0</lockedby_user>
  <createtime>2008-05-23 12:45:04</createtime>
  <locktime>0000-00-00 00:00:00</locktime>
  <totalvotes>0</totalvotes>
  <hits>0</hits>
  <node_id>1942940</node_id>
  <edittime>0000-00-00 00:00:00</edittime>
  <type_nodetype>854232</type_nodetype>
  <document_id>1942940</document_id>
  <author_user>1312198</author_user>
  <package>0</package>
  <title>E2 Ticketing System</title>
</node>
