<node>
  <doctext>[chromatic] sez:
&lt;p&gt;
In the double interests of making Everything (the Engine) more flexible and reducing load by providing alternate, customizable interfaces for power users, it's clear to me that providing information in an XML format is the way to go.
&lt;p&gt;
This will allow clients to be written in [JavaScript] (ya freaks), [Perl], [Python], [Ruby], C, with bindings to all sorts of toolkits, like [Tk], [Gnome], [QT], [Win32], [HTML], and the like.
&lt;p&gt;
There are enough clever people around that even when there weren't good interfaces, a handful of [Perl Monks] and [E2] users wrote their own chatterbox clients and the like.  Wrapping the data in XML there helped server processing time and client parsing time.
&lt;p&gt;
You all know the benefits here, I won't have to mention [CSS] or anything like that.
&lt;p&gt;
The problem is, not everything on [Everything] has an XML interface.  Some page elements aren't appropriate.  Two do come immediately to mind -- nodelets and user settings.
&lt;p&gt;
My idea is to provide a nodelet XML htmlpage that can wrap up nodelet content in a fairly-consistent XML interface.  This will allow clients to request individual nodelets as appropriate, without having to generate them for each page request (especially in the case of static nodelets) or for nodelets that rarely change.  It would even be possible for a client to dedicate itself to a nodelet, in the case of the chatterbox.
&lt;p&gt;
There are several things to be determined, including:
&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Distinguishing between static and dynamic content&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Determining how often a nodelet should be updated&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Handling interactive elements (such as forms) properly&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Integrating navigational elements (links, search forms) into a regular display element&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
It would be nice to come up with a standard schema or DTD to make implementation easier on both sides.  Before we go that far, it's probably better to decide if I'm on the right track here with my analysis of the problem, the information to support, and the solution.
&lt;p&gt;
Comments welcome.
&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;[N-Wing] says&lt;/strong&gt;: (off-topic) (updated: all this stuff is what &lt;strong&gt;should&lt;/strong&gt; happen, although it doesn't seem to &lt;tt&gt;:)&lt;/tt&gt; ) edev people note: only edev people can see this page, and any edev person can edit this page (append &lt;code&gt;&amp;amp;displaytype=edit&lt;/code&gt; to the URL). However, when you edit this, to avoid accidently stepping on somebody's else's toes, usually it is smart to write what you're going to add on your computer, copy your text, refresh the edit page, paste your text, and hit &quot;stumbit&quot; really fast.
&lt;hr /&gt;</doctext>
  <createtime>2001-04-26 17:59:39</createtime>
  <totalvotes>0</totalvotes>
  <node_id>1030333</node_id>
  <edittime>0000-00-00 00:00:00</edittime>
  <type_nodetype>854232</type_nodetype>
  <document_id>1030333</document_id>
  <author_user>8652</author_user>
  <title>Everything XML Interface</title>
</node>
