<node>
  <doctext>&lt;p&gt;I would like to take the time to say that I seem to have become the E2 resident &lt;b&gt;graphics monkey&lt;/b&gt;. So, if you have need of any graphics, such as nodelet titles, or what have you, please contact me in any way E2 allows and/or my homenode speaks of.

&lt;p&gt;I am also learning perl, XML, PHP, and mySQL, so eventually I might be able to help/contribute in that regard.

&lt;p&gt;I am, however, a full-fledged website designer, and I know HTML and CSS like the back of my hand. I don't even use frames or tables anymore, I am so HTML4/CSS2 compliant.&lt;small&gt;&lt;small&gt;I seem to be a professional braggart too&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;

&lt;hr&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is my nook on &lt;a href=&quot;http://everything2.net/index.pl?type=usergroup&amp;node=edev&quot;&gt;edev&lt;/a&gt;, where I will be testing a few things and adding information such as feature requests and such. I will try to implement some of these if I get the go-ahead and I am sufficiently educated in the &lt;a href=&quot;http://everything2.net/index.pl?node=perl&quot;&gt;language at hand&lt;/a&gt; at that time.

&lt;hr&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Features to Possibly Add In the Future?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;small&gt;I'm working on them too!&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Chatterbox+
&lt;li&gt;#everything IRC nodelet
&lt;li&gt;Slashdot-style up/down/close nodelets
&lt;li&gt;Message nodelet
&lt;li&gt;New theme (my pet project)
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;Chatterbox+&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have a vision of a new chaterbox that takes the old one and puts it on steroids. Here's the spiel:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Client-pull data aquiring
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;IFRAME&lt;/i&gt; for quick and easy refreshing
&lt;li&gt;Topic typically associated with Chatterbox rather than the &lt;i&gt;users&lt;/i&gt; nodelet
&lt;li&gt;Room switching available from Chatterbox
&lt;li&gt;Custom room option (choose &lt;i&gt;other room&lt;/i&gt; from the drop down &lt;i&gt;room&lt;/i&gt; menu, which changes the &lt;i&gt;talk&lt;/i&gt; button to a &lt;i&gt;change room&lt;/i&gt; button, allowing one to type in the name to switch to that room)
&lt;li&gt;Perhaps #everything IRC integration (&lt;b&gt;this will cause controversy&lt;/b&gt;, but still keeping the Chatterbox, of course)
&lt;li&gt;Two-line message entering
&lt;li&gt;Allowing users to use the old Chatterbox (not everyone has &lt;i&gt;IFRAME&lt;/i&gt; support)
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some of these, I understand, will never get implemented, because some of them &lt;a href=&quot;http://everything2.net/index.pl?node=in%20your%20opinion&quot;&gt;IYO&lt;/a&gt; are probably not that great of ideas...

&lt;h4&gt;#everything IRC Nodelet&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This would be shockingly easy to implement. I have seen several IRC clients that use perl and/or PHP to implement this, without icky stuff like Java or even &lt;i&gt;IFRAME&lt;/i&gt;s. Support could be added for other IRC areas of E2 interest, like the edev one (forgive me, I can't think of any other E2 IRC rooms :/ ), by simply adding a drop-down menu. I am sure this is pretty low on everyone's priority list though.

&lt;h4&gt;Slashdot-Style Up/Down/Close Nodelets&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This would be another easy one to implement. If anyone has been to Slashdot and has an account, I am sure sie has seen this. Basically, each nodelet (they're called slashboxes, if I do remember correctly) have an up arrow to move the nodelet one nodelet up, a down one to do likewise, and a close button between them, which is pretty self-explanatory. I think E2 should be able to do this too...

&lt;h4&gt;Message Nodelet&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was thinking of a message nodelet, which would clean up the chatterbox and the people could have one or the other. I had in mind something similar to a pared-down message inbox. I'll w/u the particulars later.

&lt;h4&gt;New Theme&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I would like to create my own theme in pure CSS2 and strict HTML 4 that would look good in all sufficiently supporting browsers. Because of the aforementioned stringency in adhering to the standards, this will ensure that all new browsers should support this site in all of its glory.
&lt;p&gt;In addition, I would be using &lt;b&gt;no&lt;/b&gt; tables or frames, as in CSS2 they are deprecated. Everything (except for the &lt;i&gt;IFRAME&lt;/i&gt; in the Chatterbox+, which there are ways to get around, like DHTML) would be used without these two plagues of web design (using tables for layouts has been likened to using GOTO statements by some designers).
&lt;p&gt;I understand that a lot of stuff is still hard-coded, but I would not mind going around to help aid that problem.
&lt;p&gt;Ailie has talked about full free CSS freeform for EKW, which I would not mind helping with as well. I would like to take that one step further and help make a full-fledged &lt;b&gt;theme editor&lt;/b&gt; using tags like &lt;b&gt;{{title}}&lt;/b&gt; to show where the title would go. For an example of implementation, check out &lt;a href=&quot;http://noahgrey.com&quot;&gt;Greymatter&lt;/a&gt;.

&lt;hr&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;This Area Reserved For Testing Purposes&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I intend to build some time-saving widgets which I will post here...</doctext>
  <createtime>2002-06-29 00:18:27</createtime>
  <totalvotes>0</totalvotes>
  <node_id>1324475</node_id>
  <edittime>0000-00-00 00:00:00</edittime>
  <type_nodetype>854232</type_nodetype>
  <document_id>1324475</document_id>
  <author_user>1146310</author_user>
  <title>TheChronicler's International Node of Mystery</title>
</node>
