<node>
  <doctext>&lt;p&gt;The [E2 Flash Chatterbox Client] is a client, developed in Flash 5.0, that uses the Universal Message XML Ticker to allow interaction with the [chatterbox]. In addition to viewing the current chatterbox messages it also allows a user to sign in and send messages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The client consists of 4 primary files:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;e2chatterbox.swf - the actual flash file. It's primary job is to parse the XML and provide the user interface. The fla file can be downloaded at cornetdesign.com/e2chatterbox.fla&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;e2chatterbox.asp - The primary file that handles displaying the login form and the flash movie.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;e2Login.asp - the page that handles the login to E2. It works by making a call with the username and password provided via the login form to the E2 server. If the E2 server returns the userpass cookie, it captures it and sets a variable that allows that to be passed in subsequent interactions with the E2 server.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;getChatterboxXML.asp - This file handles the grabbing of the XML file. Yes, the flash movie has the capability of calling the ticker by itself. However, interactions between flash movies and files on other servers is spotty. This also allows me to handle some last minute server side changes without affecting the flash movie.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
The ASP files can be seen in their entirities by going to cornetdesign.com/e2chatterboxflash.txt (although for some reason IE still renders the ASP code). &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Future Enhancements&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Access to inbox. Perhaps allowing for toggling between chatterbox and inbox&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pipe Links! Not sure yet how to handle displaying the pipe links, but this is a big one.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proper rendering of character entities - I think I was a bit lazy when I handled that part of the movie&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</doctext>
  <core>0</core>
  <reputation>0</reputation>
  <lockedby_user>0</lockedby_user>
  <createtime>2002-11-11 02:13:07</createtime>
  <locktime>0000-00-00 00:00:00</locktime>
  <totalvotes>0</totalvotes>
  <dlurl>http://www.cornetdesign.com/e2.html</dlurl>
  <homeurl>http://www.cornetdesign.com</homeurl>
  <hits>0</hits>
  <node_id>1386266</node_id>
  <edittime>0000-00-00 00:00:00</edittime>
  <e2client_id>1386266</e2client_id>
  <type_nodetype>1261857</type_nodetype>
  <version>0.8</version>
  <document_id>1386266</document_id>
  <author_user>938208</author_user>
  <package>0</package>
  <clientstr>chatterbox.flash.5.0</clientstr>
  <title>E2 Flash Chatterbox Client</title>
</node>
