<node>
  <doctext>&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;........................07.august.2003........................&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Nodal/0.1.0 &amp;#91;beta 1&amp;#93;&lt;/b&gt; is now available &lt;a href=&quot;http://joseweeks.com/nodal/Nodal-0.1.0.tar.gz&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; as a perl package, for those with an OS with a &lt;code&gt;[make]&lt;/code&gt; command, and &lt;a href=&quot;http://joseweeks.com/nodal/nodal_wininstall&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; as a windows installer.
&lt;p&gt;Screenshots are available &lt;a href=&quot;http://joseweeks.com/nodal&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nodal is an [Integrated Noding Environment]. It contains a browser specialized for use with E2, a writeup editor a la [dann]'s [Offline Scratchpad], and a chatterbox client. It also contains a number of minor components.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nodal contains two executables: &lt;code&gt;chatter&lt;/code&gt;, a stripped-down chatterbox client, and &lt;code&gt;nodal&lt;/code&gt;, the full Nodal program.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;r e q u i r e m e n t s&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[perl] 5.8.0
&lt;li&gt;perl packages: [XML::Twig], [LWP], [Tk], and [e2interface|E2::Interface]
&lt;li&gt;(optional) perl package [IO::String] (for the console component)
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;w i n d o w s &amp;nbsp; i n s t a l l a t i o n&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;
If you haven't already installed [perl], you'll need to do so. ActiveState provides an easy-to-use windows perl distibution which can be downloaded &lt;a href=&quot;http://activestate.com/Products/Download/Download.plex?id=ActivePerl&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; (make sure you download ActivePerl 5.8.0 rather than 5.6.1).
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Right-click &lt;a href=&quot;http://joseweeks.com/nodal/nodal_wininstall&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;code&gt;&lt;b&gt;Save Link Target As&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/code&gt;, adding &quot;.pl&quot; to the end of the filename.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(Anyone who knows how to disable script execution in [.htaccess] to allow downloads of .pl files, /msg me.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Double-click on &quot;nodal_wininstall&quot;.
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;u n i x &amp;nbsp; i n s t a l l a t i o n&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Download &lt;a href=&quot;http://joseweeks.com/nodal/Nodal-0.1.0.tar.gz&quot;&gt;this tarball&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Install the dependencies from [CPAN]:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;tt&gt;bash$ &lt;b&gt;perl -MCPAN -e shell&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
cpan&gt; &lt;b&gt;install E2::Interface IO::String&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/tt&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Answer 'Yes' if prompted to follow dependencies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Untar the tarball you've downloaded, &lt;code&gt;cd&lt;/code&gt; into the new directory, and install:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;tt&gt;bash$ &lt;b&gt;tar xvzf Nodal-0.1.0.tar.gz&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
bash$ &lt;b&gt;cd Nodal-0.1.0&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
bash$ &lt;b&gt;perl Makefile.PL &amp;amp;&amp;amp; make &amp;amp;&amp;amp; su root make install&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Password: *******&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/tt&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;u s a g e&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nodal contains two executables: &lt;b&gt;nodal&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;chatter&lt;/b&gt;. The former is the full-featured e2 client, the latter a stripped-down chatterbox client.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;f e a t u r e s&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nodal is currently structured much like [mozilla] or [opera]: a main frame that that allows multiple tabs, with an optional sidebar that itself allows multiple tabs. The main frame can display any number of browser tabs, a writeup editor, a private message browser, and a node tracker. The sidebar frame can display a chatterbox client, a list of softlinks, a new/c!/edcool list, and an autolinker.&lt;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The browser is intended to emulate, at least in part, e2's [ekw] theme. It supports multiple font faces, colors, and sizes. It can currently only display e2nodes, writeups, and users, but supports these fairly well. (The browser also does some heavy caching, so, for people like me who take their laptops far from phone lines and wireless access points and so on, all already-viewed nodes should be available offline.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The editor currently only supports split-screen and source-only modes (a [WYSIWYG] mode is planned), and works pretty much the way the [Offline Scratchpad] does... except that clicking 'Edit' on a browser window will open the loaded node in the editor (loading your writeup in that node, if you have one; loading a pre-saved version of that node, if one exists; or loading an empty writeup). The browser's home page also lists your &quot;in progress&quot; writeups.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The chatterbox client works the way one would expect: auto-refresh, messages scrolling down the screen, an  entry field at the bottom with a &quot;Talk&quot; button next to it. It also contains an IM-like system for retrieving private messages: Any unarchived private messages cause a bar to appear below the chat area, with the author's name and the number of unarchived messages you have from him/her. Clicking on this name pops up a message window with the text of their message and a reply field. Any private messages that have been split due to length are re-joined.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nodal also has a private message browser, which works pretty much like E2's [Message Browser].&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Etc., etc., etc. Those features that one would expect from a full-featured e2client but aren't in Nodal are most likely forthcoming (e.g. list generators, nodegel visualizer and various graph generators, spellchecking, etc.). If there's something you'd like to see, I'd be glad to hear about it.
&lt;p&gt;Other planned features:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[Gtk2] support, whenever perl-gtk2 becomes usable (Tk is damned ugly on Linux).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Progressive nodetracker/visualizer/etc. Animated nodegraphs over time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Vote queueing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Import of [Offline Scratchpad] files.
&lt;li&gt;A decent configuration system (currently, the conf file must be edited by hand).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Errors and exceptions listed in the gui (rather than the console).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Various browser tweaks (homenode pictures, better handling of HTML lists, etc.).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;c o n f i g u r a t i o n&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The configuration file for nodal is stored, on unix systems, in &lt;code&gt;~/.nodal/conf&lt;/code&gt;, and on windows in &lt;code&gt;{INSALLATION DIRECTORY}/conf&lt;/code&gt;. It contains nothing more than a list of &quot;option = value&quot; pairs. The following are all the valid options (if a value is specified, that value is the default):&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;dl&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;code&gt;cookie&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dd&gt;This is the value of the &quot;userpass&quot; key stored in the cookie E2 provides. You should not need to set this manually.&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;code&gt;domain = everything2.com&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dd&gt;The domain name (without the &quot;http://&quot; or the trailing &quot;/&quot;) used to access everything2.&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;code&gt;visible = browser:chatter&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dd&gt;This is a &quot;:&quot;-separated list of components that are visible upon startup. These may include the following: browser, chatter, newcool, tracker, and message.&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;code&gt;skip_wizard&lt;/code&gt; = 0&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dd&gt;If this option is false AND no cookie is set, the login wizard is displayed upon startup. Setting it true, then, is useful if the wizard is bothing you and you have no E2 account (or are using nodal strictly offline) and so are unable to login to disable it.&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;code&gt;main_height&lt;/code&gt; = 400&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;code&gt;main_width&lt;/code&gt; = 600&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;code&gt;main_sidebar_width&lt;/code&gt; = 200&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dd&gt;The dimensions (in pixels) of the main window's height, its width (not including the sidebar), and the width of its sidebar. The window automatically resizes if either the main frame or the sidebar frame is created or destroyed (unless the window is maximized), using these dimensions.&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;code&gt;font_face = Times&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;code&gt;font_face_mono = Courier&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;code&gt;font_size = 12&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;code&gt;font_size_mono = 12&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dd&gt;Font face and size for both variable-width and mono text.&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;code&gt;font_color = black&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;code&gt;font_color_link = blue&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;code&gt;font_color_active = red&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;code&gt;font_color_hover = darkblue&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dd&gt;Text color for, respectively, plain text, links, links while clicked, links during mouseover.&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;code&gt;style_background = lightgray&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;code&gt;style_oddrow = gray&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;code&gt;style_heading = darkgray&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dd&gt;Background color for, respectively, plain text, every other row in a list, and headings.&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;code&gt;chatter_refresh = 30&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dd&gt;Interval (in seconds) between chatterbox refreshes.&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;code&gt;chatter_private_refresh = 300&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dd&gt;Interval (in seconds) between refreshes of private messages.&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;code&gt;edit_refresh = 1000&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dd&gt;Interval (in milliseconds) between refreshes of the editor's preview pane while in split-screen mode (0 means only when the &quot;Refresh&quot; button is pressed).&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;code&gt;newcool_refresh = 600&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dd&gt;Interval (in seconds) between refreshes of the &quot;New Writeups,&quot; &quot;Cool Nodes,&quot; and &quot;Editor Cools&quot; tickers.&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;code&gt;linker_success_color = darkblue&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;code&gt;linker_failure_color = red&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;code&gt;linker_exception_color = yellow&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dd&gt;Text color of completed link in the autolinker. Respectively, these represent (1) success at linking, (2) failure at linking, or (3) indeterminate (perl exception generated).&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;code&gt;linker_sleep = 30&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dd&gt;Interval (in seconds) between the time the autolinker completes one link and begins the next.&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;/dl&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;k n o w n &amp;nbsp; i s s u e s&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The big one is perl-tk's broken [unicode] support. Really odd unicode issues. Nodal can display &quot;&amp;copy;&quot; and so on--unless the same paragraph contains a multi-byte character (like, say, &quot;&amp;trade;&quot;), in which case the &amp;copy; looks like this: &amp;Auml;&amp;copy;. This happens whether or not I &lt;code&gt;s/&amp;#91;\x{100}-\x{FFFF}&amp;#93;/?/g&lt;/code&gt; the text. In the best case scenario, Nodal will be able to display all single-byte characters correctly using perl-tk; hopefully, perl-gtk2 will work better with unicode.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No support for &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;sup&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; or &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;sub&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;. If anyone knows a decent way to convince Tk::Text to raise or lower text, I'd be glad to put it in.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;l i c e n s e&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nodal is &amp;copy; 2003 by Jose M. Weeks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nodal is free software; you can redistribute it and/or modify it under the same terms as Perl itself.
&lt;h2&gt;c o n t a c t&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;/msg [Simpleton] or email &lt;a href=mailto:jose@joseweeks.com&gt;jose@joseweeks.com&lt;/a&gt;.







</doctext>
  <createtime>2003-05-04 07:14:34</createtime>
  <dlurl>http://joseweeks.com/nodal/Nodal-0.1.0.tar.gz</dlurl>
  <homeurl>http://joseweeks.com/nodal/</homeurl>
  <node_id>1458471</node_id>
  <edittime>0000-00-00 00:00:00</edittime>
  <e2client_id>1458471</e2client_id>
  <type_nodetype>1261857</type_nodetype>
  <version>0.1.0</version>
  <document_id>1458471</document_id>
  <clientstr>nodal</clientstr>
  <title>Nodal</title>
</node>
