<node>
  <doctext>&lt;p align=&quot;right&quot;&gt;As announced on [September 2, 2001] in [root log: September 2001]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;What are firmlinks?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&quot;Firmlinks&quot; are a new feature implemented to solve many of the content sorting problems here on E2. They are a mechanism that can point users in another direction within everything2.  This gives our database stronger cohesion, and will make it a more usable entity to find information in the future, rather than just softlinks. 
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;At the top of a node or a writeup you are viewing you may see: &lt;br&gt;&lt;h2 class=&quot;topic&quot;&gt;If you want &lt;b&gt;([node name here])&lt;/b&gt; you might also try:  &lt;b&gt;([better choices here])&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;br&gt;
An example exists at [Millenium] (one n).  It is a misspelling of the word [millennium], but has a firmlink to it. Firmlinks uses an underlying and already tested system (really similar to that which does softlinks) to connect nodes. It is the same perf hit to the db as if the node had a few more softlinks.  That is all. This is a relatively cheap feature that will help put the database in order.  Coded into the system is the ability for gods and editors to create firmlinks from one node to another.  They display whether or not you are on an E2 node, or one of it's writeups children.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Why &quot;firmlink?&quot;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
Because they are like softlinks in that they point to other nodes, but more solid, as they are chosen by editors and gods, and cannot get lost in the noise.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;How do I make them?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A god or an editor can create a firmlink by going to the bottom of an E2 node and using the add firmlink button.  If you type the title of an E2node, it links directly to that node.  It will show up at the beginning of the node, along with the other firmlinks.  The form to do so is right below the softlinks, and right above the &quot;add a writeup&quot; dialogs on the display page.  You can only add a firmlink from the e2node, not a writeup.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Can I delete a firmlink&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Only a god can delete a firmlink.  It uses the same basic method as does the deletion of a softlink&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Is there a limit to the number of firmlinks?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;No, eds and gods are free to add as many as they wish.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;What is good firmlink fodder?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The following items are suggested items for firmlinks:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Names with more than one way of saying it: [Bill Clinton], [William Jefforson Clinton],  [William J. Clinton], etc.  We should pick the most one to use (Bill Clinton maybe), and have the others firmlink to it.
&lt;li&gt;Abbreviations: [Universal Serial Bus] -&gt; [USB] (which might be more common, judgement call).
&lt;li&gt;Misspellings (or possible misspellings): [calender] -&gt; [calendar]. [Definately] -&gt; [definitely]
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
The gods will be monitoring firmlink usage, so feel free to put down as many as you want, but use them correctly.  These are NO NOISE softlinks, and should be used to organize the state of clutter in our database, and discourage wrongly spelled titles. If you destroy a see also node in a &quot;good&quot; place, put down a firmlink to supercede it.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
We should probably create a page where people can request firmlinks. It might be a lot of work going back through and re-referencing the db this way, but it will create intelligent cohesion above what is there now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
I strongly think that firmlinks are an important step towards the future of organization in the database, and now the power is in the hands of the people who shape the database, the editors and gods. We all now will be able to point users and the information in the right direction.  Please do not abuse this power, as it is an extension of trust and judgement to you, as is your ability to kill writeups.  The future of the database as it gets larger depends on it's organization, so please don't hesitate to use it.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Please give me detailed info on bug reports, theme and client included.- JayBonci&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</doctext>
  <createtime>2001-09-03 01:04:33</createtime>
  <totalvotes>0</totalvotes>
  <node_id>1150873</node_id>
  <edittime>0000-00-00 00:00:00</edittime>
  <type_nodetype>1144104</type_nodetype>
  <author_user>459692</author_user>
  <title>E2 Editing: Firmlinks</title>
</node>
