<node>
  <title>Broadcasting messages</title>
  <type_nodetype>13</type_nodetype>
  <doctext>&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is possible to send a single Chatterbox message privately to all members of a group. This function is primarily used to send messages to all [content editor]s or all [god]s.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Please use your discretion when choosing to send a broadcast message.&lt;/b&gt; Do &lt;b&gt;all&lt;/b&gt; members of the group really need to see the message? When appropriate, consider sending your message to a single person, or use [online]-only messaging (described below).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
To broadcast a message type &lt;code&gt;/tell &lt;i&gt;user_group&lt;/i&gt; &lt;i&gt;message&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/code&gt; or &lt;code&gt;/msg &lt;i&gt;user_group&lt;/i&gt; &lt;i&gt;message&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/code&gt; into the Chatterbox and click &lt;b&gt;talk&lt;/b&gt;.

The usergroups to whom you can currently broadcast messages are:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;[content_editors]&lt;/code&gt;  -  sends a message to all content editors and active gods.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;[malcontent_editors]&lt;/code&gt;  -  sends a message to all editors who choose not to ignore the [malcontent editors] chatline.  Essentially it's a joke line, silly chatter should be kept here. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;[e2gods]&lt;/code&gt;  -  sends a message to all &lt;b&gt;active&lt;/b&gt; gods; these users are generally on daily  If there's a situation that demands attention go ahead and use this msg function ... most likely there are one or two [cloaked] gods sitting around anyway.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

Since broadcast messages often pertain to things happening in the database at the moment they are sent, you can choose to send your message to only those members of the usergroup who are &lt;b&gt;online&lt;/b&gt; at the time. To do this, type a question mark (?) immediately after the &lt;code&gt;/msg&lt;/code&gt; command in your message.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;b&gt;Examples:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
To tell all online gods and content editors that you are speaking with the user Hapless Noder, type&lt;br&gt;
&lt;code&gt;/tell? content_editors I'm talking to &amp;#91;Hapless Noder&amp;#93; about his last writeup now.&lt;/code&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
To ask all gods if they know what happened to a given node, type&lt;br&gt;
&lt;code&gt;/msg e2gods Does anyone know what happened to &amp;#91;My first writeup is so groovy&amp;#93;? Msg me privately.&lt;/code&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;




&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Back to [God Powers and How to Use Them]&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</doctext>
  <node_id>1081562</node_id>
</node>
