<node>
  <doctext>&lt;p&gt;To begin, [Lord Brawl]'s original post...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;C! Changes&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
I don't entirely like it. But I don't hate it either, and I think it can be fixed.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;The Changes&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
As I understand it:
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The number of &lt;b&gt;C!&lt;/b&gt;s available at each level was slightly reduced
&lt;li&gt;A &lt;b&gt;C!&lt;/b&gt; is now worth 3 XP instead of 10
&lt;li&gt;Every user now has an opportunity to &lt;b&gt;C!&lt;/b&gt; any writeup, rather than it being an
exclusive operation by the first user to &lt;b&gt;C!&lt;/b&gt; a writeup
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
There is no &lt;em&gt;UnC!&lt;/em&gt; despite much chatterbox debate, and a lot of &lt;b&gt;-1C&lt;/b&gt; visible in the database.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
I will argue from this base of understanding.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;What C! means&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
What is the meaning of a &lt;b&gt;C!&lt;/b&gt;? I think if has come to serve two key purposes:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A one-time shot of bonus XP for particularly good work, given by &lt;em&gt;any user&lt;/em&gt; who's leveled high enough
&lt;li&gt;Added exposure for a good writeup that may have passed unnoticed by the community
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
I think the ability of any user who's contributed enough to the community to &lt;em&gt;significantly&lt;/em&gt; reward another user is a key element of E2. I've always liked this egalitarian part of E2. I'll return to this idea under &lt;i&gt;Impact&lt;/i&gt; below.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
I think that the ability to discover old gems buried in the database and put them onto the front page is another very positive feature. I've sometimes wished that writeups could &lt;strong&gt;not&lt;/strong&gt; be cooled until they were no longer on [Everything New Nodes], or at least the &lt;em&gt;New Writeups&lt;/em&gt; list. This might reduce, say, the usual race to cool any new writeup by [junkpile]. But I digress.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Of course, &lt;b&gt;C!&lt;/b&gt;s can be abused too, used like [vote tag] in a small group of friends or to make the front page say &quot;[Serve] [women] [popsicle]s [made] [from] [pee]&quot;. (Yes, I de-pluralized popsicles. I am a party pooper.)
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Impact&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
It's hard to argue when I don't know what the rationale was for the changes. I wish we'd talked this through
beforehand&amp;sup1.
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I've often thought there were too many &lt;b&gt;C!&lt;/b&gt;s. But note that I almost never almost use all of mine in a day. Someone who values a &lt;b&gt;C!&lt;/b&gt; as a primary reward may feel otherwise. I have seen people talk in the catbox  about &quot;dumping&quot; their &lt;b&gt;C!&lt;/b&gt;s at the end of day, which I feel is a bad thing, as it detracts from the reward aspect of the &lt;b&gt;C!&lt;/b&gt;. In short, I favour the reduced number of daily &lt;b&gt;C!&lt;/b&gt;s.
&lt;li&gt;As stated, I like the ability of users to &lt;em&gt;significantly&lt;/em&gt; reward each other with &lt;b&gt;C!&lt;/b&gt;s.
I think 3 XP reduced the value of a &lt;b&gt;C!&lt;/b&gt; and makes it a penny-ante reward.
&lt;li&gt;I think that this change blurs the line between a &lt;b&gt;C!&lt;/b&gt; and a vote, and in fact makes the &lt;b&gt;C!&lt;/b&gt; 
into a sort of super-vote. I think this is a bad thing.  I note that [I'm trippin' my nut sack into a frenzy of dik play] has seen a lot of &lt;b&gt;C!&lt;/b&gt; activity already. Hopefully this was not the intent of the change.
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;Changes&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
What I would do if I ran the zoo:
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Gods should gain the ability to bestow C!s&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Since we can top up a user's votes, why not &lt;b&gt;C!&lt;/b&gt;s as well? This would be a feature I would use.
Used with care, this could be a meaningful reward from the gods, just like added votes are today.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Increase XP value of a C! to 5&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
I think the XP value of a &lt;b&gt;C!&lt;/b&gt; should be 5, not 3. To me 5 XP is a meaningful reward from another user. 3 XP is noise.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Change how multiple C!s work&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Multiple &lt;b&gt;C!&lt;/b&gt;s can be a positive thing, if we can prevent &quot;C! swarming&quot;. I'd like to see this implemented
as follows: Only one &lt;b&gt;C!&lt;/b&gt; would be permitted on a writeup, but the &lt;b&gt;C!&lt;/b&gt; would &lt;em&gt;expire&lt;/em&gt; after some time had passed (say, one month). This would allow truly cool writeups to be rediscovered and returned to prominence, but would prevent the sort of nonsense [I'm trippin' my nut sack into a frenzy of dik play] has already shown us. I think the total number of &lt;b&gt;C!&lt;/b&gt;s given should still be tracked and displayed.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;User search changes&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
If multiple cools stay, I think it would be good to be able to do a user writeup search by &quot;Most Cool&quot; to see what's getting a lot of &lt;b&gt;C!&lt;/b&gt; action, and by &quot;Least Cool&quot; to see what's not getting any attention. 
(Perhaps [datagirl] has a writeup no one cooled yet!)
While I'm on the topic, I'd like to see user search by &quot;Most Active&quot; and &quot;Least active&quot;, too -- so I can see what's getting a lot of voting action, and what's languishing in obscurity.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;Summary&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
I like to see E2 change and evolve. I think this change misses the mark out of the gate, but can be tuned to 
become another significant step forward for E2.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WickerNipple:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Concerning 'expiration'... I'm all for it, as long as we maintain that a given node can still only be c!ed once by a given person... Were we to use this system though, I'd be in favor of 3xp per c! - as much as I wasn't crazy about it the first time I saw it.  If nodes are going to be able to be c!ed more than once, it's simply going to have to be a super-vote as opposed to the xp hammer.&lt;/p&gt;
Concerning C! handouts... I'm entirely against it.  The new xp system is obviously designed to limit the number of C!s available for chinging things like the toilet seat... everyone has their favorite pet nodes they ran out and hit today to place their emphasis, but that trend will run out and people will simply have to become more careful.  We shouldn't tread on the new experiment.  Handing out C!s like candy does that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
In response to Lord Brawl's request for feedback, [Gritchka] said:
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
The devaluation to 3 XP reduces the good I can do, and I take great care of and pleasure in my C!ing. 
I try to use all 6 every day, even if I spend the last hour of the day hunting around for something. 
I often leave work having spent 105 votes and only 3 C!s, so that gives me something to savour in the evening. 
As with factual vs junk, people who C! properly are now penalized because of the abuse that's been going on. 
The simple solution would have been to take the power from the three worst offenders, 
such as by cursing them until they stop. The remaining power, to put things on the front page, 
is I suspect going to be swamped and worthless. 
A truth the good [Pseudo_Intellectual] told me long ago was that
personal messages are far better (more effective, more pleasing) than votes and cools. So I've
made a macro, which I'm now going to use as I used to use C!s.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr&gt;
[Jinmyo] sez:&lt;br&gt;
First off: As [dem bones] said in his initial proclamation on this topic: &quot;I am the worst.&quot; There is of course no question about that. Any attempts to question this, even if merely a quiver of the lip or a finger straying over a key, will be summarily dealt with. No question about it.&lt;p&gt;

However, I think that some discussion of the relative merits of the proclamation itself might be worthwhile (even if punishable).&lt;p&gt;

In general, as stated, I agree with [Lord Brawl].&lt;p&gt;

There's an obvious point but I thought I'd mention it. I wonder if devaluing a ching to 3 XP makes them easier to throw away on any old junk. Knowing that a ching would bring 10 XP to the user could mean it was something one might pause and consider. If it's only 3 XP, well, it's just a supervote. I certainly think too much crud has been cooled. It will be interesting (I suppose) to see if reducing the value means cheapening the action so that we are flooded with even more kudzu.&lt;p&gt;

At this point, having just been chinged, I feel it cost the user little if any consideration. I barely feel any interest in remembering anything about the wu chinged. Maybe they really liked it, maybe they didn't. Like being voted up or down, it signifies nothing. Not only because I don't care about XP but because I can't believe the user who chinged the wu cared.&lt;p&gt;

Perhaps that might represent something useful to consider. Perhaps not.&lt;p&gt;

I often chings to stir old worthy nodegel to the visible surface. I also often use it to encourage users. The former use feels relevant still. The latter, not really.&lt;p&gt;

In closing, as required, I do hereby affirm and assert, without any reservation of heart or conscience, that bones is the &lt;b&gt;worst&lt;/b&gt;. No question about it. Amen. &lt;i&gt;/me offers the traditional E2 touching the fontanelle and spinning on one heel salute though she doesn't do it so gracefully&lt;/i&gt;&lt;p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;

[Demeter]'s $0.02 

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt; I like the opportunity to multi-ching. I think that, in the end, it will result in the 'best of the best' being duly rewarded, as people are able to C! things they *would* have chung if someone else hadn't.
&lt;li&gt; I don't mind, personally, the reduction of number of C!'s.  I rarely used all mine, because I'm bloody picky about what I put my name on to say it's &quot;cool&quot;. I can understand others' concerns thought, particularly Gritchka's -- I wish I had the time/energy to take the same approach to bestowing chings.
&lt;li&gt; On reflection, I tend to agree that 3XP for a C! is too little. It makes it a less valuable commodity to hand out, so may well mean that it is handed out more frivolously.
&lt;li&gt; With regard to bestowing Chings -- um -- I'm not sure where to come down with this one. I can see the value in it, particularly because some good new nodes may get overlooked in multi-chinging excellent older ones, and it woud be a pity if that happened. On the other hand, just handning them out harum-scarum defeats the whole point of the exercise. Perhaps an option might be a repository of chings that could be awarded by editors and gods (Perhaps as Cool Man Eddie himself), on the nomination of noders, so that noders could /msg say CME with suggestions of worthy nodes that they aren't in a position to ching themselves (possibly with an auto feature that x nominations = auto ching, others on the discretion of the gods/editors). I dunno, just an idle thought.
&lt;li&gt; I will personally curse any user chinging the damn toilet seat node, unless they can argue that they did it on the merits of the wu.  I'm sorry, but MoJoe has had his money's worth and then some out of that wu, and I *don't* want to keep seeing it on the front page.
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;

</doctext>
  <createtime>2001-07-30 17:20:26</createtime>
  <totalvotes>0</totalvotes>
  <node_id>1125401</node_id>
  <edittime>0000-00-00 00:00:00</edittime>
  <type_nodetype>13</type_nodetype>
  <document_id>1125401</document_id>
  <title>C! Changes</title>
</node>
