<node>
  <type_nodetype>13</type_nodetype>
  <doctext>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;In brief:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;tt&gt;/drag user_name&lt;/tt&gt; will bring a user into [Debriefing Room] with you.  You will be expected to talk to him about why you pulled him away from outside.  He will be locked in the Debriefing Room for 30 minutes to cool down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Full version:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EDB may be retired, but there remains the rare occasion when a user is disruptive or abusive enough in the chatterbox that he needs to be removed from the conversation for a while.  The drag command brings you to a chatroom called [Debriefing Room], and drags the target noder along with you.  You call the drag function with the following chatterbox command:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;tt&gt;/drag user_name&lt;/tt&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Where user_name is the noder's name with spaces replaced with underscores.  Unlike a borging, a user who has been dragged can still talk, albeit only in the Debriefing Room, and send private /msgs.  If you drag a user to Debriefing Room, &lt;em&gt;you will be expected to discuss why&lt;/em&gt; you did it before going back outside.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although you can leave at any time, the user will be trapped in Debriefing Room for 30 minutes and only able to chat with people in there with him.  The time remaining will be displayed in the user's Other Users nodelet, and also in a message if he tries to leave by going to one of the other rooms.  If for whatever reason you want to pull him out sooner, for example if he didn't realize what he was doing or you made a mistake, you can use the [e2 Bouncer] to get him out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A user who has been dragged into Debriefing Room will have his numborged count increased, so we can track chronic troublemakers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Back to [God Powers and How to Use Them]&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</doctext>
  <node_id>1963047</node_id>
  <title>Dragging users</title>
</node>
