<node>
  <doctext>&lt;p&gt;Ok, this isn't really a FAQ, more like a HOWTO, but I'm following site naming convensions here...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is just a checklist for the very rare times a user should be deleted. In most cases, the user should be locked instead of nuking them from the face of the Everything. If it is decided that a user &lt;em&gt;should&lt;/em&gt; be deleted, it would probably be smart to only let [nate], [JayBonci], or I do it (AFAIK, they're the only ones that know how to do all these steps anyway). In these steps, &lt;var&gt;DELETE_ID&lt;/var&gt; refers to the soon-to-be-deleted-user's node_id.&lt;br /&gt;
-- [N-Wing]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
lock them
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
see if they wrote any writeups, and possibly delete them (if the user is bad enough to be deleted, their writeups were probably way stupid anyway)
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
likewise, maybe their node heaven WUs should be nuked; or maybe not, it doesn't take much space
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
make sure they don't have any messages from people&lt;br /&gt;
SELECT COUNT(*) FROM message WHERE for_user=&lt;var&gt;DELETE_ID&lt;/var&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
if they do, maybe send the messages back to the original sender, saying it was sent to &lt;var&gt;DELETE_TITLE&lt;/var&gt;, who was deleted (if there are more than a few, it would be easy enough to write a little tool to do this)
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
see if there are any messages from the soon-to-be-delete-user&lt;br /&gt;
SELECT COUNT(*) FROM message WHERE author_user=&lt;var&gt;DELETE_ID&lt;/var&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
do &lt;strong&gt;not&lt;/strong&gt; delete those messages; the recipients most likely wouldn't want that; instead, it could be nice to send a /msg to each recipient &lt;var&gt;DELETE_TITLE&lt;/var&gt; and &lt;var&gt;DELETE_ID&lt;/var&gt;, so they can figure out who messages were from, if they want to
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
more????????????????????????????
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</doctext>
  <node_id>1385509</node_id>
  <type_nodetype>13</type_nodetype>
  <title>E2 FAQ: delete user</title>
</node>
