<node>
  <doctext>Some poor [tortured soul] has [pulling an asamoth|asamothed], and now you're stuck killing a few hundred nodes that now say, &quot;[Screw E2!]&quot;&lt;p&gt;

Fear not, for thanks to the [jaybonci|wizards] [n-wing|behind] [nate|the] [edev|curtain], you can use the [Altar of Sacrifice] to remove an entire catalog of writeups by a single [author].&lt;p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;First off, you will need to generate a list of [node ID]s. The third box on the page, aptly titled &lt;b&gt;Generate an id list for a user&lt;/b&gt;, will generate the listing for you. Enter the &quot;retired&quot; users name and hit the &lt;b&gt;Generate List&lt;/b&gt; button. After a few seconds of gears whirring and clanking noises from the server, a new page will appear with the node IDs. You will need to copy this list by highlighting the numbers and copying them (by pressing &lt;i&gt;ctrl+c&lt;/i&gt; in MS Windows machines). Don't worry, the bullets will not be copied with the node IDs.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;Now, press your back key on your [browser] to get back to the [Altar of Sacrifice] page.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;At the Altar of Sacrifice page, enter the name of the [user] in the top box titled &lt;b&gt;The Users Username&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;Paste your list of node IDs in the next box, titled &lt;b&gt;A list of the ids by that user. Name is used here as a safety.&lt;/b&gt; The name of the user is compared with the node ID to avoid [accidently] [killing] someone else's nodes. On MS Windows machines, feel free to use &lt;i&gt;ctrl+v&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;Press the &lt;b&gt;Prepare the slaughter&lt;/b&gt; button. Again, more clicking and whirring may be heard from the server as the nodes are gathered by the [system].&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;A new page will be presented to you, with the list of actual node titles appended to some words of wisdom. Nothing has been done to these nodes yet, as you need to hit the familiar button at the bottom of the list... &lt;b&gt;[The Killing Floor II]&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;After the button is pressed, you're presented with the familiar Killing Floor page, except with a huge amount of nodes to be killed. Don't waste your time entering in why the nodes were killed, perhaps just the last one will do in case the [writer] returns to check. Press the &lt;b&gt;massacre&lt;/b&gt; button to deliver them to the ghostly hands of [Klaproth], who will conduct the nodes across the river [Styx] to [Node Heaven].&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
That's all there is to it. Sure beats killing them all by hand, doesn't it? I remember back in the old days, when we'd have to track them down character by character in giant snowstorms, barefoot and with a club...
</doctext>
  <createtime>2001-11-12 13:27:59</createtime>
  <node_id>1198265</node_id>
  <edittime>0000-00-00 00:00:00</edittime>
  <type_nodetype>13</type_nodetype>
  <document_id>1198265</document_id>
  <title>E2 FAQ: Altar of Sacrifice</title>
</node>
