<node>
  <doctext>&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

[Rancid_Pickle] - this was turned in for the FAQ by [mblase] but I think it needs some work first.  Firstly, it's a bit on the negative side instead of an objective instructor tone that's ideal.  Secondly, the examples it uses aren't the best nor are they real.  Third, it doesn't really instruct on how to node with quality so much as how to avoid downvotes... does that make sense?  It's really not the same thing.
&lt;p&gt;


&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Contrary to popular belief, [Noding for Numbers] is not automatically a [Bad Thing]. [The Project project|Noding projects] are an essential part of what makes E2's database useful to everyone. Many worthy subjects are simply too massive to be confined to one [writeup], while others are better off being broken up into many nodes so that they can be [Search|searched] individually.
&lt;p&gt;
The trick to successful [NFN], if there is a &quot;trick&quot; to it, is to do it in such a way that it conforms to E2's normal standards for quality noding. Posting a large number of individually-worthwhile nodes is considered valuable here. Posting as many [inane|quick-and-dirty] writeups as you can without putting any effort into them is not.
&lt;p&gt;
If you're looking to create a few dozen or a few hundred closely related nodes, then, try to remember the following tips--not just for the sake of your own [voting/experience system|XP], but for the general edification of the database.

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;
&lt;h3&gt;[Make us care]&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;
Don't just node stuff that's already [common knowledge], or that no one who didn't live your life will be interested in. 
It's insulting to your reader.  Pick a subject that will interest the reader, something that will draw most people to say &quot;That was a really worthwhile effort,&quot; and a few to spend an hour or two exploring your entire [metanode]. 
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;Bad: &lt;u&gt;Obscure Garage Bands from My Home Town&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;Good: &lt;u&gt;England's Number One Songs and Why They Were Hits&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;
&lt;h3&gt;[Write your own stuff]&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;
E2 rarely appreciates writeups that are nothing more than [Cut-And-Paste Writeups Will Die|cut-and-paste content] from other sources, especially as part of a project. Writeups which are nothing more than identically-formatted cut-and-pasted text will be voted down at least as often as they are voted up. But when you append a few of your own [original] thoughts to those writeups, or [Copy from one, it's plagiarism; copy from two, it's research|combine information from other sources], you're making a contribution.
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;Bad: &lt;u&gt;Band Lyrics I Copied Blandly from the Liner Notes&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;Good: &lt;u&gt;Well-Formatted Lyrics, How The Song Sounds, and What They Mean&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;
&lt;h3&gt;[Quoting statistics won't impress me]&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;
The most hated NFN projects on E2 (read: [vote dumping|vote dumps]) are built from list after list of bland, uninteresting [statistics]. These are bad because they prove you put little original thought into them, but even worse, they provide little or no [context] for the information. You have full use of the [English language] at your command for every writeup you create; use it to make yourself clear.
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;Bad: &lt;u&gt;Boring Numerical Properties of the Atomic Elements&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;Good: &lt;u&gt;The Elements and How They Were Discovered&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;
&lt;h3&gt;[Pick titles carefully]&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;
If every single node title in your project is [Choose Short Titles|an obscure string of words and numbers that no one would ever hardlink or search for], you should rethink your titling scheme. Titles that people are likely to come across casually or by chance will increase the &quot;interestingness&quot; of your project as well as the sheer number of [upvote|upvoters] over time. 
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;Bad: &lt;u&gt;1989 Pontiac Trans Am Limited Edition (Metallic Navy Blue)&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;Good: &lt;u&gt;Trans Am&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;
&lt;h3&gt;[(Don't display in &quot;New Writeups&quot;)|Don't display in New Writeups]&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;
If you're going to be creating a lot of nodes at a time, it's [common courtesy] not to flood the [New Writeups] [nodelet] with half a dozen writeups on the same topic. (Besides, annoyed noders tend to [downvote] by reflex.) Either check [(Don't display in &quot;New Writeups&quot;)|that box] or space your writeups far enough apart that no more than three are displayed at a time.
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;Bad: &lt;u&gt;Battle of Gettysburg&lt;/u&gt;, &lt;u&gt;Battle of Hastings&lt;/u&gt;, &lt;u&gt;Battle of Ingersol&lt;/u&gt;, &lt;u&gt;Battle of the Bulge&lt;/u&gt;, &lt;u&gt;Battle of This&lt;/u&gt;, &lt;u&gt;Battle of That&lt;/u&gt;...&lt;/i&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;Good: &lt;u&gt;Battle of Gettysburg&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;
&lt;h3&gt;[Finish what you start]&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;
There's few things more annoying than when a noder begins a noble and comprehensive [metanode] and stops halfway through, leaving the reader hanging on an eight-month-old promise of &quot;more to come&quot;. If you're determined to Node for Numbers, be [comprehensive]. If you create an open-ended project which will need to be updated in the future, leave it open at the end in case you're not around to complete it next year.
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;Bad: &lt;u&gt;Academy Award Winners Up Through 1978&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;Good: &lt;u&gt;Academy Award Winners with Hardlinks Deliberately Left for Next Year's Results&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;
&lt;p&gt;
And, of course, the usual guidelines as spelled out in [Everything University] apply to your writeups themselves. 

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;
&lt;p align=center&gt;
&lt;b&gt;
back to&lt;br&gt;[Everything FAQ]
&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</doctext>
  <createtime>2001-09-05 06:12:19</createtime>
  <node_id>1152509</node_id>
  <edittime>0000-00-00 00:00:00</edittime>
  <type_nodetype>13</type_nodetype>
  <document_id>1152509</document_id>
  <title>E2 FAQ: Noding for Numbers</title>
</node>
