<node>
  <title>E2 FAQ: Etiquette on Everything2</title>
  <doctext>Perhaps a better title would be &quot;Etiquette and Protocol on Everything2&quot;?
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Some subjects that shall have to be touched on:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;GTKYN's
&lt;li&gt;Lyrics
&lt;li&gt;Current Copyright Law
&lt;li&gt;Personal Experience Noding
&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Are my personal experiences good noding material?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Much of the best material on E2 comes directly from people's personal experience. This doesn't mean that it's a good idea to node every detail of your personal life and you should always think twice about posting anything that you might regret later - how would you feel if your mother/ SO/ boss read it? How would &lt;b&gt;they&lt;/b&gt; feel? That being said, it is the personal aspect which makes E2 more than just an encylopaedia.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where should I put it?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
The rule to follow here is to Node for the Ages. Everyday experiences belong in the daylogs where they are put into context, rather than in a node of their own. If, however, you feel the experience is more universal, and provides an insight into a problem, issue or situation many people face, or it's a funny story that will still be funny a year from now, by all means node it away from the daylogs, but make sure you follow the general rules for where to place your write up. Check to see if there is a node your experience reates to directly before creating a new one.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Can I illustrate my points in factual write-ups with personal experiences?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Absolutely! Relevant events from your own life may help to make dry facts more interesting, to confirm a theory, or to add a layer of meaning to song lyrics. Be careful not to present your own opinions as facts, but otherwise, illustrate away.&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;Demeter&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Where to place your writeup
&lt;li&gt;&quot;Response&quot; writeups
&lt;li&gt;Nodeshelling/NRT
&lt;li&gt;TROLLS AND HOW THEY PERISH
     &lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;What is trolling and what happens if I do it?&lt;/b&gt;
     &lt;br&gt;
     &lt;br&gt;Trolling on Everything2 usually means creating inflammatory write-ups deliberately to provoke others. Those who engage in this sort of thing are called &quot;trolls,&quot; and there are several varieties of them. The best kind of troll here creates antagonistic or absurd write-ups with style, excellent writing skills, and a cleverly concealed sense of humor; this troll often does not actually believe what s/he writes and enjoys fooling others into responding in anger. Those who see the subtle wit in this kind of trolling can learn to appreciate the spectacle of it.
     &lt;br&gt;
     &lt;br&gt;The worst kind of troll creates vitriolic write-ups out of rage; they are often directed at particular noders. There is no humor or style inherent in this kind of trolling and it is not well-received on Everything 2. If this kind of troll is spotted by an editor or god, word usually spreads quickly. Abusive inflammatory write-ups will be killed; the troll may receive a warning and, if not heeded, may be locked out of the database.
     &lt;br&gt;
     &lt;br&gt;While Everything2 noders are not generally coddled by the editors and administration, disruptive offensive behavior is not tolerated.
     &lt;br&gt;
     &lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;Hugs and kisses, [knifegirl]&lt;/i&gt;
&lt;li&gt;((more subjects??))
&lt;li&gt;((more subjects??))
&lt;li&gt;((more subjects??))
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
If any of you could tackle one or two of these topics with a Q/A
format I'd appreciate it...don't worry about overlapping
topics with other gods, the more the merrier.  Just add whatever
content/thoughts you've got on these (and more) subjects here
and I'll compile all of your lies into one cohesive page.
&lt;p&gt;
Some of you have already been helping with [E2 FAQ: &quot;Censorship&quot; and &quot;Suggestions&quot;]
and any further comments about that FAQ page should be 
made here.



&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Q:&lt;/b&gt;

&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;b&gt;A:&lt;/b&gt;


&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;b&gt;Q:&lt;/b&gt;

&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;b&gt;A:&lt;/b&gt;


&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;b&gt;Q:&lt;/b&gt;

&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;b&gt;A:&lt;/b&gt;


&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;




&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;p align=center&gt;//-=-\\&lt;br&gt;
[]&lt;br&gt;
\\-=-//&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p align=center&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p align=center&gt;&lt;em&gt;back to&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;[Everything FAQ]&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</doctext>
  <type_nodetype>13</type_nodetype>
  <node_id>830141</node_id>
</node>
