<node>
  <type_nodetype>13</type_nodetype>
  <doctext>&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;(This piece was performed 6/24/2001 at &lt;b&gt;[Summit in Savannah]&lt;/b&gt; 
-- thanks to the cast and crew for a great effort. -- [wharfinger])&lt;/i&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;[wharfinger]:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Here's the time line. &lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;([noder get-together|Background and Discussion]) &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Story background: [dem bones|bones] has invited us all to a God Summit, for 
&quot;team-building&quot; and to hash out major changes in editorial policy (the latter is 
just a last-resort excuse for disagreements between 8:00 and 9:00, if we can't 
think of any better excuses). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some of this is speculative: I'm hoping [thefez] will be willing to participate,
and [Lord Brawl]'s role will have to be reassigned if he's not up for it. I don't  
know what lizard-lobe of my brain generates these things, but it's insisting on 
[Lord Brawl] in that role. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My apologies to all for moving you around like chess pieces. Art is no respecter
of persons, nor much else. If anybody wants anything more to do, please /msg me 
with ideas. Naturally, this is just a skeleton: We can all throw in bits of 
impromptu detail about what others are doing, above and beyond what's mentioned
here. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Writeups are to be noded in real time, at the end of their time slots. We may want 
to compress the time scale a bit. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&quot;Due date&quot; for first drafts is Friday 6/15;&lt;/b&gt; I'll be out of town 6/11 through 
6/14 and probably won't be on E2 much, if at all. I suggest that we all make restricted 
superdocs and get 'em on view as early as possible, so others can pick up some 
detail and avoid [continuity error]s. &lt;em&gt;Small&lt;/em&gt; continuity errors are fine, since 
all the witnesses are drunk and/or tripping, but the big stuff needs to be consistent. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;b&gt;riverrun:&lt;/b&gt; I'm thinking, like Brawl, that I should probably set this up with a little writeup about flying out to my inherited hideaway in my light plane, so things don't happen too quickly to strain credulity. Maybe node this monday afternoon. No mention of the summit in this writeup. Ideas?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;riverrun:&lt;/b&gt; Monday at 20:00 Z I noded [the little death and Veronica Lake]. I've mentioned Savannah, but the writeup is &lt;b&gt;factual&lt;/b&gt;, so please don't use details from it, with the exception of Savannah, the town near our house. Thanks. I intend to follow up with another wu or two to push myself in that direction. Any ideas on a delivery date for the whole piece?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table bgcolor=&quot;#202020&quot; cellspacing=&quot;0&quot; cellpadding=&quot;1&quot;&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;

&lt;table cellspacing=&quot;1&quot; cellpadding=&quot;8&quot; border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;
&lt;!-- header row --&gt;
&lt;tr bgcolor=&quot;#e8e8e8&quot;&gt;
&lt;td width=&quot;15%&quot; align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Time&lt;br /&gt;(US Central Time, GMT-6) &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td width=&quot;70%&quot; align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Events&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td width=&quot;15%&quot; align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Narrator&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;

&lt;!-- body --&gt;
&lt;tr bgcolor=&quot;#f8f8f8&quot; valign=&quot;top&quot;&gt;
	&lt;td align=&quot;right&quot;&gt;Submit at 8:00 pm&lt;/td&gt;
	&lt;td&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;Everybody has been arriving all afternoon at a farmhouse in a flat and 
	desolate part of Illinois. [riverrun] inherited the farmhouse from somebody. &lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;The danger here is old-fashioned block expositon. Don't describe any of us in detail:
	Just one or two quick brush-strokes at most. We're not Jane Austen. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;riverrun:&lt;/b&gt; Suggests [Summit in Savannah] for locale/title. Right at the Illinois/Iowa/Wisconsin border at the top of the Mississippi; kinda witchy, that. See the 10 P.M. timeline for more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I should think [riverrun] inherited the house from the parents of a buddy of his who died in his arms in Vietnam (electrocuted by a short in an electric guitar during a thunderstorm at the biggest concert of his career it might later be revealed). At any rate, work the Vietnam thing in early and let it be, just festering in the background.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/td&gt;
	&lt;td&gt;[dem bones] if we can rouse him from his slumber. More likely [wharfinger]. &lt;br&gt;
&lt;i&gt;[The Arrival and the Reunion]&lt;/i&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;

&lt;tr bgcolor=&quot;#f8f8f8&quot; valign=&quot;top&quot;&gt;
	&lt;td align=&quot;right&quot;&gt;Submit at 8:20 pm&lt;/td&gt;
	&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;[WickerNipple] puts LSD in the soup. You don't have to eat the soup if you 
	don't want to; I won't, because I have no clue what LSD is like. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;WN: &lt;/b&gt;I intend to add a single writeup about spiking the soup thirty minutes &lt;i&gt;after&lt;/i&gt; the deed is supposedly done... somewhat apologetic, somewhat worried... but really none of the above (&quot;hell, dannye and brawl need to loosen up a little...&quot;).  I will then simply disappear.  No mention of me actually in the plot from henceforth please except for possibly the occasional &quot;Where the hell is Wicker?&quot;  I'd like to remain very MIA at the end of the whole thing... &lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/td&gt;
	&lt;td&gt;[WickerNipple]&lt;br&gt;
&lt;i&gt;[E2 Gods Summit 2001: Lemme show ya about tripping your nut sacks] &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;

&lt;tr bgcolor=&quot;#f8f8f8&quot; valign=&quot;top&quot;&gt;
	&lt;td align=&quot;right&quot;&gt;Submit at 8:30 pm if ideath does her own writeup, 8:40 pm otherwise&lt;/td&gt;
	&lt;td&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;Drinking, arguments, etc. Or else [Jinmyo] has made mushroom soup, but 
	she gathered some of the mushrooms from near the house, you see, and it turns out 
	that her taxonomy is a bit rusty (&lt;b&gt;or else&lt;/b&gt; [WickerNipple] distracts her and 
	sneaks LSD into it while she's cooking; two independent infusions of hallucinogens
	might strain credulity a little &lt;em&gt;too&lt;/em&gt; far)... So if [Jinmyo]'s up for it, 
	this would be a [Jinmyo] cooking writeup about making soup, but written and cooked 
	under the influence of a powerful hallucinogen.
	&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;WN:&lt;/b&gt; [Jinmyo]'s soup will need to be a cold one... perhaps something meant to be cooked ahead of time and then chilled... LSD breaks down under heat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;riverrun:&lt;/b&gt; Seems like a MAJOR conflict could be developed here: that being MY house, MY reponsibility, perhaps a gentle reminder that hallucinogens need to be considered in terms of set and setting. I mean we're here to do some &lt;b&gt;bidniz&lt;/b&gt;, right? If we plant the seed early, ACK! ACID! doesn't come out of nowhere. Nice opportunity to contrast drug-induced fury/madness and the REAL DEAL, implying I'm not quite right, which is something dannye always says anyway.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;WN:&lt;/b&gt; Wait, I'm sorry... did you think I was going to tell you guys about the acid?  HA!  Surprise!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;b&gt;[Jinmyo]&lt;/b&gt; Okay. Please see [e2 Gods Summit 8:20 p.m.]. I've made a wild mushroom soup, been tasting it, starting to trip (which I don't know much about, really). This way I don't have to be too realistic and can foreshadow some of the horrors to come. Bearing the heat thing in mind, I have [WickerNipple] helping me with a salad of wild greens. He can lace the dressing. I've got the cleaver in there too.&lt;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;ailie:&lt;/b&gt; I &lt;em&gt;love&lt;/em&gt; the bit about the tiara. I may incorporate it into my meatspace existence!	
&lt;/td&gt;
	&lt;td&gt;[Jinmyo]&lt;br&gt;
&lt;i&gt;[e2 Gods Summit 8:20 p.m.]&lt;/i&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;

&lt;tr bgcolor=&quot;#f8f8f8&quot; valign=&quot;top&quot;&gt;
	&lt;td align=&quot;right&quot;&gt;Submit at 9:00 pm&lt;/td&gt;
	&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Drinking, arguments, TBA. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
	&lt;td&gt;[Jet-Poop]
&lt;i&gt;[General Noodlings by Jet-Poop]&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;

&lt;tr bgcolor=&quot;#f8f8f8&quot; valign=&quot;top&quot;&gt;
	&lt;td align=&quot;right&quot;&gt;Submit at 9:20 pm&lt;/td&gt;
	&lt;td&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;[thefez] contemplates the necessity of abducting [ideath] or somebody. It
	should be one of the women, I think.&lt;/p&gt; 
	&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;[wharfinger]&lt;/b&gt; 6/15/01: There was talk about having [Jinmyo] be the 
	abductee, but we may go back to it being [ideath]. [riverrun]'s writeup leaves 
	that open. This is [ideath]'s (or iFezth's, as it were) call, I think: The plot can work 
	with it either way. &lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;[ideath]&lt;/b&gt; 6/15/01: I'll abduct me, or however that works out. &lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/td&gt;
	&lt;td&gt;&quot;[thefez]&quot;, aka [ideath] submitting as [thefez], by his permission. 
	&lt;i&gt;(In the end, [thefez] did write about 90% of his piece - [wharfinger])&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;

&lt;tr bgcolor=&quot;#f8f8f8&quot; valign=&quot;top&quot;&gt;
	&lt;td align=&quot;right&quot;&gt;Submit at 9:30 pm&lt;/td&gt;
	&lt;td&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;[thefez] executes the abduction; [riverrun] 
	pursues [thefez] and his captive (I wrote this 
	before seeing [riverrun]'s suggestions about 	machismo/Vietnam flashbacks ([noder get-together|discussion]), 
	but IMHO this works great with that).&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/td&gt;
	&lt;td&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;[wharfinger]&lt;br&gt;
	&lt;i&gt;[The Delicate Vintages of Irvine and the Rats' Breakfast]&lt;/i&gt; It's not art, but we'll leave that to the 
	writers. It covers the story line, at least.
	&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;

&lt;tr bgcolor=&quot;#f8f8f8&quot; valign=&quot;top&quot;&gt;
	&lt;td align=&quot;right&quot;&gt;Submit at 9:50 pm&lt;/td&gt;
	&lt;td&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;[knifegirl] 
	vanishes into the kitchen with intent being somehow semi-clear to narrator; 
	[dem bones|bones] appears to have ingested something pretty damn powerful. &lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/td&gt;
	&lt;td&gt;[dannye]&lt;br&gt;
&lt;i&gt;[noder get-together: dannye]&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;

&lt;tr bgcolor=&quot;#f8f8f8&quot; valign=&quot;top&quot;&gt;
	&lt;td align=&quot;right&quot;&gt;Submit at 10:10 pm&lt;/td&gt;
	&lt;td&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;[knifegirl] performs strange and unsettling Wiccan (or whatever) rite in
	kitchen. Goal? Maybe to calm everybody down, maybe something more... &lt;i&gt;sinister&lt;/i&gt;...
	&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;On second thought:&lt;/b&gt; Maybe the rite is intended to bring peace, but the soup 
	kicks in and &lt;em&gt;things go horribly wrong!&lt;/em&gt; I like that best.
	&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/td&gt;
	&lt;td&gt;[knifegirl]&lt;bR&gt;
&lt;i&gt;[E2 God Summit 2001: 9:30 pm] &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;

&lt;tr bgcolor=&quot;#f8f8f8&quot; valign=&quot;top&quot;&gt;
	&lt;td align=&quot;right&quot;&gt;Submit at 10:30 pm&lt;/td&gt;
	&lt;td&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;[dannye] and a preternaturally mellow [dem bones] vanish into a bathroom for 
	a few minutes; when they return, [dannye] is equally mellow. [knifegirl] returns 
	from kitchen a few minutes later, looking scared. [dannye] starts to turn blue: OD. 
	[Lord Brawl|Brawl] and [wharfinger] drag [dannye] into [wharfinger]'s rental car to
	get him to a hospital. It's raining outside. [wharfinger] (drunk) pops the clutch 
	and tears off; he wraps the car around a telephone pole in sight of the house. The 
	car bursts into flame. [Lord Brawl|Brawl] goes back into the house, writes it all 
	up, blaming [dem bones|bones] for the deaths.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;riverrun:&lt;/b&gt; Here's a little piece of northern Illinois background that works, I think--In Savannah, a river town at the top of the mighty Mississippi, I walked out of a bar one night and into a STORM of locusts. So thick you couldn't see. You had to swim through them, through the incredible din of &lt;i&gt;millions&lt;/i&gt; of wings beating furiously, scratching at your body. Once you got over the freakiness, it became almost...erotic. There was certainly a sense of the &lt;i&gt;hugeness&lt;/i&gt; of Mother Nature. To experience this on acid would be node-worthy I think, adding to the sense of irrevocable Fate. Imagine an exploding car igniting a thousand square acres of &lt;b&gt;locusts&lt;/b&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;wharfinger:&lt;/b&gt; You're out [thefez|fez]-huntin' when the car crash happens, and we 
don't want to immolate you, too. And I like Brawl in the rain at the end, not locusts. OTOH I'm 
assuming your bit at the end will describe the [thefez|fez]-hunt: Fighting through the locusts 
to find your quarry... &lt;strong&gt;Yeah!&lt;/strong&gt; The locusts are beautiful for that. Also, the 
locusts would explain why you can't catch somebody who's on foot and burdened with a 
captive. I'm still seeing Brawl in the rain, though. How long must the locust storm last? &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;riverrun:&lt;/b&gt; Well, so long as it's dramatically convenient. I only put the car in there cause that'd be one HELL of a big explosion and I've NEVER seen it before. Also it's the sort of weird local detail that adds verisimilitude. No reasons the locusts can't &lt;i&gt;move&lt;/i&gt; if you think the explosion's worth the trouble. Rain is fine for the car too, obviously.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/td&gt;
	&lt;td&gt;[Lord Brawl]&lt;br&gt;
&lt;i&gt;[Brawl's Delirium] &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;

&lt;tr bgcolor=&quot;#f8f8f8&quot; valign=&quot;top&quot;&gt;
	&lt;td align=&quot;right&quot;&gt;Submit at 10:50 pm&lt;/td&gt;
	&lt;td&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;[Lord Brawl], crazed by grief, kills [dem bones] with a keepsake machete that 
	[riverrun] brought back from Vietnam. It might be overdoing it to pattern this on 
	the scene in &lt;i&gt;Apocalypse Now&lt;/i&gt; where Martin Sheen kills Brando.
	&lt;/p&gt; 
	&lt;p&gt;[dem bones] dies in [ailie]'s arms. [Lord Brawl|Brawl] comes to his senses and 
	staggers out into the rain, gouging his own eyes out as he goes. That's a touchy 
	one: He's gotta gouge 'em out while in view of the narrator, but he still has to 
	be able to find the door. Maybe we should leave the eye-gouging offstage, and not 
	reveal it until the next and last writeup. Then again, he can grope for the 
	doorway, leaving bloody handprints on the wall... Whatever's Right. 
	&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/td&gt;
	&lt;td&gt;[ailie]&lt;br&gt;
&lt;i&gt;[E2 Gods Summit 2001: 10:30pm - ailie]&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;

&lt;tr bgcolor=&quot;#f8f8f8&quot; valign=&quot;top&quot;&gt;
	&lt;td align=&quot;right&quot;&gt;Submit at 11:10 pm&lt;/td&gt;
	&lt;td&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;[riverrun] returns empty-handed from pursuit of [thefez], sees [Lord Brawl]
	on driveway. Flames begin to emerge from kitchen. He goes into the house to add a 
	last writeup. Final image is [Lord Brawl|Brawl], eyeless and blood-boltered, 
	kneeling silently in the rain. I'd really like to see &quot;blood-boltered&quot; used in there 
	somewhere, since this winds up so much like a revenge tragedy. &lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/td&gt;
	&lt;td&gt;[riverrun]
&lt;i&gt;[E2 God Summit 2001 : 11 P.M. riverrun]&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;

&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
[E2 Gods Summit 2001 : Local Background]&lt;br&gt;
[the little death and Veronica Lake] is a first allusion to NW Illinois. No references to this WU, please--riverrun&lt;br&gt;
[e2 Gods Summit 8:20 p.m.] by [Jinmyo]&lt;br&gt;
[E2 God Summit 2001: 9:30 pm] by [knifegirl]&lt;br&gt;
[Brawl's Delirium] 10:20 pm&lt;br&gt;
[E2 Gods Summit 2001: 10:30pm - ailie]&lt;br&gt;
[E2 God Summit 2001 : 11 P.M. riverrun]&lt;br&gt;
[General Noodlings by Jet-Poop]&lt;BR&gt;
[noder get-together: dannye]&lt;BR&gt;
[The Arrival and the Reunion] - [dem bones]&lt;br&gt;

&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
</doctext>
  <node_id>1076663</node_id>
  <title>E2 God Summit 2001 timeline</title>
</node>
