<node>
  <doctext>&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;E2 Changes: Short Version&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fundamentally, the goal here is to switch E2 over from the 'publish it all, let the gods sort it out' to 'publish it and keep it because it's good.'&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Simple, right?  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Read it all two or three times before msg'ing me with all the questions, comments, warnings and threats or start a new discussion if you want to comment/talk it out.  I wasn't planning on putting this up for discussion for several more months.  I'll do it now as long as one thing is clear:  Jay and I aren't done thinking about this and the code isn't even close to ready.  These changes will coincide with some major hardware changes and the introduction of the newest version of our ecode (what C2 is running on).  The soonest we can hope for is Spring of next year.  You know how that goes, so it'll probably be later.  Jay and nate are both extremely busy with their dayjobs now, too.  [dem bones|I'm] totally shiftless but all I'm good for is writing down what I want.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, here's a thumbnail sketch of the Big Changes.  These are the broad strokes.  You'll see some chinks in the armor - we've got many of them solved and many we're still thinking on.  Overall this will be a vastly more professional website while simultaneously improving community and reducing editorial/user stress.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I swear to God.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Community Improvements&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt; &lt;b&gt;Editorial Group Changes&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt; The content editor and 'gods' group will be melted into one large group called (probably) '&lt;em&gt;publishers&lt;/em&gt;.'  

&lt;li&gt; Punitive tools will be removed.  The publisher group will have full permissions &lt;em&gt;only on the writeups they've published&lt;/em&gt;.  Publishers will no longer be focusing on roaming the database or ENN for weaknesses, but adding always to E2's strengths but publishing quality work from the submissions page.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt; Editors will be encouraged to work mainly in their specific areas of expertise for publishing purposes.  Informally.  I see it this way:  a 'choose your publisher' page listing the user's choices and their individual areas of expertise.  A user will probably gravitate towards an editor with similar interests.  &lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt; EDB will be extinct.  We'll still have a way to block a troll from distracting the entire chatroom but it'll be 'silent' and a msg will be sent to the user explaining his/her error(s).  The time the user is chatless can be assigned when the msg is written.  Only a very small group will have access to this tool, it's to be used only in &lt;em&gt;extreme&lt;/em&gt; situations.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt; A very small group consisting of coders and bones will be left as an 'admin' group ('gods' as a term has got to go) and a second and very small group will be handling the larger tasks of project deletions or other work that requires access to admin tools.  The members of the group left with deletions powers will always do their work with their name signed.  It won't be a hunt and kill group so much as a janitorial team.  As for the weak writeups we've still got in the database, we'll be handling those when users sign up with 'publishers' (and get an audit) or/and with good old E2 Nuke Requests.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;li&gt; &lt;b&gt;New 'personal' nodetype&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt; In place as a level power, on the higher end.  
&lt;li&gt; Writeups in these nodes only be visible to users who've logged in.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Not votable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Won't create softlinks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; No editorial standard for content - like daylogs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; These nodes can be private or public or available only to users the author has specified.  
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;li&gt; &lt;b&gt;Daylogs and dreamlogs:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Can be C!d.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; No longer votable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; No longer &quot;count&quot; towards user levels.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Still appear on the public server.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;li&gt; &lt;b&gt;Experience System:&lt;/b&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Professor Pi is still looking at this.  The idea is the new xp/level system will be much simplified with only four or five levels.  The goal of this sytem is simple:  to reward a user who has clearly shown they understand how the site works.  Once they're past this 'newbie' status we'd like to get them home node pics and votes/C!s relatively quickly.  A few toys in the higher brackets but levels 2-3 will have all the basic perks E2 has to offer.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Database Quality Improvements&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt; &lt;b&gt;Improved User Control of Nodes:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Users will be able to 'title' their individual daylog entries, day/dreamlogs will be searchable by both this title and the date.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Users will be able to delete their own writeups&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;li&gt; &lt;b&gt;Publishing System Changes:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt; No more directly-posted public writeups, except for day/dreamlogs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Noders will submit writeups to a editor-viewable-only &quot;Publish&quot; page.  It will be identical to [ENN].  This will be the submissions bin from the userbase.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Editors will evaluate each and every writeup for publication.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Users can request that specific editors look at their work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Editors work with authors to improve writeups denied immediate publication.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Editors will be associated with writeups they approve for publishing, and will field all concerns about those writeup for the authors &lt;em&gt;forever&lt;/em&gt; (or until they sign them over to another publisher)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Authors need only deal with one editor to have their writeups published&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;li&gt; &lt;b&gt;Copyright Stance Changes:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[E2 Copyright Changes] about covers it.  
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</doctext>
  <node_id>1469222</node_id>
  <title>E2 Mission Statement</title>
  <type_nodetype>13</type_nodetype>
</node>
