<node>
  <type_nodetype>13</type_nodetype>
  <doctext>&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Idea:&lt;/b&gt;  Gods begin to offer quests individually.  I've been going over
[Mythos] and trying to fill in some blanks and I realize, again, that there are
a fucking lot of blanks.  What I've been needing is a posse - a group of different
users working towards a common goal.  More to the point a group dedicated to a 
common effort with a &lt;i&gt;leader&lt;/i&gt; - somebody overseeing the project and 
making sure it all gets done and gets done right.  So that's what we'll do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Offering these quests will be voluntary on your part and the topics will be 
up to you.  I'd suggest taking suggestions for topics in the c-box from time
to time and then putting together your Quest.  The 'rules' of each quest is up to the individual god.  A central document 
(this one) would be manually edited/updated as to what gods are currently
running quests.  Maybe N-Wing or JayBonci could make the document a bit fancier 
and give us fields to update or whatever.  Often, I'd imagine, in setting up
your quest you could begin by putting together a 'metanode' on the subject
with a bunch of hard linked terms/ideas leading to empty nodeshells.  Take a 
look at '[Greek and Roman Mythology]' ... now pretend that all of the hard links
lead nowhere.  That would be an excellent beginning for your Quest.  From that
node you could outline exactly what you need done, who is working on which, what
your offering in return and when the quest will be finished.  You could allow
users to add temporary writeups ala E2 Mentoring Sign-Up and simply place
the links that they've been assigned in their writeups - have them make a note
when they're finished, etc.  When the Quest is finished
simply remove all of your temporal instructions and you've got a beautiful 
project and a bunch of motivated users.  All this document would need to do
is list which gods are offering which quests - the rest could be at your
'metanode'.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;None of this addresses the problem of evaluating these quest entries - which
was the major problem with the previous quests.  This will break up the size of
them, however, and since it's voluntary you can run them when you've got the time
or inclination.  You could also assign &lt;i&gt;all of this&lt;/i&gt; to any user if you 
trust their judgement.  When the user is finished evaluating all the writeups
for the quest he/she simply gives you a list of users to superbless X.  It
would take you ten minutes on the outside.  (This would be an excellent way to
evaluate potential editorial staff)  We can also provide C!s and 
'golden trinkets' as godly boons.  If we do need help evaluating the results
of a quest we could turn to a c_e or even draft other users into the effort - 
using [superbless] to pay the bills.  XP is currency and there's been no 
serious inflation - use it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Quest Example:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Quest title:&lt;/b&gt;  [Greek and Roman Mythology]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Mission:&lt;/b&gt;  To complete E2's entries for all cyclopes, fates, graces,
nymphs and titans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Requirements:&lt;/b&gt;  All writeups must be original work by submitter.
Please use at least three seperate sources (we could give four or five url's,
perhaps, that we've found helpful on the subject) and provide a phonetic
spelling of the creatures name.  Each writeup should include a brief geneology 
as well as quotes featuring the subject in the Odyssey, Illiad and/or Theogeny.
(We could specify a minimum number of soft links.  We could also have the 
soft linking / firm linking done by time the user gets there.  Have a nice, neat
project just waiting for text to be dropped in.)  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Reward:&lt;/b&gt;  A C! from me for each entry, a blessing for every two writeups
you complete toward this project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Protocol:&lt;/b&gt;  Add a writeup below describing how many writeups you'd
like to tackle.  I'll edit your writeup to list the links you're assigned and 
then msg you.  When you're finished make a note in your writeup.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A second type of quest could include &lt;b&gt;consolidation&lt;/b&gt; - we gather a list of nodes
which have five or six very short writeups and offer great rewards to volunteers
willing to assimilate several or all the writeups then go further and really cover
the topic.  I'm sure you see these nodes as often as I do - each individual writeup
should die but none of them offer enough substance alone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Comments:&lt;/b&gt;










&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
</doctext>
  <node_id>1163424</node_id>
  <title>E2 Quests superdoc</title>
</node>
