<node>
  <title>Experience Points</title>
  <type_nodetype>13</type_nodetype>
  <doctext>Voting...is installed!  What does this mean?  How does it apply to you?  How does it work?  What's my middle name?  All of this and more...&lt;p&gt;
First of all, to vote on any given [writeup] simply click on the + or - icons to the left of the [timestamp].  You can click + or - on each writeup of a node and vote on all them at once by then clicking the [VOTE] button located below the last writeup and before the [soft-link] box.
Use these votes wisely!  As opposed to the [electoral college|United States version] your votes count!  When a writeup gets five negative votes it will be kicked to a page that some editors will be perusing regularly, thus risking deletion by the staff.  As you can see below having your writeup deleted is [a bad thing].  It will hurt your &quot;experience points&quot; and negatively effect your level.
Conversely, if your writeups are voted + by your fellow users you will gain experience points.  Details are below, in a rough-sketch of our devious little plan.
You will receive a certain number of votes per 24 hour day, the higher your level the more votes you receive.  Each time you use all of your votes in a given day you will receive an experience point bonus.
&lt;p&gt;
(my middle name is, incidentally, [William]...I was named after my grandfather)
&lt;p&gt;
The stuff below is still in the &quot;maybe&quot; stages.  We sketched it out after Nate had finished a long run of [Everquest].  The titles will almost certainly change...[Suggest Level Titles For Everythingians] here!...and the XPs and number of votes may change as well.

&lt;p&gt;
As you can see, with each [level] gained a new &quot;[power]&quot; is awarded.  We would like you to eventually have your own versions of Everything that you can fool around with, probably with a gateway from your home node.  Image libraries, (no [porn], sorry) and the ability to [bless]/[curse] (hand out XP or take it away...a few points each day).  It's gonna be [cool].  Comments?  Ideas?  Scornful accusations?  Let us know what you think [Comments on Everything Voting|here].
&lt;p&gt;
One will be a webmail server for Everything.  This will allow you to send/receive email to people's home nodes (mail can only be viewed by them).  &lt;b&gt; You've got nodes!&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
The &quot;percentage chances&quot; are another way to encourage interaction with the Everything system:  Every time you vote or get voted on there is a percentage chance that your XP will increase.  (decrease if you get voted negatively)
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;table width=100% border=1&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;th&gt;Level&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th&gt;XP&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th&gt;Votes/Bookmarks&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th&gt;Title&lt;/th&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;

[%
my $TITLES = getVars(getNode('level titles', 'setting'));
my $VOTES = getVars(getNode('level votes', 'setting'));
my $EXP = getVars(getNode('level experience', 'setting'));

my $max = 10;
my $str;

for (my $i = 1; $i &lt;= 10; $i++) {
  $str.=&quot;&lt;TR&gt;&lt;TD&gt;$i&lt;/TD&gt;&lt;TD&gt;$$EXP{$i}&lt;/TD&gt;&lt;TD&gt;$$VOTES{$i}&lt;/TD&gt;&lt;TD&gt;$$TITLES{$i}&lt;/TD&gt;&lt;/TR&gt;&quot;;
}

$str;
%]


&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;p align=center&gt;
Other ways to alter [XP]:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
+10 points if a writeup is &quot;[Page of Cool|cooled]&quot;&lt;br&gt;
-5 if a writeup is &quot;[nuked]&quot;&lt;br&gt;
20% chance of +1 every time you [vote]
&lt;br&gt;
33% chance of +1/-1 if your writeup is voted +/-&lt;br&gt;
+1/2 number of votes cast if all votes are cast on any given day
&lt;br&gt;
Other Ideas:&lt;br&gt;
[T-Shirts]/[Calendar]s awarded if you make [M-Noder] status...T-shirts/calendars designed by high-level noders
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</doctext>
  <node_id>434836</node_id>
</node>
