<node>
  <doctext>This is one side of a conversation that [Excalibre] had with [RangyJoeyHondo] earlier tonight, 15 February 2006:
&lt;p&gt;
2006.02.16 at 03:20 RangyJoeyHondo says OK. Thanks for your message, let me consider the best way to move forward nd get back to you in the next half an hour. &lt;br /&gt;
(r)     2006.02.16 at 03:30    RangyJoeyHondo says Hey, I think it's actually kind of cool. I've a few frustrations with a couple of admins here, but you and I have never really made sense to each other so I'm happy to ask you to admin my request hopefully it works for both of us. Please delete this &lt;br /&gt;
(r)     2006.02.16 at 03:30    RangyJoeyHondo says account. If for some reason you cannot, please at least delete all the write ups in ths account. As a result of your editory work, and good for you, please also delete the account of JohnnyGoodyear who is, as you well know, my progenitor. If, as a CE, &lt;br /&gt;
(r)     2006.02.16 at 03:30    RangyJoeyHondo says you cannot delete this and Johnny's account, please contact an admin who has that power. If that admin questions my sincerity, please direct them to this message and the fact that you suck and it's not even half past ten. If you are concerned about this &lt;br /&gt;
(r)     2006.02.16 at 03:30    RangyJoeyHondo says in any way, please direct your concerns to gorgonzola or wertperch who already kinda blew the fun and contribution I ws making here and thus you will find friends of a similar stripe. Thanks. &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
(r)     2006.02.16 at 03:47    RangyJoeyHondo says /msg Excalibre Nah....it was fun while it lasted, take this as one of your rites of passage. Just delete all of me and Johnny too, who's better than you to do that. Just the nature of online stuff. Thanks for the effort. If you have trouble with account &lt;br /&gt;
(r)     2006.02.16 at 03:47    RangyJoeyHondo says deletion, wertperch would be my preference, he would - like yourself - be the perfect God to help you rid yourself of this incarnation . &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
(r)     2006.02.16 at 03:50    RangyJoeyHondo says I will not be back in this incarnation or in Johnny's, although Johnny is publishing again in the real world, so take this as my request that you fulfill my copyright requirements and remove my content from your site. I use the word 'yours' as a result as &lt;br /&gt;
(r)     2006.02.16 at 03:50    RangyJoeyHondo says you being listed an editor. Thank you. &lt;br /&gt;
(r)     2006.02.16 at 03:51    RangyJoeyHondo says Dolt. I am johnnygoodyear. Check your node notes editor. Now deliver. &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
(r)     2006.02.16 at 03:54    RangyJoeyHondo says For legal purposes, I have copied this conversation with you and I expect you and your online publishing management to comply with my deletion request within good time. Should you not do so, I will look to you first, and then your management as my legal &lt;br /&gt;
(r)     2006.02.16 at 03:54    RangyJoeyHondo says counsel suggests.     


&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
Excalibre's messages to me were:
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
(r) 2006-02-15@20:42 (10.1 min) Excalibre says Oh dear, have you spoken with RangyJoeyHondo? Because your name came up. I just killed a broken nodes request by him and recommended he take it up with the user himself. (And I'm pretty sure I was nice about it!) And he just asked me to kill all his &lt;br /&gt;
(r) 2006-02-15@20:42 (10.1 min) Excalibre says writeups and his account. And those of JohnnyGoodyear. I'm confused. I'm hoping I didn't just somehow inadvertently fuck up. &lt;br /&gt;
(r) 2006-02-15@20:51 (10.1 min) Excalibre says Wait, what the fuck is going on? Should I actually delete his writeups? Is he actually JohnnyGoodyear?
(r) 2006-02-15@20:55 (10.1 min) Excalibre says What the fuck happened then? He goes from editor to stomping off? What's wrong with him? &lt;br /&gt;
(r) 2006-02-15@20:59 (10.1 min) Excalibre says I haven't been copying my outgoing messages, but I'll email you a copy of his incomings (since he was rather prolix and somewhat hard to understand.) I think he's drunk; he's seriously having a hard time writing even comprehensibly here, which is why I &lt;br /&gt;
(r) 2006-02-15@20:59 (10.1 min) Excalibre says find it hard to believe he's JohnnyGoodyear. &lt;br /&gt;
(r) 2006-02-15@21:10 (10.1 min) Excalibre says Personally, I have to say that I'd get a few shivers of naughty delight klaprothing each of JohnnyGoodyear's works . . .

&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
[Lord Brawl] replies: Deleting JG's stuff with no notice and no public say-so from him, especially in advance of any comment dann might eventually choose to make on the JG admin situation, would be setting off a powderkeg among his clique of fans. I do not want to deal with the fallout. I would be happy to contact JG or have dann do it to verify this request before we proceed.
&lt;/p&gt;</doctext>
  <node_id>1786926</node_id>
  <type_nodetype>13</type_nodetype>
  <title>Farewell JohnnyGoodyear?</title>
</node>
