<node>
  <doctext>&lt;p&gt;Once upon a time, when I was a wee child in grade school, I knew a girl named Daisy. Now Daisy was a pretty girl, and she had a lot of girlfriends, but we were very young and boys that age don't like girls too much, on account of Cooties and such. So the girls would play together and the boys would play together, and once in a while they would tease each other, the way children are wont to do.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One day this boy named Johnny was on the playground, and he started teasing the girls and calling them names. Johnny was a bit slow, with a loud mouth and a simpleton's laugh, and when he would tease them and call them smelly, the girls would laugh and make fun of Johnny. All except for Daisy. Daisy didn't like being teased, not one bit. She didn't care that Johnny was stupid, she wanted to give him a piece of her mind. So she started arguing with Johnny, trying to shout him down and tell him off in front of all the other kids on the playground. Johnny, being thick-headed, would just yell back at her, not listening to a word. Things escallated until a teacher had to separate them. She pulled Daisy aside and asked her to please play nicely, that Johnny wasn't like the other kids, and to take that into consideration. But Daisy was hot and bothered, and started to tell the teacher all the things she was trying to tell Johnny. The teacher asked again for her to settle down, to please play nicely, but Daisy just kept trying to make her case. Finally, when she realized that even the teacher wasn't interested in what she had to say, she stormed off in a fit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The next day on the playground, when Daisy came out to recess and saw Johnny playing marbles in the sand with the other boys, she walked up to him and resumed her argument. Everyone just kind of blinked in astonishment, but Johnny wasn't going to be yelled at for something that happened yesterday and which he had half-forgotten. So he began taunting Daisy again and calling her names. This made Daisy even angrier, and soon the teacher showed up again to separate the two children. Again she asked Daisy in a pleasant voice to please be civil and play nicely with the other children. Daisy accused the teacher of taking sides, of interfering in her business, of smoking in the teacher's lounge, and used a few words that only adults are allowed to use. Then she stormed off again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the following day when time came for recess again, Daisy showed up on the playground ready for a fight. But Johnny was home sick from school that day, and Daisy had no outlet to vent. She was mad because her parents were getting a divorce, and because they were making her go live with her grandmother, and because her dog had puppies and her mom made her give them all away to the animal shelter. She needed someone to pummel on to release all the frustrations she had from her miserable life. But her enemy wasn't around, so she just had to stew in her bitterness and resentment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This cycle continued on the playground for several more days, until eventually, all the other kids began to notice that Daisy was perpetually mad at Johnny. While few of the other kids really liked Johnny that much, none of us actually hated him like Daisy seemed to. The other teachers had noticed this too, and every day that Johnny and Daisy were both together on the playground, one of them had to ask Daisy to calm down and play nicely. They talked to Johnny too, but Johnny just claimed that he was being bullied, and the teachers more or less agreed that this was true, but asked Johnny to please not provoke Daisy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, after days and days of this disruptive behavior, one day at recess when Daisy started in on Johnny, the teacher took Daisy up by the arm and removed her from the playground. She was placed in a nearby classroom where she could see the other children playing, but could not participate herself. The teacher said, &quot;I've asked you again and again and again to please play nicely, to behave yourself, to stop attacking Johnny, but you refuse to listen. You will sit here in TIME OUT and think about the playground rules.&quot; Daisy SCREAMED at the TOP of her LUNGS that it wasn't FAIR. But the teacher was done asking nicely.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We never saw Daisy on the playground again after that. I heard that she went home and told her grandma that the teachers weren't fair, and that the kids on the playground weren't fair, and that the principal was a &quot;poop head&quot; (although she used a bad word instead of poop). I hear she decided to go to a different school from that point on, where a lot of other kids who had discipline problems ended up. But I don't really know much about that school.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As for Johnny, he went on to become a jock in high school, and then he joined the Marines or something and got killed by friendly fire one night while he was burning a village full of women and children in some Third World country. Like I said, he was kind of slow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hey, thanks Kurt! I knew you'd like my little story. It's full of analogies because it's a composite - not really about any one specific set of circumstances between any specific group of people, but typical of a scenario that has been played out again and again over the years in the E2 chatterbox. It's not a Position Statement. It wasn't written by the E2 administration as an Official Response, it's just something I did myself. It's not even really a parable either - I'm glad you picked up on that. And since I wrote it out in five minutes and didn't revise a single thing before I posted it, maybe it's not the best work I've ever done either, but I appreciate your feedback.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You've always shown a great deal of respect for me as a person, and never tried to humiliate me in public for a cheap laugh or anything. You're one of my role models, actually. Being called names by you is really flattering! But I better stop before I start gushing. Someone might mistake my attempt at politeness for pretentiousness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'd just like to add that you are correct in observing that my narrative advocates only one side of the story. I was not involved directly in any communication between jasstrong/jasmine and bones, or any other party, in this particular dramatic episode of the soap opera we call Everything2. My story comes only from what I read in the chatterbox and what is said about it amongst the staff. It's my own interpretation of events as an impartial bystander... and I do mean impartial, as like you, I have nothing personally invested in this whatsoever. I only wrote this so that people like [RoguePoet] would have another perspective on events like this, without involving specific grievances (since everyone has something different to bitch about).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They say there's three sides to every story: yours, mine, and the truth. My story wasn't a tale of how E2 is managed (or mismanaged, as you elaborate on at length). It's a story of how human beings can become so focused on their own emotions and worldview that they become convinced that they possess the only voice of reason. It's a tale of what happens when people refuse to take responsibility for their own words and actions, and how they may disrupt a public forum or agitate those whose role is maintaining civil discourse. It's about taking a private argument and dragging it out into the open again and again where nobody wants to see it, and the fallout of ignoring the assholes in charge (and make no mistake - the people in charge anywhere and everywhere are always assholes). It's a story torn from every single kindergarten playground everywhere, because it's all about what happens when people act like selfish children instead of adults.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Can't we all just... get along?&lt;/em&gt; As this story represents, for some people at least, the answer is definitely &lt;em&gt;no.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</doctext>
  <node_id>1539013</node_id>
  <type_nodetype>13</type_nodetype>
  <title>jasresponse</title>
</node>
