<node>
  <doctext>[Jinmyo] sez: Received this evening, private stuff deleted.&lt;p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;

Jin-chan,&lt;p&gt;

Is this thing on? (taps computer) I hope that this actually works. It is a computer in the office of one of our sub-temples in Osaka, Sogo-ji. But there are wires everywhere and the modem seems to be 2800 baud. I think this is bad.&lt;p&gt;

I am so sorry I have been out of contact, but following Hanamatsuri there have been so many festivals, so many people, and so much to do. The succession issues are very gnarly. Not in a surfer-guy American sense but in the sense of entangled. Haha. I should have just written &quot;entangled&quot; but I wanted to have my little joke and it cost me about five minutes to type it and it wasn't funny at all, really.&lt;p&gt;

.....&lt;p&gt;

There are certainly a great many emails from you I should read and I will. But I thought I should send this now, while I can. I also have received bounced emails sent to Michelle at the e2 address. I think this does not work so well. And I need to reply to [dannye]'s very kind letter. Please pass on my fondest greetings to these friends and all of my other friends on e2.&lt;p&gt;

Can I ask you to login as &quot;me&quot; and discard the messages that have accrued? Please, as before, copy those I need to see into an email. Ah, sorry. I asked if I could ask you and I asked you.&lt;p&gt;

.....&lt;p&gt;

It is very humid and hot. But the windbell sounds cool. Silly, I know.&lt;p&gt;

.....&lt;p&gt;
Again, please send my greetings, especially to my dear friend [wharfinger]. I hope that he and all of you are well. Please make a superdoc of the relevant parts of this letter.
</doctext>
  <createtime>2001-06-27 23:35:30</createtime>
  <totalvotes>0</totalvotes>
  <node_id>1091242</node_id>
  <edittime>0000-00-00 00:00:00</edittime>
  <type_nodetype>13</type_nodetype>
  <document_id>1091242</document_id>
  <author_user>113</author_user>
  <title>Jun 27, 2001 email from sensei</title>
</node>
