<node>
  <doctext>CLIENT SERVER:


Commonly written client/server. The concept behind this system design architecture, is that the task at hand can be
  divided into a client part and a server part.

  The client part sends requests to the server part: the server part tries to satisfy them.
  Usually the client handles the user interface, that's to say, the typical user of the system uses the client, while the server
  handles the data storage and computation.

  Examples: 

    1.airline reservation systems (like SABRE). You have a million terminals that operators use to reserve and buy seats
      on planes. The actual reservation and ticketing data is stored on a big computer somewhere, called the server. 
    2.The WWW. A client program (normally called a browser) sends requests to a server: the requests are coded in
      HTTP, and the server sends back text and images. 
    3.Checkout systems in supermarkets: each cashier mans a client, and a central inventory and accounting system
      receives the transaction information and updates the inventory and the books. 
    4.A MOO: the central server maintains reality consistent, while the clients modify bits of the world and interact with it. 

  A client server system is well suited to situations where you want to centralize data (either because it is very expensive or
  because it has to be consistent) or where you have a very expensive resource that has to be shared (like a very big iron).
  Client server systems are inherently asymmetric, that's to say that there is a different load on the server than on the client
  (that is why usually a server is a big system).
  There can be also asymmetries in communications traffic. For example, Web network traffic is highly asymmetrical,
  because for every tiny (1 Kilobyte) client request there is a usually larger server answer.

  Opposed to peer to peer, where the participating entities are on the same level (a good example of this is Windows 98 file
  sharing)




IMAGING:




  The capture, storage, manipulation and display of images are the main processes in imaging. 

  The capture of the images used: 

      visible light the most common 
      invisible light such as infrared, ultraviolet and x-rays 
      ultrasound such as in ultrasound scanning 
      magnetism such as in magnetic resonance imaging 
      radar such as in navigation and satellite imaging 

  The storage of the images used: 

      photographic film used to be most common 
      digital media are now preferred due to ease of manipulation 

  The manipulation of the images used: 

      optical techniques using film negatives and enlargers 
      computer imaging / digital imaging manipulations are now more common due to its flexibility and versatility 

  The display of the images used: 

      photographic papers 
      colour printers such as ink jet, solid wax, dye sublimation and colour photocopy 
      computer displays such as CRT and LCD 
      false colours where the colours used are not the actual colors such as satellite imaging using infra red, red and green
      frequency band for red, green and blue colours 



METADATA



Metadata is information that tells you about other information. For example, the table of contents in a book tells you what
  is in the book, how it's organized, and where each part begins. The index in the back of the book also describes what's in
  the book, but in a different way. 

  On a higher level, the card catalog (or its online equivalent) at your local public library is another example. It keeps track of
  information about all the books in the library: who the author is, what the title is, what subjects it addresses, when it was
  published, how many pages are in it, and what books are related to other books. There's more metadata in the library, too:
  look at the signs that show you which part of the library the books are in. Information about where different kinds of
  information are: that's metadata. 

  On a web page, the only metadata is often just a title. In other cases, there's also a description and a list of keywords to
  help you find the page in a search engine. On a well-designed site, every page will also have some sort of navigation tool
  that puts it into context as part of the site. 

  And on this writeup, the metadata is at the top: it shows that Sylvar wrote it, that this writeup is about a thing, and when it
  was written. If you have voted on the writeup, it will show you its reputation. If someone has chinged it, then you will see
  that information as well. All of this is metadata that describes this writeup. 

  What's the fuss about metadata, then, if it's already been a normal part of life for such a long time? When there's a huge
  amount of information to keep track of, such as on the Internet, you'd be lost without some sort of metadata. Can you
  imagine trying to find a book in the library with a keyword search? &quot;I'm looking for all books that have the words 'science',
  'religion' and 'evolution' anywhere in the book.&quot; Good luck, pal.



FIREWALL:


A fire wall monitors the traffic on a network or computer. When it is part of a network it is usually a seperate computer
  which all communications to outside the network must pass. Its purpose is to block certain kinds of communications. For
  example, it could be set to block e-mail. It can also stop malicious people trying to break into the network.



EMAIL:

A method for a person to send a document across the internet or an intranet to another person. Email is essentially a text
  transfer system, but like in all such systems, images and other forms of data can be encoded in such a way that they can be
  sent via email and extracted again by the recipient.


INTERNET:




  The mother of all networks. First incarnated beginning in 1969 as the ARPANET, a U.S. Department of Defense research
  testbed. Though it has been widely believed that the goal was to develop a network architecture for military
  command-and-control that could survive disruptions up to and including nuclear war, this is a myth; in fact, ARPANET
  was conceived from the start as a way to get most economical use out of then-scarce large-computer resources. 

  As originally imagined, ARPANET's major use would have been to support what is now called remote login and more
  sophisticated forms of distributed computing, but the infant technology of electronic mail quickly grew to dominate actual
  usage. Universities, research labs and defense contractors early discovered the Internet's potential as a medium of
  communication between humans and linked up in steadily increasing numbers, connecting together a quirky mix of
  academics, techies, hippies, SF fans, hackers, and anarchists. The roots of this lexicon lie in those early years. 

  Over the next quarter-century the Internet evolved in many ways. The typical machine/OS combination moved from DEC
  PDP-10s and PDP-20s, running TOPS-10 and TOPS-20, to PDP-11s and VAXes and Suns running Unix, and in the
  1990s to Unix on Intel microcomputers. The Internet's protocols grew more capable, most notably in the move from
  NCP/IP to TCP/IP in 1982 and the implementation of Domain Name Service in 1983. It was around this time that people
  began referring to the collection of interconnected networks with ARPANET at its core as &quot;the Internet&quot;. 

  The ARPANET had a fairly strict set of participation guidelines - connected institutions had to be involved with a
  DOD-related research project. By the mid-80s, many of the organizations clamoring to join didn't fit this profile. In 1986,
  the National Science Foundation built NSFnet to open up access to its five regional supercomputing centers; NSFnet
  became the backbone of the Internet, replacing the original ARPANET pipes (which were formally shut down in 1990).
  Between 1990 and late 1994 the pieces of NSFnet were sold to major telecommunications companies until the Internet
  backbone had gone completely commercial. 

  That year, 1994, was also the year the mainstream culture discovered the Internet. Once again, the killer app was not the
  anticipated one - rather, what caught the public imagination was the hypertext and multimedia features of the World Wide
  Web. Subsequently the Internet has seen off its only serious challenger (the OSI protocol stack favored by European
  telecom monopolies) and is in the process of absorbing into itself many of the proprietary networks built during the second
  wave of wide-area networking after 1980. It is now (1996) a commonplace even in mainstream media to predict that a
  globally-extended Internet will become the key unifying communications technology of the next century. See also the
  network and Internet address.


WORLD WIDE WEB:


A worldwide collection of hyperlinked text, images, and other types of computerized data. 

  The web is a client-server system in which there are many servers all over the internet, which provide documents to the
  clients, web browsers which users use to access the web. 

  The fundamental type of document is a text file written in HTML (Hyper Text Markup Language). HTML is a markup
  language in which the text is interspersed with symbolic codes that represent formatting, document structure, and
  hyperlinks. These documents are normally accessed by a system called HTTP (Hyper Text Transfer Protocol), which is
  somewhat similar to FTP in that a client asks a server for one or more documents, and the server sends them, or gives an
  error if it is unable to. 

  Hyperlinks are simply references to other documents in the web. These references have a common form, called a URL
  (Uniform Resource Locator), which is designed to make it possible to reference any network-accessible document,
  including those accessible by methods other than HTTP. URLs can specify older methods of accessing documents (such
  as FTP) which predate the web, and are extensible to handle access methods not yet dreamed of. 

  Thus, the web can be thought of as encompassing essentially all forms of communication over the internet. Though most of
  the networking not based on HTML documents transported over HTTP are often not considered to be part of the web,
  most of them can be accessed from the web.



APPLICATION:


an application is a piece of software that is designed to meet a specific set of problems on a computer.
  if you want to write and edit text, you use a word processing application, or if you want to create or edit images, you use
  an image editing application.


GUI  (Graphical User Interface)


When a person wants to use the computer, they have to somehow interact with it, or use it (hence the term, &quot;user&quot;, which
  refers to the person using the computer). A computer's interface is the means by which a user tells the computer what to
  do. Of course, a person doesn't only interact with computers, they also &quot;interface&quot; with other tools and machines. For
  example, the interface of a stove is the buttons/knobs used to control the temperature. Stoves have a fairly simple interface,
  just a few controls, because they can do only one thing. Computers are more advanced, so they usually have more flexible
  means by the user can communicate with it. 

  There are few computers that lack a keyboard, which is an input device, like the controls on a stove. On older (personal)
  computers, the only way for the user to use the computer was through typing commands. The screen they looked at only
  showed letters and symbols. (That way of using the computer is called a character user interface or command line
  interface.) A major problem with this method is that new users wouldn't be able to use the computer unless they already
  knew what to do. However, with the advent of more powerful computers, the computer can display pictures, or graphics
  in addition to text. The user can also use something like a mouse or trackball to move a little picture on-screen (usually in
  the shape of an arrow) called a cursor. 

  There are several advantages of a graphical interface over a character interface:

    1.Assuming the user has some basic computer skills (like moving the cursor on the screen using the mouse), they can
      explore the environment on their own. 
    2.The user can see what things they can do, and choose one. This way, they don't have to know what is possible to
      do and how to do it before they start. 
    3.Pictures are easier to comprehend and take less time to process than reading paragraphs of text. 
    4.Multiple things can be done at once. If the screen is large enough, the user can work on several things at once, and
      switch between them at will. 

  A graphical user interface, or GUI, is simply a method of interacting with a computer that uses pictures and text instead
  of just text. A well-made GUI can make it easy for a new user to start using the computer to complete a task, and learn
  how to do new things on it. 



INTERFACE:


A point or means of interaction between two or more systems, components of a computer system, or the system and the
  user.










</doctext>
  <core>0</core>
  <reputation>0</reputation>
  <lockedby_user>0</lockedby_user>
  <createtime>2000-05-08 19:14:08</createtime>
  <locktime>0000-00-00 00:00:00</locktime>
  <totalvotes>0</totalvotes>
  <hits>7</hits>
  <node_id>536238</node_id>
  <edittime>0000-00-00 00:00:00</edittime>
  <type_nodetype>13</type_nodetype>
  <document_id>536238</document_id>
  <author_user>315</author_user>
  <package>0</package>
  <title>mom's homework</title>
</node>
