<node>
  <type_nodetype>13</type_nodetype>
  <doctext>Enjoy yourself.  This is utmost in importance.
*
I'm sure you heard the story of the man who becomes rich because he gains a friend.  This probably illustrates a fundamental human point:  the only thing that &quot;we&quot; ever really have is people. This is also the reason I decided to call myself a Christian again.
*
It's hard work to explore the human mind.  Appreciate your fellow writers(like your mom).
*
Fragmentation often helps me perceive facets.
*
If there is one thing that I always want to improve about my work, it's the craftsmanship.  Does that make any sense to you?
*
How close are you to what you are reading right now?  What could close that distance?
*
Do you ever feel like all the things you read have something to praise?
*
Judgement is a fun game.  You can play it at home, with relatively little equipment.  You just think about a person, reduce their life to sociological concepts, and say &quot;Jesus!  I can't believe they live like that.&quot;
*
Was that trite?
*
I will have two extra copies of this manuscript, when I finish.  I might mail one of them to Rachel.  I
might send the other one to my sister.
*
I was talking to Ryan the other day about my love life.  My thoughts were that I was messing things up by
trying to explain things, and that, in the future, I would try to concentrate on simply generating the right
smell...
*
Is this a craft?  Can I use this to explain my existence to society so that I can survive?  Do I have to do
other stuff too?  Ok.
*
Oh, yeah.  You can always find a copy of this on &quot;oostendorp.net&quot; -- it's ridiculous that I own that.
Millions of people around the world can access my file simply by writing my last name in a little box on
their screens...  It cost $70.  It's not much, but it's a home...
*
Somewhere, there is a number with my name on it.  If I get a piece of paper in the mail which says that that
number will increase, that means that I can feed the other pieces of paper that I get in the mail which say
that that number will decrease.  This is Nate's life in terms of his economics.
*
Analogy is another fun game.  Explain one system with another system.  It's easy, really, because all these
systems look kinda the same anyway...
*
I have a few friends, I think that we'd all like to get in on it.  None of them know &quot;what they're doing with their lives&quot; anyway...  and it's to the point now where I think anyone my age who knows is na&#239;ve.  Well,
that's not really true.  It depends on the person.
*
I've gained a lot of insight from playing chess.  This is why I'm excited about learning &quot;Go&quot;.  Maybe I'll leap from game to game, stealing insights -- a board-game wisdom pirate!
*
The key here is not to get lost.  Remember that all you're reading is more-or-less carefully worded rubbish from Nate's mind...  I am in constant need of  reminding myself.
*
Boy am I ever going to have a hard time editing this mess!  Oh well.  If it gets too big to read all at once, I'll divide it into chunks and serve it arbitrarily to people on the internet...
*
If this is getting boring to you, stop immediately!  Go read something else that interests you....
*
&quot;System have subsystems have subsystems have subsystems have subsystems, and that is why we are always starting over.&quot;  - Computer Science wisdom.
*
If there's one thing we Gen-Xers can't stand, it's someone with a &quot;cause&quot;...
*
Am I writing a post-modern masterpiece?  Or waste of time?  Is it the difference in the number of people who read it and shrug and the number of people who read it and nod?  Maybe I should put a poll up on the site and we can keep track of it, then...
*
I'm trying to write this piece in the moment, as to include a certain amount of Zen.  You'll have to ask me about my motivations later...
*
This piece needs more actual content.  Let's begin:
*
Was that moment just now just like that moment that was the exact moment that the Buddha was enlightened?  How could you make the next moment better?
*
If this bores you, it's because there's a point at which all art goes bad, when Intricate Jazz Solos sound like deranged random notes and Impressive Masterpieces from Ages Ago seem like stale mouthfuls of art history trivia.  That point is defined by when you lose interest.  Don't forget that that stuff should always be available to the people who find it engaging, and optional to those who don't.  Nothing is more nauseating than force-fed art.
*
Our relationship has gotten all messed up!  Who let that happen!?!
*
And what makes you think that the things that you say aren't sacred?  What did that Jesus guy have on you?  Do you think being the son of God helped him out?  If anything, he should make it easier for you...  you can see where he's been already...
*
I am dividing this work up into small sections, so that it will be easier for you to swim with them.
*
Keep in mind that there are three forces at work here.  You, me, and this page.  Except by the time you read this it's only you and this page.  And now the page doesn't matter.
*
I agree with the idea that we need spiritual revival.  I know a lot of people who haven't found their spark yet...  and a few who've lost it and could stand to find it again.
*
I'm always skeptical about collection plates.  I give to them anyway.  I guess this makes me &quot;Good&quot;.
*
How would it affect your reading of this if I told you I was a Christian?  What effect would it have on you if I told you I wasn't a Christian?  What if I asked you which you were first?  If you could, would you go
back in time and answer something differently, just to confirm that I would give you the other answer?
Why?
*
But don't scare them off!  They'll think that you want something from them!
*
I'm certain I'll lose interest in whatever is going on here the moment I stop working on it.
*
I think there are levels of interest at work here.  Your reading of this is likely to be distracted by something more dependent on real-time.  Excellent.  Go call your boyfriend or whatever.  You can always read this later...
*
I guess I can see some advantages in being looked at as a bit eccentric...  At least you're not saying &quot;Oh, Nate he's just a [computer geek | college kid | detached intellectual | et al.]&quot;  Or maybe you are, and you're reading this anyway...  in that case it was you who had the jump on me...  a very funny situation indeed.
*
If you've gotten tired of this genre in which I'm writing, please move on...  I'm only writing because I still find it interesting.  But, of course, in the end I'll try to get a machine to do it for me...
*
You probably interact with wise people every day.  Savor them.
*
Someone should probably reading this thinking: Isn't that cute?  Here's a little man who is amazed by his own ideas...
*
I can entertain myself for hours if necessary.  I'm sure you can, too; otherwise you wouldn't have gotten this far...
*
I was reading Dr. Suzuki's Essentials of Zen Buddhism.  In the middle of page 17, without warning, I found myself aware of every capital &quot;Z&quot; on the page where the word &quot;Zen&quot; was written
*
Rob once explained bars to me:  &quot;You see, everyone who sits at the bar...  everyone's a little bit shitty.  I mean, there are, of course, degrees of shittiness, but there's a certain comradery that you gain, simply by sitting at the bar...&quot;
*
Yes, I can admit that I was from Clean Calvinist Politically Right Family &quot;A&quot; and don't let me forget it!
*
&quot;Wouldn't you?&quot;
Yes, you would.
*
No more drunkards!
No more aeroplanes!
No more vigor!
No more urinary passages!
No more enigmas!
        --Triztan Tzara
*
No one can escape from destiny
No one can escape from DADA
Only DADA can enable you to escape from destiny.
        --Triztan Tzara
*
Bob throws a ball straight up with an initial velocity of 2000 km/sec.  What is the ball's maximum height?  Bob is 3'4&quot; and can't get dates, despite his tremendous torso strength.  Express answers in si units to nearest 3 significant digits.
*
Which of the following are not true?
A)  Bill is Round
B)  12 &lt; 17
C)  If you blink your eyes and click your heels you can be interviewed by Larry King
D)  57
E) The professor has gout.
*
If I kissed you, but then you wiped it off would it still be a poem?
*
If I were to write a poem to you to tell you I love you but instead of speaking words only speak sounds that I thought told you that I love you but to your perspective really seemed like some sort of threat almost like what you hear punk rock singers saying because you can't really understand the words but it isn't the words that are important anyway it is the SOUND that I was trying to show you in the first place, but it wasn't the sound that I really intended for you to hear, but you really liked it anyway because you're rather fond of punk rock singers and your favorite group of all time is the CLASH and could we go out for soup or have some pie together after class?
*
1.  There were 3 cylinder group with 2112 inodes per group, so 6336 inodes were created in partition 0.  The number of superblock file slots used is 3, one per cylinder group.  The number of files possible is 6336.
*
Hello Nathan!  This is a really cool machine.  I wish you would buy me one for my birthday.  But I know that probably isn't likely since you are just a poor student. I wonder what computers will be like 5 yrs from now.  Really I NEED one of these for my recipes in the kitchen.  Well I must go and slave over a hot stove and dish water for awhile.  I love you., Mom
*
I am tired to the bone
little flecks of calcium
crumble off and are too exhausted
to put themselves back on my neck
my back
my knees
*
I was having dinner with Cecile.  She had given me a book of Calvin and Hobbes cartoons for my birthday.  I commented that I found Calvin's father amusing, because when I was a kid, and I had to do something that I didn't want to, my father tell me &quot;it builds character.&quot;  Cecile said that they had a phrase like that for little girls in France:  &quot;You must suffer to be cute.&quot;
*
SPONTAINIOUS DADA POEM:
Ta tata ta bim
ta tata da bim
bimbim bem lutu too
kimkim bam lutu tu
tu tu tu tu tu tu tu tu
tut tut tut tut tut tut tut
pug gnut vet vet vet vet
et et et et et tu? Tut?
Nok nok nok tet
nok nok nok tet
tee tee at at at at
ubi E ubi E
sca kata nihm too
scata not nihm too
*
my stereo hummed
Philip Glass' organ echoes
playing
and small
distortions in patterns were easily missed
he glanced at (me drinking out of his mug)
and related
a held recent moment of clarity
while dialing the telephone
had revealed this axiom:
&quot;If tubas were banned,
only bands would have tubas.&quot;
grinning and blinking,
that mornings coffee was sipped in celebration of discovery
*
CD Hamrick and I often correspond on email while at work, since we both work on computers.  We were expecting new office furniture, and I commented that it was going well, but it was strange to have our office furniture be by far our largest asset.  His response was:  &quot;furniture and zombies!&quot;
*
One time, Martin and I were talking in his office.  I asked him if he had gotten bored at work.  He mentioned that yes, a while ago there were two years where he really didn't do too much, and was bored most of the time.  Somewhat shocked at the idea of two years of boredom, I asked him what he did.  &quot;I built a ship inside a bottle,&quot; he said, &quot;it was a big ship.&quot;
*
Marty used to have an electronic parrot in his office.  When a noise was made near it, it had a small computer chip inside and a speaker which would repeat the sound several times while the bird flapped its wings and rolled its eyes.  Martin had made a sign which he hung under the bird:  &quot;Meet Donnelly's Newest VP.  Talk to her.&quot;
*
Martin had a plush moose head, which he had clamped to his cubicle wall.  On the moose was a green and white striped &quot;Cat in the Hat&quot; hat, which he had somehow aquired.  He called it his &quot;Phycisists Hat&quot; and sometimes, when I walked into his office, he'd be wearing it.  But when he saw me coming in, he'd put it back on the moose.
*
Be warm for a half hour
Be warm for an hour
Be warm for an hour and a half
Be warm for two hours
        -- The Snooze Button Truth

</doctext>
  <node_id>167152</node_id>
  <title>Nate's Wisdom Data</title>
</node>
