<node>
  <doctext>You probably have noticed a new &quot;node bucket&quot; section
to your personal nodelet -- this has a couple new 
features which you will be interested in:
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You can add items to it in the same manner as the normal 
personal nodelet
&lt;li&gt;it allows you to drop (remove) items without going to your homenode
&lt;li&gt;when you are on a group-type node, it will give you the
option to add node in the group.  This is a &quot;safer&quot; means
of nodegroup manegement -- and works cross-browser
unlike our current nodegroup editor.  &lt;b&gt;This also allows you
to move writeups to different e2nodes!&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You specify nodes to drop with the checkbox, if you are
adding to group and you uncheck the &quot;drop and execute&quot; box --
that will add the node to the group, but also keep it in 
your node bucket.
&lt;p&gt;
Please let me know if there are any problems/confusion about
the new feature.  This is a backport of a nodelet in the new
everything core, but I've been using it on [Animefu] and
it seems to work fine.
&lt;p align=right&gt;--[nate]

&lt;p&gt;Addendum -- moving a writeup to a different e2node
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Go directly to the writeup in question (not it's e2node -- the actual writeup view, where you'd see the &quot;kill&quot; link)  All writeup titles end in (person|place|thing|idea)
&lt;li&gt;Click on the add link in the node bucket
&lt;li&gt;Now go to the E2NODE that you want to insert the node into -- there should be a &quot;launch editor&quot; link at the 
top of the node, because it is a GROUP of WRITEUPS
&lt;li&gt;Check the box in the nodebucket for the writeup you want to drop, and click &quot;add to group&quot;
&lt;li&gt;Note that this will NOT remove the writeup from it's old e2node -- it just 
puts it in the new one.
&lt;/ol&gt;
</doctext>
  <createtime>2001-01-13 19:56:45</createtime>
  <node_id>909990</node_id>
  <edittime>0000-00-00 00:00:00</edittime>
  <type_nodetype>13</type_nodetype>
  <document_id>909990</document_id>
  <title>Node Bucket Usage</title>
</node>
