<node>
  <title>Node Forwarding: Useful Feature, or Malarkey?</title>
  <type_nodetype>13</type_nodetype>
  <doctext>&lt;h2&gt;wormhole!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These things are node_wormholes! What a cool name! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I made a superdoc for this because I thought it was a bit much to explain in a /msg.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a proposed feature. I went ahead and implemented it, but I can (Hell, I &lt;em&gt;will&lt;/em&gt;, even) go back and remove it if the mood of the meeting is against it. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A [node_forward] is a node, like anything else around here. It has one property: The node ID of a &quot;target&quot; node. When you go to a node_foward node, it scoots you along to that &quot;target&quot; node and you're none the wiser&lt;sup&gt;&lt;small&gt;1&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example: We could make a node_forward called [Node Title Edit], which would point to [Edit these E2 Titles]. When a well-meaning but clueless user directs a newbie to [Node Title Edit] in the chatterbox, that newbie can click on the link &lt;strong&gt;and s/he will end up at [Edit these E2 Titles],&lt;/strong&gt; presto-chango, abracadabra. We don't have to educate each and every user about the issue. We just have to create one forward node and the problem is solved. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It's got some potential for misuse, of course: It is much better to coerce and cajole the little darlings into spelling hardlinks correctly, than to run around behind them creating forwards for all their misspellings. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here's an example. Note that it's not pipe-linked: It's just a plain hardlink to a node -- but you end up somewhere else.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[forwardtest]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here's what the editing interface looks like:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/index.pl?node=forwardtest&amp;displaytype=edit&quot;&gt;edit forwardtest&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[nate], [N-Wing], [JayBonci]: This is implemented idiotically. It's done with &lt;tt&gt;javascript:location.href&amp;nbsp;=&amp;nbsp;url;&lt;/tt&gt;, which sucks. Inside &lt;tt&gt;&amp;lt;noscript&amp;gt;&lt;/tt&gt; tags, we've got &lt;tt&gt;&amp;lt;meta http-equiv=&quot;refresh&quot; content=&quot;url&quot;&amp;gt;&lt;/tt&gt;, which sucks even more. It ought to be done on the server, naturally, but I couldn't figure a way to do that (well, I found one, but it did weird shit). Call it a proof (or refutation?) of concept. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;sup&gt;&lt;small&gt;1&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;We'd make it work a bit differently for gods. The code for that is in there, but it's commented out while I demonstrate the thing. Right now, you're seeing just what an end user would see. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Further Notes:&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;These would be creatable and modifiable &lt;em&gt;only&lt;/em&gt; by gods, it seems to me (and to Lord Brawl, who asked). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;While we're at it,&lt;/strong&gt; let's make [create node] a level 5 (or whatever) power and have lower-level users be able 
to create nodes only via the search feature -- which might in some troublesome cases lead them time and again to a &quot;DON'T 
FUCKIN' DO THAT, YOU BONEHEAD!&quot; document. But slightly more tactful. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;No, no, never mind&lt;/strong&gt; -- [create node] does the same thing anyway. Still, it's hard to find anybody too dumb to 
create a node via the search feature. All the morons use that; that's usually why they do all-lowercase titles. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[bones] says:  I think 'create a node' should return 10 possible node titles 
that are already in the database - but this would take longer, of course.  I 
think one of our major problems is where some of the information is being put
on E2.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I like Node Forwarding - I would like to not have to deal with 'node id' - I'd 
prefer to just use node title.  I'd also like to be able to set several 'node 
forwards' at once, in one page load. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[wharfinger] says: Doing it by title + nodetype instead is no problem. Doing 
several forwards in one page load would be a different feature from the one I've 
just written (which as I've said is not ideal even for what it is). It might be a better 
one, but given how often it would be used, I'm not sure that it's enough better to 
justify the effort. [N-Wing], [nate], or [JayBonci] or somebody would have to fire 
up his mammoth, pulsing brain to answer that one. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;[wharfinger] 8/29/01 13:33:55&lt;/strong&gt; Gritchka suggests that using 
these to redirect surnames to full names would create problems, e.g. with Dvorak 
the keyboard layout vs. various people named Dvorak (and also with Hawking the 
man vs. hawking the verb, and Steve Jones vs. Tom Jones vs. Quincy Jones etc.) 
and, uh, yep, that's not an appropriate use of the feature at all. It's got much more 
limited application than that. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, Dvorak keyboards mostly appeal to cranks, flakes, and 
New Age maniacs. Maybe it's for the best. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It would be nice to be able to forbid the creation of, say, anything called &quot;[definately]&quot;. 
I mean, just forbid it, period (except of course for gods, ha ha, since we're so goddamn 
wise and good). But that's another issue. &lt;/p&gt;
</doctext>
  <node_id>1147570</node_id>
</node>
