<node>
  <doctext>&lt;p&gt;[wharfinger] wonders: Am I saying anything that needs to be said here, or 
am I just [shitting on the floor|throwing a fit]? Should I &quot;node&quot; it? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr&gt;


&lt;p&gt;The [supermarket] is there for everybody, or at least that's what I thought 
when I walked in and crapped on the floor. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The supermarket &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; there for everybody. Any fool can see that. If 
it's not there for everybody, then it's just a playground for [The Power 
Structure of Everything 2|a small clique] who run it to suit themselves. Of 
course, the small-minded, petty [middle manager]s who run the place are too 
rigid and biased to let the supermarket be the great place it could be if they'd 
just [loosen up] a bit. I was making a statement in my own way, and they 
couldn't handle that. The point clearly went right over their heads, because 
they started telling me I wasn't &quot;allowed&quot; to shit on the floor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not &quot;allowed&quot;?! How absurd! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was expressing my feelings. There's nothing wrong with that. [The mental 
cripples who run the supermarket must be afraid of feelings], or else they'd 
welcome mine. It's not like I damaged anything! The floor is made of slick tile. 
Shit won't harm it. It won't even leave any permanent marks! How do I know? I 
know because &lt;strong&gt;those pathetic little men with their little cop-minds 
erased everything I'd done and left no sign of it!&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why couldn't they leave it there? Maybe some people don't like it, but that's 
&lt;em&gt;their&lt;/em&gt; problem, not mine. It's purely [subjective]. They could walk 
around it, couldn't they? But they won't do that. [They have to destroy 
everything they don't understand]. That's because it scares them. They're afraid 
that somebody else will see it and understand how small and laughable they 
really are. They're afraid somebody else will see through their stupid 
rules.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you know they threw me out of there? When they came to clean it up, I told 
them not to. I explained that they were free to express themselves any way they 
liked, and I wouldn't object. I told them how unfair it was to single me out: 
There were dozens of other customers in the store -- why were they picking on 
&lt;em&gt;me?!&lt;/em&gt; They wouldn't listen. They wouldn't even answer my arguments! 
Obviously, they knew they couldn't refute me. In fact, when I tried to protect 
my work, they called security and had me thrown out. What else could I do but 
try to call attention to their [abuse of power]? I yelled! I screamed! I let 
everybody know! But the other customers were afraid to help, just like in any 
[police state].&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course I went back the next day. I won't let my rights be taken away so 
easily. I won't [self-censorship|censor myself] just to please a few petty 
tyrants. The whole scene played out again, just like the first time. It's funny 
and a little bit sad, how predictable they are. The next day, I went back to 
insist on my rights once more, and they wouldn't even let me in the store. How 
do you like that? When I first shopped at that store, it seemed like a friendly 
place, but finally the ugly truth came out: It's a [dictatorship]. You're only 
welcome there as long as you [obey] authority.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The managers know that if they don't enforce their arbitrary little rules, 
they'll have no power. What they don't understand is that [sic semper 
tyrannis|their time will come, like that of all tyrants]. One day, the 
[supermarket] will be there for everybody. Everybody will belong. Everybody will 
have fun there, and all the most exciting and creative people will shop there. 
It's really a pathetic shame, how they've taken what could have been such a 
great store and chased away all the truly creative customers. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for me, well, [they don't deserve me]. I won't waste any more time trying 
to make that store a better place. These days, I've got my eye on a little 
[delicatessen|deli] down the street. When I walk in there, everybody's friendly. 
Tomorrow I think I'll just waltz right in, [drop trou], and cut loose. I've been 
eating some [vindaloo|exciting things] lately. I can tell that the guys at the 
deli are strong and [open-minded] enough to welcome a real challenge to their 
views.&lt;/p&gt;
</doctext>
  <type_nodetype>13</type_nodetype>
  <title>The supermarket is there for everybody</title>
  <node_id>1128377</node_id>
</node>
