<node>
  <doctext>&lt;B&gt;&lt;I&gt;Paging [Dr. Octagon]...&lt;/I&gt;

&lt;P&gt;I am repurposing this as a homenode away from home, where I can keep thoughts and ideas about E2 that I wouldn't like everyone to see. You know, like suggestions and stuff. If you wanna see the original thing I posted here, please scroll down.&lt;/B&gt;&lt;HR&gt;

Suggestions

&lt;UL&gt;

&lt;LI&gt;Under &lt;U&gt;no&lt;/U&gt; circumstances should an e2god (or anyone else for that matter) be able to read the private inboxes of another user without the expressed permission of that user. I propose a checkbox in user settings (turned ON by default) which makes it impossible for us to view any such messages. If a user is being harassed and wants to prove it, he or she can then uncheck the box and give us access. I have been assured a number of times in the past that no one on E2 can or will read my private messages. I expect this policy to continue indefinitely into the future. The post office doesn't go through my mail. Verizon execs don't sit around the board room listening to folks having phone sex. This is basic ethics &amp;ndash; a no-brainer. I'm not suggesting that any one of us would actually abuse the right, but there's no point in having the temptation constantly waved under our noses when another system would work just as well.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;/LI&gt;&lt;BR&gt;

&lt;LI&gt;When a e2node title changes, the associated writeups should also change their titles. This should either happen automatically, or by clicking a button which simply re-sumbits all the writeups in the node. Currently, this is being done manually (by the few gods who even care) by going to each writeup and re-sumbitting it -- a supreme pain in the ass.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;/LI&gt;&lt;BR&gt;

&lt;LI&gt;All long noded public domain books should be moved into &quot;document&quot; form. The e2node for the book title should contain basic information and link to a Table of Contents on the first page of the E2 document for that book. The navigation and layout should be standardized. This will prevent the confusion that results from coming across the 39th chapter of something and not even knowing what it is, and more completely separates the user-created material from the larger reference materials which require a much greater investment of time to read than the avergae E2 user has in a session. A master list of the books noded in document form would also be available, like a library.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;/LI&gt;
&lt;/UL&gt;

&lt;HR&gt;&lt;P&gt;Hi Uberfetus,

&lt;P&gt;Having missed most of the discussions &quot;behind the scenes&quot; regarding the E2 Nuke Request that I posted, I would like to add a few more comments.

&lt;P&gt;First off: I did not post the nuke request out of a grudge against anyone, but out of a desire to keep the factual content on E2 relevant.

&lt;P&gt;I believe these nodes should no longer be present for the following two reasons:

&lt;P&gt;- The content is incomplete, and therefore misleading. For instance, looking at the [Strom Thurmond], one could conclude that he only served two terms as a senator. There is no data for previous years, but there is also no indication that the data is incomplete. (granted, the other writeups in the node make up for this, but you see my point for the other nodes that only have the single writeup.)

&lt;P&gt;- The factual content is marginal. These writeups don't add more relevant information than was already included in the two lists (except perhaps the party affiliation, but it is unclear to me why that data wasn't included in the two congress-listings).

&lt;P&gt;The writeups serve as a bad example for new noders. Frankly, I believe if any new noder would undertake a project like this, the writeups would be removed, and he/she would receive a word of warning.

&lt;P&gt;It seems to me that the best alternative would be to keep the nodeshells, with the softlinks going to the two congress-listings, and see them filled up wherever people desire to do so.

&lt;P&gt;Please understand that I have written the request with the best intentions of improving the factual content of E2. I would be interested in hearing your opinion on this.

&lt;P&gt;Best Regards,

&lt;P&gt;Prof. Pi

&lt;HR&gt;&lt;P&gt;

Prof. Pi,

&lt;P&gt;Before I respond, you should be told that I am in the midst of a period during which have no home Internet access for a few weeks. What this means is that my involvement with E2 is very limited until the end of August. I am no longer aware of the daily happenings of the site, and haven't been carrying out basic god duties such as nuke requests and nodeshell deletions for quite some time now.

&lt;P&gt;Instead, I've been logging in only occasionally (when I have the opportunity) to read my /msgs and give feedback about various things going on.

&lt;P&gt;Although there was an announcement about your Nuke Request (in fact, it was only through your e-mail that I learned the identity of the request poster), there has not been much editorial dialog on the subject, at least as far as I can tell.

&lt;P&gt;However, I did state to the content editors that I have found the congressional writeups useful, and I would, in fact, be sad to see them go &amp;#91;though not crushed&amp;#93;. I have no doubts concerning the truthfulness of your intentions; I have seen no evidence that you are anything but a well-meaning E2 user. And I do feel that JeffMagnus could have and should have done a better job with the auto-noding. Nevertheless, I disagree with blanket removal of the writeups.

&lt;P&gt;I am one of the more lenient editors when it comes to the practice known as NFN. There are some silly and useless examples of NFN out there which deserve deletion. Noding zip codes. This is like noding [5] as &quot;How many fingers people have on their hands&quot;. No one looks up [5] looking for this information -- if they want it, they can go to [hand] or [finger]. Noding games like tic-tac-toe also produces massive amounts of junk writeups which serve no purpose except to reach the next Level.

&lt;P&gt;So the question to me is whether or not the congressional writeups fit this description. Firstly, it is clear to me that senators and members of the US House of Representatives *ought* to be noded, and under their names. You'd probably agree. They make the laws of the land, and each of them is a pretty big deal, at least in the area they represent. I am of the opinion (definitely not shared by some other gods) that a nodeshell for a fact which ought to be noded is better than no node at all. In my mind, there are three levels of allowable factual noding.

&lt;P&gt;1. Nodeshell: This allows interlinking of the node, the minimal content. Softlinks are vital, and they are, in my opinion, what makes the site so unique. In addition, (in my experience) it inspires others to fill the gap in knowledge faster than if there were no shell at all.

&lt;P&gt;2. &quot;Placeholder&quot; Writeup: A small amount of information describing the title. Not something I would upvote, but if I don't know what the title of the node means, this should at last define the term or identify the individual for me.

&lt;P&gt;3. &quot;Complete&quot; Writeup: In-depth description of topic. Longer stuff which generally gets cooled. Could/Should have some subjective content, but in addition to (rather than in place of) the facts.

&lt;P&gt;(1) and (3) are pretty clear-cut. Whether or not a writeup fulfills (2) is a judgement call. Here are three writeups I made up to demonstrate what I mean.

&lt;P&gt;Bill Gates
&lt;BR&gt;-------------------------------------
&lt;BR&gt;(person) by pinchemadre

&lt;P&gt;Satan. Should be dragged out into the street and shot for his shitty Windows OS.

&lt;P&gt;-------------------------------------
&lt;BR&gt;(person) by CmdrTaco

&lt;P&gt;Richest guy in the world. Runs Micro$oft. Doesn't like Linux. You will be assimilated.

&lt;P&gt;-------------------------------------
&lt;BR&gt;(person) by Cool Man Eddie

&lt;P&gt;(1955-) The richest man in the world, on paper. Founded Microsoft in 1975 along with Paul Allen. Brought the world familiar software such as DOS, Windows, Office, and Internet Explorer. One of the geeks who launched the personal computer revolution. His vision is debatable, but his enormous impact and marketing skills are not.
&lt;BR&gt;-------------------------------------

&lt;P&gt;So which of these is acceptable according to my (2)? All provide some information. &quot;pinchemadre&quot;'s writeup tells me that he is responsible for Windows, but is ultra-subjective, abrasive, and minimalist. I'd nuke it. &quot;CmdrTaco&quot;'s is closer, but it's still quite subjective, only really tells me he's a rich guy who runs Microsoft, and wastes 3 out of 14 words on Gates' position on Linux, of relatively little importance to people who don't run an open-source news site. The subject would get maybe two pages in a 300 page bio. So, while better, I'd nuke that too.

&lt;P&gt;Cool Man Eddie's gives me the basic information I would expect. It doesn't tell me he has a wife, went to Harvard, or lives in Washington, but still gives a nice, concise description of the man. His subjective final sentence does not detract, either. I'd say this fits my (2) criteria pretty well. Until someone writes some big bio on E2, this will do just fine.

&lt;P&gt;This is how I feel about the congressional writeups. It gives the basic important info without any fluff. Where better writeups exist ([Max Baucus]), the info from the auto-nodes *should be incorporated* into the better writeups (meaning they ought to have party affiliation, house, and which number Congress they are a part of), and Magnus' should be  deleted. But say I hear about some guy named [J. Dennis Hastert] and want to look him up. I don't know he's in the House of Representatives, so I wouldn't know to look him up in a list of all House members. If it was a nodeshell, I could maybe find a softlink to his House, but I still don't know that he's a Republican representing District 14 in Illinois. I think this information ought to stay until bettered.

&lt;P&gt;I will, however, pass your concerns on to the other gods.

&lt;P&gt;Regards,
&lt;BR&gt;Uberfetus


&lt;P&gt;&lt;HR&gt;&lt;HR&gt;&lt;HR&gt;&lt;P&gt;I have had surprisingly productive conversations with some of most vocally angry noders about some of the perceived &quot;injustice&quot; carried out by this editorial staff. One thing stands out as the most important lesson:

&lt;P&gt;We need to accurately divine whether a user needs a guiding hand or a bitchslap. Newbies especially post a LOT of total crap, without necessarily realizing its crappy nature. There are &lt;I&gt;plenty&lt;/I&gt; of times we should be firm and tough, but not always. We are here to help not only the database, but also the user.

&lt;P&gt;Before acting, ask yourself whether a writeup is a genuine (yet failed) attempt to improve E2, or just someone being malicious or subhumanly dumb. Respond appropriately. 

&lt;P&gt;Remember, people are a little afraid of us, but we want this to be like the fear of God rather than the fear of the Nazi party. Our actions, like it or not, are a type of PR. So let's project &quot;OK, I'll see what I can do,&quot; or &quot;You messed up, and here's how to fix it,&quot; rather than &quot;Bugger off, you're nothing to me.&quot; With some consideration, we can mold our own reputation to be that of wise servant-masters and NOT arrogant fat cats. 

&lt;P&gt;As a newbie, I remember being treated pleasantly by the editors and gods, the few times they privately communicated with me (even when about unpleasant things, like killing and borging). I'd like to think that the communication is equally pleasant today.

&lt;P&gt;Rant over, responses welcome.

&lt;P&gt;--[Uberfetus|Uber]

&lt;P&gt;&lt;U&gt;P.S.&lt;/U&gt; I'm not implying that &lt;b&gt;we&lt;/b&gt; are the source of some of the strife on here. I'm just warning you to keep an eye on how you present yourself and how others perceive your actions. I'm convinced 90% of problems are caused by poor communication, so we should wear the best possible faces in our communication with the &lt;s&gt;filthy rabble&lt;/s&gt; users.

&lt;hr&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
[Lord Brawl] says: Despite the advantages of [Node Heaven], etc. I think things were better when we were diligent about daily Editor Logs. 
Then the community could see what we were doing and why. Now all most people see is complaining in the chatterbox, and usualy the complainers
being dealt with in an apparently brutal and high-handed fashion.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
I've been trying to articulate a clear policy about how and why I act, in both my home node and writeups like [GTKY]. 
I'll also pull people into [Poliical Asylum] to talk. But this means I haven't actually noded myself in about a month.
Which is frustrating as all heck.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
I do think I'm slower on the kill switch for active noders than most of my confreres (and perhaps more interested in killing the work of fled noders.)
Thus I have not been in the maelstrom quite as often. But I have been thinking that We could improve both borging and the Killing Floor by having a way to assign
and communicate a reason for each.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
Borging could bring up a form with a &quot;confirm&quot; button. It could have radio buttons for common reasons 
(&quot;for inappropriate behavior&quot; (default), &quot;for insulting other users&quot;, &quot;for blatant trolling&quot; etc.) and &quot;other&quot; along 
with a free-form text box for us to enter the other reasons. They'd get a message like this:&lt;br&gt;
&lt;i&gt;You have been banned from the chatterbox for inappropriate behavior. This will last &lt;/i&gt;n&lt;i&gt; minutes.&lt;/i&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
or for maximum accountability
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;i&gt;You have been banned from the chatterbox by [Lord Brawl] for inappropriate behavior. This will last &lt;/i&gt;n&lt;i&gt; minutes.&lt;/i&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
It might also make sense if there could be one room (I like the name &quot;The Carpet&quot;) where they could talk to us
about what happened and why. (This might also allow them to clear private &lt;tt&gt;/msg&lt;/tt&gt;s, which is a complaint
I've heard about borging a few times.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Killing floor&lt;/b&gt; could also have a reason field, and/or could also generate an automated message:
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Your writeup &quot;&lt;/i&gt;I like to suck my dog's toes&lt;i&gt;&quot; has been removed by the editorial staff.&lt;/i&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
These changes might take some unnecessary mystery out of what goes on without being too onerous for us.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
Was that meandering enough, Uber?
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
</doctext>
  <createtime>2001-01-04 00:08:41</createtime>
  <node_id>898154</node_id>
  <edittime>0000-00-00 00:00:00</edittime>
  <type_nodetype>13</type_nodetype>
  <document_id>898154</document_id>
  <title>The Meandering Thoughts of Uberfetus</title>
</node>
