<node>
  <type_nodetype>13</type_nodetype>
  <doctext>&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;all &lt;i&gt;known&lt;/i&gt; UT WUs have been destroyed, now to search the heavens&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;place text here scattershot&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;assemble into &quot;timeline&quot;, if at all possible&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;P&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;P&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unthai&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lake of Portals &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Complex Nonliving Systems &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Dwarf Of Stapleton Market &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Corps of Explorers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;LtCol. Tri Morrakand&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Terron, the daywalker&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Temporal Knights &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;God Kills. Chemistry Saves. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master Chemist&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Radical-chemists &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Street-chems &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Vespa Argot&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Organic Flux &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Spatial-Temporal Relocations, Ltd. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;First Metavirus Cataclysm &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Patriarchs &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Patriarch Wars &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Descendents of Eternal Lineage&lt;/li&gt; 
&lt;li&gt;Star Gatherer&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;li&gt;end of the line (robnotrob):&lt;/li&gt; &lt;br&gt;
This is as far as I go. Just past the ridge maybe 2 or 3 clicks you'll see a sign, underground tokyo Then you have a couple of options: you can try and get there yourself, in which case your only chance is to go at night. Not much of a chance . The trip takes too long and when the sun comes up, well you'll be somethings dinner. Or you can wait for him, he'll know you're there. Don't ask me how. People call him Terron, the daywalker. The mutants call him hell.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;li&gt;United Interests (thefez):&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;
one of the last trans-stellar corporations of the late 23rd century, UI made thier bread and butter in land speculation, terraforming, mining and pharmaceuticals research. In the final years of the 23rd century the new, fresh-faced CEO (a position referred to as the Star Gatherer in UI circles) Ammon Zot issued directive 4467071, which allocated the resources necessary to expand their Corps of Explorers into the now infamous UIIEF.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;li&gt;UIIEF (thefez):&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;
United Interests Interplanetary Expedition Force, est. standard year 2287. This unit was disbanded thriteen standard years later, at the insistance of the Council of Set, whose trade negotiations with the outer colonies were being disrupted by what they referred to as &quot;The damnable piracy and wholesale slaughter at the merciless hands of the despicable United Interests demon-worshippers.&quot; UIIEF spokespeople were unavailable for comment at the time.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;li&gt;vatjob (thefez):&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;
an android prototype grown in large crystalline vats, hence the slang. the original concept was to grow specialized workers and warriors for domestic use and offworld sale, but the social upheavals during and after the first metavirus cataclysm made it impossible to control the growing and programming of artificial personnel.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;li&gt;Sam Zenpus (thefez):&lt;/li&gt; &lt;br&gt;
&quot;'It ain't just Buck Rogers out here anymore; we got real problems.' With that Sam powered up his suit and leaped from one of the orbital platforms arrayed around the ancient derelict monolith. That was the last time I saw him. God help as all.&quot; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

-memoirs of LtCol. Tri Morrakand, UIIEF&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;li&gt;Council of Set (thefez): &lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;
an atemporal, political and religious fraternity of wizards, scientists and mystics who have had control of human interests throughout history. to give a date of the creation of this organization would be impossible, as their complete mastery of the mechanics and philosophy of warping technology makes such distinctions irrelevant. as can be heard in the mantras that echo through the chambers of the Council, &quot;always, everywhere and forever&quot;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;li&gt;Zira Muldoone (thefez):&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&quot;I heard from a vatjob in Lepto Station, topside, that Muldoone was off in the waste land, preaching to the Radioactivists. Seemed kinda far-fetched. Can't imagine those radheads listening to a pureblood.&quot;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;li&gt;Master of Assassins (thefez):&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Let us not forget the Chem-Guild, o my brother. The Master Chemist would cut you off real quick-like if he thought that you had forgotten who REALLY has the power in UT.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;li&gt;nukeboyz (thefez):&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&quot;You will see. Behold the glory of the divine Atom! In it's perfect reflection the true believer who is genetically fit will be given gifts innumerable. To the rest, death!&quot;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

-the Archon of the Radioactivists, true name unknown&lt;P&gt;

&lt;li&gt;The Soldiers of God (thefez):&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;
a splinter organization of Spatial-Temporal Relocations, Ltd., the Soldiers of God have dedicated themselves and their progeny to the eradication of all non-licensed use of Warping technology and to the disbanding of all other financial and religious movements whose econo-pious epicenters rely on this technology.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;li&gt;Armistice of Tunis (thefez-eclip5e):&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;
A treaty signed after the Patriarch Wars, it signified the growth of the CyNex 8 Neural Network. This aggrement also helped to form the new Virospitals that would start to help street-chems and other denziens to regain hope.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;li&gt;Sergeant Nicholas Thrillbanger (the gilded frame):&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;
I never liked him much, myself. The kinda guy who's always pulling on the tails of your waistcoat but never saying nothin'. Sure he's all killer--all of them are, but you wouldn't know it with his wooden eye and glass leg. He's the trigger man for those CyNex bugs they use. He can make them pop and burn, right while they're buried in the back of yer head. But he's backhanded and Sam Zenpus would say so if he still had his tongue.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;li&gt;Zulamar (thefez)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;
its been said that Zulamar was once a sheikh of a murderous clan of brigands who plied their savage trade across the routes through The Western Lands, but it has also been hinted to that he has amassed his huge criminal organization through aggressive internet recruiting and evasive tax and income manipulations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;li&gt;patriarch wars (thefez):&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;
the clans that came into being in the wake of the first metavirus cataclysm clamored for power. this power was to be had in the Descendents of Eternal Lineage, known presently as the Patriarchs. These beings, at one time thought to be immortal, emerged from their basalt tombs to lead the clans to the greatest confrontation of the New Age. For sixty solar years these wars scarred the already weakened planet, and ended with the Armistice of Tunis.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;li&gt;Dr. Hilton Burmen (thefez):&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Dr. Burmen, before the release of the metavirus and ensuing worldwide chaos, was a member of the shadowy Right to Fight organization. After the first metavirus casualties began to appear, it is believed that he took to his island stronghold to begin working on a way to reverse the process. Nothing is known of his current whereabouts, except for the sporadic rumors that come from the FR6616 region of southern Chile. These reports, however, cannot be confirmed.&lt;P&gt;

&lt;li&gt;The Shogun of Underground Tokyo (thefez)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&quot;The Shoguns' policy of Zero Diplomacy only truly applies to the faceless nomad bands that flitter about on the surface world. His coffers are lined by the guilds, just as ours are. His will is theirs.&quot; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 
-Zulamar, Master of Assassins&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;li&gt;Right to Fight Organization (the gilded frame):&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&quot;I joined Right to Fight organization in its founding days, just after the release of the CyNex 8 neural network. This &quot;living software&quot; had taken one step too far. You see, to move on, to attain the new, often you must kill the old. CyNex 8 had determined that its creators had become the old. Whether it was true or not could only be determined by trying to shut it down. One could say that by fighting it, I was a conspirator.&quot; -Dr. Hilton Burmen &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;li&gt;CyNex 8 Neural Network (the gilded frame, thefez):&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&quot;It was freeform, like working with putty. We had no specific design in mind when we started. That kept us from the anticipation of horror that hung over those working with the rebel seismic device. We picked up all the fringes at the cutting edge of science and knotted them together. We were like children with total disregard for the future as we laughed and played. I learned my lesson the day it was released: Pay attention to what the hell you're doing.&quot; -Dr. Hilton Burmen&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&quot;The CyNex systems started ugly. We couldn't just grow the neural material we needed, so we 'liberated' it from hosts who could never really fully use it anyway; criminals, the insane and the uninsured. Fusion with the machine was tricky, and our nano-boys couldn't fill the work orders. Thats when we teamed up with the Om Corporation. Of course, our investors and legal staff hit the roof when we announced it, but CyNex was our puppy. I felt it was worth the risk. History has proved us fools.&quot;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

-fragment of last known transmission from Dr. Titus Ivanko, Team Burmen, AD 2017&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;li&gt;SelectKill(tm) EMP Software (thefez):&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;
SelectKill was the last open-market &quot;software package&quot; developed by the Right to Fight organization in tandem with what was to become Spatial-Temporal Relocations, Ltd.. This software, when inserted into a neural network, will seek out all desired nodelets and information bundles. When the target information is found, SelectKill will send a series of pulses designed to scramble the data, making it unusable and leading to its isolation and expulsion from the home system.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;li&gt;Neuroleptic Epidemic (thefez-eclip5e):&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;
The disease quickly overtook parts of Underground Tokyo. It was partly because of the after-affects of the First Metavirus Cataclysm, and also the Rebel Seismic Device. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;li&gt;Super-Complex Bio-Machine (the gilded frame-eclip5e):&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Sequentially after the CyNex 8 Neural Network was designed, and implemented, a Complex Nonliving Systems device was needed to scour the network to gleam information otherwise unsearchable to the Radical-chemists. This AI bio-mechanical droid was built just for that task. Search, report, and deploy. Eventually a new type of Synth-Net was incurred. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;li&gt;Virospital (dem bones-eclip5e):&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;
A region, or part of Underground Tokyo that is governed, ruled, and cared for by a particular group of Radical-chemists. The Living Software that controls portions of the region usually dispences warnings about the advances of the Neuroleptic Epidemic. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;li&gt;Synth-Net (dem bones-eclip5e):&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Part of the CyNex 8 Neural Network that was scoured by the Super-Complex Bio-Machine. It eventually became the more inportant information revolving around the information needed by the Radical-chemists. It was all archived and displayed the Lang-Code, moderated by chem-Guild. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;li&gt;Chem-Guild (thefez):&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&quot;There are three fundamental tenets of Guild membership. The first is the protection of the Art from all outsiders . Second, complete obediance to the Guild Council. Lastly, always remember to register all chem-rituals or any transaction of a religious nature with your liaison to the Master Chemist--his spies are not confined to the tunnels and domes of Underground Tokyo and he's always watching.&quot; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

-Vespa Argot, junior chem-guildsman&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;li&gt;Guild Council (thefez-eclip5e):&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;
The group made up of the regional Virospital Master Chemists. They make the decisions about who will be the lord of the Chem-Guild. The group decides by who documented the most information on the Synth-Net, by upgrading their personal Super-Complex Bio-Machine in order to find pertinent information. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;li&gt;accidental poisoning in humans (thefez):&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&quot;When it comes to poisons, there are no accidents. Every toxin, every venom, every necrotizing salve under our sun comes to us with a reason. They will speak to you; you must but listen. They will tell you the secret of their existence. It is to kill another.&quot;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

-Zulamar, Master of Assassins&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;


&lt;li&gt;Class II Warpfield Generator (thefez-eclip5e):&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Designed by the Council of Set, and sold to small companies in limited form, such as the Spatial-Temporal Relocation, LTD. Its known to cause side effects which in some cases can cause mild Synth-Net corruption, and Neurolepsy. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;li&gt;Living Software (dem bones-Distractor):&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Taken from the lecture notes of Dr. Hilton Burmen: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&quot;Even after the Palo Alto Ban Self-modifying Code Ban was put into effect, software developers sought a way to perpetuate themselves. The spectre of forgotten, obsolete software has haunted developers since Y2K -- programs lost, forgotten, too important to delete and too scary to fix. The obvious solution was to create software that improved itself, learned from its exceptions and error conditions. Network connectivity and a new generation of self-compilers and self-interpreters provided the ingredients. Street-Chem sysadmins created safe havens, providing the file permissions and n-dimensional non-volatile memory space for the nacent code's first steps.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

Released into the network, living software replicated through code symbiosis. Detected by a Solodine Industrial programmer within a poorly written device-driver that suddenly began performing beyond specification, it became the seed-kernel for the first complex nonliving system, the CyNex 8 neural network.&quot; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;li&gt;chem-ritual (thefez):&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;
a chem-ritual can vary in complexity from &quot;take two of these and call me in the morning&quot; to elaborate week-long festivals, depending on the desired result. the cost of the ritual also depends on its complexity, as well as the rank of the rad-chem performing it. for simple flights of fancy, any radical-chemist can hook you up in a few minutes for a nominal fee. For &quot;seasonal&quot; events and special occasions, senior rad-chems are usually employed, as their prestige is greater.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 
&lt;li&gt;UTN (thefez-gtsum):&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;
The name originally derived from the poorly concieved subway tunnels that criss-crossed the city. Tunnel Doc's were arrogant enough to belive that the microfilament rock weave would withstand the constant pressure's. Apparently they never considered nano-molecular viruses. About three years before everything else went to shit. The techno shamans detroyed the whole deal because it was interfeering some spirit lines and draining their spirit battery.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;li&gt;Om Corporation (thefez):&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&quot;One people. One world. One Corporation.&quot; was the mantra of this, one of the world's first true megacorporations. What started as a merger between several large and varied financial entities at the dawn of the 21st century quickly evolved into a social and political force in which &quot;employees&quot; were solely dedicated to the advancement of &quot;The Company&quot;. At first, it was touted as a revolutionary new business style. As time passed more and more competitors were labeling them as &quot;business tyrants&quot; and &quot;cultists&quot;. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;li&gt;Neurolepsy (thefez):&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;
quite literally a brain seizure, the neuroleptic epidemic was passed from computer systems that were linked to the CyNex 8 neural network to humans through Direct Interface links, such as datajacks and retinal imaging systems. computer symptoms included data loss and function degradation, while human losses were overwhelmingly due to massive synaptic shutdown and the resulting suspension of autonomic functions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;li&gt;Core-wired (thefez):&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;
the original concept behind core-wired was to create machines that were fully capable of &quot;surviving&quot; off of the planet's resources, and maintaining/upgrading themselves as necessary, without additional human aid. no one ever expected that a neural network would ever be capable of imposing its order on the natural world, but as the knowledge base of core-wired systems grew, the machines began making alterations to the ecosphere to optimize their own expansion.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;li&gt;Lang-Code (dem bones-eclip5e):&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;
When the first Super-Complex Bio-Machines began to scour the CyNex 8 Neural Network, all communication was done between a distributed network of similar devices. The network was continually updated by the Living Software which spoke in a combination of protocol language, and programming code. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;li&gt;Zero Diplomacy (thefez):&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&quot;This is the message that we must carve into the miniscule minds of those craven nukeboyz and dwellers on the blasted surface of this rock: We will not negotiate. There will be no sacrifices. No capitulation. Never!&quot; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

-the Shogun of Underground Tokyo&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&quot;Didya Ever See The Portals?&quot; (thefez):&lt;/li&gt;
&quot;Oh yeah kid, before the new regime came in and blocked the whole thing up, you could take NW 6 out of Underground Tokyo and be at the Lake of Portals in ten minutes! There are hundreds of 'em, all arranged around the first Class II Warpfield Generator ever built! But I guess all the freaky-freaks had to go and ruin it for us sensible and responsible time travellers.&quot;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

-Sam Zenpus&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;li&gt;Rogue-Bit (eclip5e):&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Occasionally the Super-Complex Bio-Machine would come down with a morphed case of a type of Neurolepsy. Instant shutdown would result. At the second of shutdown, the machine would emit a small string of numbers that would propogate into the Synth-Net. Sometimes street-chems could use this information against the Om Corporation. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;li&gt;Machine City (thefez):&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&quot;It appeared before us as a mirage. For days we had been wandering in that Hell, looking for the signs the elders spoke of. All of the plants were poison, and one or two took to following us--waiting for a quick meal if one of us should fall. No one really believed in the Machine City. It was story told by old women to scare disobedient children. If they could have known the truth they would have never invoked the name of this place. It heard them; it came for us.&quot;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;li&gt;FR6616 region (thefez):&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;
6616 was declared a &quot;Free Region&quot; by the Council of Set in the year of the twin suns, common year 2013. Although largely uninhabited, it is believed that the Right to Fight organization maintains an operating time portal in the mountainous area. This Zone of Unoccupation is also known for its unusually high occurrences of firstborn aquatic mutations, which normally take the form of gills behind the ears or scaly, translucent flesh.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;li&gt;Underground Tokyo (thefez, the gilded frame, dem bones):&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;
what started as a financial and religious movement after the first metavirus cataclysm, underground tokyo earned its reputation anew after the detonation of a rebel seismic device in tokyo bay. the system of half-submerged caverns and tunnels has never been fully mapped, and all humanitarian efforts to &quot;repatriate&quot; its pasty and light-sensitive residents has been met with fierce resistance. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&quot;Since it went underground, Tokyo has never been the same. I don't remember the city from before and I don't care to. Outsiders call it a dungeon but they wouldn't have suvived without it. It's a fortress against the world we gave up and when I surface, I go with that dungeon in my heart.&quot;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; -Terron, the daywalker&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

Underground Tokyo is no more. Slowly, she sinks.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;





</doctext>
  <title>Underground Tokyo Anthology</title>
  <node_id>1422494</node_id>
</node>
