<node>
  <doctext>&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
The answer to 99% of the questions you'll be asked over 
the course of your [brief lives] is simple, honest and 
&lt;i&gt;almost always&lt;/i&gt; correct:  &lt;b&gt;&quot;It depends.&quot;&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
In any given situation there is an infinite number of variables.
For every variable you're aware of there are an infinite
number you are not aware of.  
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;b&gt;E2 is not a competition.&lt;/b&gt;

&lt;b&gt;Do votes/reps/xp even have value?&lt;/b&gt;

Yes, as a general guideline I find they are accurate.

&lt;b&gt;There is no 'fair'.&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;b&gt;But that other guy's writeup is dumber than mine!!&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
I know, I know...you already knew that.  People have been
telling you the world isn't fair since you were born, right?
All of them were telling you the truth.  There's no fair,
there's no Santa Claus and your mommy don't love you.  There it is.
There's no justice, either.  To answer an editorial or user
opinion on your work with &quot;But &lt;i&gt;so-and-so a node&lt;/i&gt; is 
way dumber/stupider/poorly spelled/poorly titled/etc example
why not pick on that guy?&quot;  is simply unacceptable.  We'll
(hopefully) get to that guy, to that other writeup that needs
work...but for right now we're working you and yours.  
There is simply a good chance that E2's current standards
are higher than they've ever been...older, poorer writeups
do not excuse newer, poorer work.  Nope.  Nope.  Nope.
&lt;p&gt;


There are inane, babbling and 
mean one-liner writeups that are spelled incorrectly,
filed under ridiculous titles, placed on the [Page of Cool]
and voted up to [rep|reps] of over 100.  Yet yours was voted
down to -8 and 
[voting/experience system|killed with penalty].  That sucks.
It sucks and it happens every day.  The reasons are many.
Any given user submits any given writeup which is viewed/voted upon
by any given number of other users with any given number
of personalities, issues, ideals, beliefs, practices, 
philosophies, hang-ups and bedroom habits.  Then
simply calculate the editor effect...you've only got a few
dozen more personalities, practices and moods to take into
account there.  (Keep in mind [the power structure of 
everything 2|the editorial staff] is also
human...they are neither [golem] or [homonculi].  
Objectivity, while a heady goal, is ultimately unattainable.)


It's that complex.
It's that simple.  


&lt;p&gt;
The only advice I can
give you is to not take it personally.  Then again, it's quite
possibly somebody who has simply decided they don't like you.
&lt;p&gt;
Nevermind.  
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;
It depends.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;p&gt;







&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;


</doctext>
  <node_id>905370</node_id>
  <type_nodetype>13</type_nodetype>
  <title>Why did my writeup get voted down??</title>
</node>
